Chapter 2213: Chu Du Versus Hei Lou Lan

This was a nameless grassland, the ground was dry and desolate, there was barely any vegetation except yellowish wilting wild grass.

The sky was gray and hazy, no sunlight could be seen.

A cold and dark wind blew on the faces of the immortals.

At this ordinary location, tens of Gu Immortals were gathered!

All of their attention was placed on two people.

The male immortal wore a yellowish brown leather robe unique to Northern Plains, he had a red and thick leather belt, as well as pitch-black leather shoes.

The loose robe could not conceal his muscular body, while his face was nothing extraordinary, he looked very plain.

But nobody present could ignore him despite that.

Because his name was Chu Du.

The Domination Immortal!

And opposing him, there was a female immortal.

The female immortal wore a half-mask covering her nose, mouth and cheeks, only revealing the upper half of her face, which showed her strong contours, sharp and long brows, bright eyes and a bold aura.

She was Fairy Black Moon, a powerful expert who challenged countless people and had never suffered a loss since her rise in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world!

As for her true identity as Hei Lou Lan, few Gu Immortals knew.

Not long ago, Hei Lou Lan defeated one of the most prominent members of Liu tribe, rank seven Gu Immortal expert Liu Chang. She challenged Chu Du thereafter.

Chu Du did not back down, he directly agreed.

Once news of this battle was spread, the tension of Northern Plains' Gu Immortals rose, they paid huge attention to it.

Right now, the time for the two immortals' fight had arrived.

"Chu Du, you have finally arrived." Battle intent surged in Hei Lou Lan's eyes, blazing like flames.

"The contest of strength path, I have been looking forward to this." Chu Du replied happily: "Regardless of the outcome today, fairy, I would like to invite you to my Chu tribe as a guest, we can exchange our experiences in cultivating strength path."

Hei Lou Lan snorted coldly: "Chu Du, I've heard of your great name since long ago. But if you want to exchange pointers, we will have to see if you are qualified."

Chu Du smiled: "Please have the first move."

Hei Lou Lan did not stand on ceremony, her body flew out like lightning, rising up and flying towards the upper clouds.

Whoosh whoosh whoosh!

Waves of human figures descended from the clouds, crashing towards Chu Du like meteors.

Chu Du raised his head and immediately retreated upon seeing this.

He was very fast, after pulling some distance, he used his killer move as he pushed with both palms.

Boom...

A surge of great strength burst out, air currents were generated, Hei Lou Lan's strength path phantoms shattered like bursting bubbles against this powerful attack.

Chu Du pushed with his palms again, clearing out the dark clouds in the sky, exposing the clear skies and radiant sunlight.

Hei Lou Lan, who had hidden herself in the cloud layer was also exposed as a result.

Hei Lou Lan had a serious expression, after the concealment of the dark clouds, her killer move was already prepared.

At the next moment, her hands clenched into fists, raising them above her head before slamming them down towards Chu Du's direction.

With a thunderous sound, air was squeezed and distorted as the fist shadows instantly arrived in front of Chu Du.

Chu Du raised both arms, blocking the attack.

Bam.

There was a loud collision as he was forced back by a hundred steps.

But soon, he stopped in the air, shrugging his shoulders, a layer of dust fell from his sleeves.

He was completely unharmed!

Hei Lou Lan was not surprised at all, she continued to rain down a flurry of unceasing attacks.

Chu Du blocked her attacks time and time again while retaliating in response.

Both sides were separated by some distance, they attacked with long-ranged methods that caused incredible commotions.

The observing immortals were all staring at the two of them with fixed gazes.

"So exciting, to think that strength path Gu Immortals would have so many outstanding long-ranged methods."

"Currently, it seems that Fairy Black Moon and Chu Du are evenly matched."

"Hmph, now is too early to make that conclusion," Chou Lao Wu snorted coldly, "Strength path Gu Immortals are strongest at close combat, they are still using long-ranged methods to probe each other now."

Chu Du was firm as a mountain while Hei Lou Lan displayed many outstanding long-ranged methods, after more than ten rounds of combat, the two sides suddenly charged and clashed in the center.

With that loud sound, all of the immortals jolted.

"They are fighting seriously now!"

"This is an extremely rare contest of strength path!"

"Whoever wins this will be the number one strength path cultivator in the current world."

In the current five regions, there were very few strength path Gu Immortals.

After all, strength path had been declining for a long time, far beyond half a century worth of degradation.

Before Hei Lou Lan appeared, Chu Du was publicly recognized as a strength path expert in the five regions, he had quite the reputation. With the sudden appearance of Hei Lou Lan, most Gu Immortals were shocked by her path. To think that another anomaly would arise in strength path!

Under everyone's gaze, the two continued to rain down punches and kicks at each other, it was an intense fight.

Attacks and defenses were unleashed and put up continually, each move had an incredible amount of strength in them.

Be they Chu Du or Hei Lou Lan, neither had the intention to retreat, they fought strength with strength, ferocity with ferocity!

The battle between strength path Gu Immortals could be said to be plain and simple, it was not as glamorous as other paths. But in the hearts of many Gu Immortals present, a chill started to form.

"Even though strength path is declining, strength path Gu Immortals are not to be underestimated."

"If I had to fight against either Chu Du or Fairy Black Moon, the outcome would be disastrous!"

Each attack by Chu Du or Hei Lou Lan would cause a thunderous sound that twisted and distorted the air, air currents surged as wind continued to form from their impacts.

Compared to long-ranged methods, strength path excelled more at close combat.

A Gu Immortal with superb cultivation in strength path would be threatening in their every punch and kick.

Their advantage in close combat was regarding the aspect of attack frequency.

Hei Lou Lan and Chu Du fought quicker and quicker, the observing Gu Immortals tried to imagine themselves as either party and felt cold sweat pouring down their foreheads.

"In the future, if I meet any strength path Gu Immortal, I must not let them get close to me!"

"The punches and kicks are unleashed too frequently, there is no time to prepare killer moves in such a fight. Without killer moves, how can anyone defend against such intense attacks?"

More than ten rounds passed again.

Chu Du gradually gained the upper hand.

Even though Hei Lou Lan was strong and had many methods, her combat experience still paled in comparison to Chu Du.

Her cultivation time was far less than Chu Du.

Chu Du accumulated his advantage through his immensely rich combat experience. After adding up all these advantages, he started to suppress Hei Lou Lan.

Chen Cheng, Yin Wu Que, and the rest had grim expressions.

"This cannot go on, I need to take a risk!" Hei Lou Lan's gaze turned sharp as a blade, flashing for an instant.

She knew that if she did not change her fighting style now, if this went on, she would definitely lose.

At the next moment, Hei Lou Lan shouted loudly as she rained punches and kicks on Chu Du with rapid intensity.

Chu Du was like a reef by the sea, no matter how intense the waves were, he remained motionless.

Hei Lou Lan was not surprised, while Chu Du defended himself, she quickly moved back and started preparing her killer move.

Chu Du smiled as he quickly approached her!

"Oh no!" Chen Cheng saw this and gasped aloud.

The observing Gu Immortals saw this and knew that Chu Du had waited for this opportunity for some time.

Chu Du erupted with shocking speed, rapidly getting closer to Hei Lou Lan.

Hei Lou Lan had no choice but to helplessly stop her killer move activation, she fought against Chu Du with punches and kicks, blocking the other party's unceasing attacks.

But because of this, by stopping her killer move midway, the activation failure caused a backlash that caused severe internal injuries to Hei Lou Lan.

Chu Du created a battle opportunity, he made great use of it and fought against Hei Lou Lan until she could only defend herself.

Chu Du had the complete advantage now!

A wave of cheers erupted.

These voices came from Chu Du's god-children as well as the supreme elders of Chu tribe.

"Hmph, don't rejoice too early."

"Fairy Black Moon has not used her trump card yet!"

Hei Lou Lan's supporters had grim expressions, they rebuked.

Totem killer move — Dark Capital Strength Biao[1]!

At the next moment, Hei Lou Lan's body shook.

A tiger roared, its huge black claws sent Chu Du flying.

The giant black tiger flapped its wings and vanished on the spot, appearing behind Chu Du.

Chu Du quickly defended himself, even though he blocked the dark capital strength biao's attack again, his body was still sent flying like a cannonball, crashing towards the ground from the force created.

"It's here! Fairy Black Moon's signature method — Dark Capital Strength Biao!" Someone shouted in excitement.

Chou Lao Wu had a cold expression, this was the first time he saw it: "This totem killer move is too convenient. It can stay dormant on the skin during normal times and be activated with a single thought when needed."

"Indeed." Hao Zhen gritted his teeth, "If not for this move, our first supreme elder would have obtained victory already."

[1] Tiger with wings. Back

Chapter 2214: You Have Won This Battle

The dark capital strength biao was incredibly fast, it was hard to deal with in the first place.

More importantly, after Hei Lou Lan stabilized her position, she quickly used a healing method on herself before joining the fight again.

She had great coordination with the dark capital strength biao, they attacked from the left and right, firmly suppressing Chu Du.

Chu Du was in a pitiful state, many areas of his robe were torn, showing that his defenses were no longer holding up.

Blood soon appeared on his lips, his injuries were slowly accumulating.

Chu tribe's Gu Immortals had grim expression, in the current situation, they could not see hope of Chu Du turning this around.

The dark capital strength biao gave Hei Lou Lan too great of an advantage!

"You will lose!" Hei Lou Lan shouted with momentum, unleashing her killer move, eight directional strength fight.

Chu Du was surrounded by countless figures, he could not break out for the time being.

Suddenly, a shadow casted down from above him, it was the dark capital strength biao!

It opened its mouth to bite at Chu Du. If this bite connected, Chu Du would be heavily injured, if not dead.

At the moment of crisis, Chu Du laughed loudly instead: "Finally caught you!"

At the next moment, strength path giant hand appeared and grabbed forcefully.

The dark capital strength biao was caught unguarded and growled loudly, it wanted to struggle.

But after only one breath of time, the strength path giant hand firmly held onto it and slammed it to the ground.

Boom!

There was a loud sound as the ground shook, rocks were sent flying and dust clouds rose.

Immortal killer move — Battle Strength Transpiration!

Chu Du suddenly erupted with an intense aura as his body expanded to the size of a ten meter giant.

His entire body turned red, all of the pores on his body opened up, as his sweat turned into steam, surrounding his body.

Immortal killer move — Heaven and Earth Combined Strength!

Chu Du straightened both arms before clapping them together in front of his chest.

At the next moment, the immortals gasped, Hei Lou Lan's expression changed.

The surrounding thousand li were enveloped by a formless force, the Gu Immortals were restrained and unable to move easily, they felt like bugs that had fallen into oil.

Affected by this killer move, the speed of the dark capital strength biao fell drastically, its threat towards Chu Du also plunged to rock bottom.

"This is a quasi-battlefield killer move!" Hei Lou Lan gritted her teeth, Chu Du's move was amazing and beyond her expectations.

"I did not want to use this." Hei Lou Lan snorted internally, activating the expend strength Immortal Gu in her immortal aperture.

This rank seven Immortal Gu was lent to her by Longevity Heaven secretly, other than that, there was also a killer move that used expend strength Immortal Gu as the core, it was called seventy-percent expended strength.

At the crucial moment, Hei Lou Lan immediately activated this move.

This move's preparation had no aura and was stealthy, only when it was used, it unleashed an overwhelmingly extraordinary burst of aura.

Chu Du quickly tried to dodge but he did not succeed.

After getting hit by this move, every action or killer move of his took much more effort to complete, by at least more than fifty percent.

While Chu Du's condition fell, Hei Lou Lan unleashed a flurry of attacks again.

The battle was in a heated stage, both sides were stuck in a deadlock.

The observing immortals retreated at once, they left the range of heaven and earth combined strength, becoming more at ease as they continued to watch the battle.

"Regardless of this battle's result, these two are peak characters among Northern Plains' rank seven experts!"

"Such terrifying battle strength, I'm afraid they might be able to challenge rank eight Gu Immortals as well."

"Chu Du, Black Moon... they are the support pillars of strength path in the current world, undoubtedly."

The Gu Immortals sighed to themselves, at this point in the battle, be they Chu Du or Hei Lou Lan, they had earned the respect and recognition of everyone.

Such evenly matched opponents made the immortals even more excited to see the eventual winner.

"Awesome, this is really great." Chu Du had many bone fractures and his robe was dyed red, but he laughed heartily and expressed his excitement towards this battle.

Hei Lou Lan gritted her teeth and did not speak, she had gotten into a disadvantage once again.

The reason was still the difference in combat experience.

Chu Du was superior to Hei Lou Lan in every tiny detail. As they accumulated,they eventually affected the entire battle.

Hei Lou Lan tried all ways to regain her footing but the more she fought, the more tiny weaknesses she exposed, giving Chu Du even more opportunities to take advantage of.

"He was clearly hit by my seventy-percent expended strength, how can he still have such stamina?" Seeing that Chu Du was not getting tired, Hei Lou Lan could not help but feel a bit shocked.

Chu Du had outstanding strength, even though Hei Lou Lan was using her full strength, she could not take down Chu Du.

Currently, she could only hope that the effect of seventy-percent expended strength would tire Chu Du out.

But another ten or so rounds passed.

Before Chu Du even got tired, Hei Lou Lan was already completely at a disadvantage, the situation was dangerous!

Hei Lou Lan gritted her teeth secretly, she was not willing to fail. In this situation, she could only take a risk and try.

At the next moment, the dark capital strength biao growled and jumped towards Hei Lou Lan.

Hei Lou Lan advanced instead of moving aside, entering the dark capital strength biao's body in mid air.

With a flash of dark light, the dark capital strength biao shrank in size, turning into a half-beast half-man form, it became a layer of armor on Hei Lou Lan's body, it seemed like smoke or an illusion.

This was a higher level use of a totem killer move!

When the Gu Immortal combined with the totem, their battle strength would surge immensely!

"Chu Du, time to go down!" Hei Lou Lan shouted, the biao wings flapped, she instantly arrived before Chu Du.

Chu Du raised his arms.

Hei Lou Lan's iron fists landed on his arms, the huge force erupted like resounding thunder, the surrounding air was forced aside as Chu Du flew out uncontrollably towards the ground.

But Chu Du landed with both feet on the ground, creating a huge and long trench behind him. While he was still retreating, Hei Lou Lan suddenly appeared above him.

Boom!

There was another attack as Hei Lou Lan sent Chu Du flying to the ground again.

Bam bam bam...

Hei Lou Lan floated in the air, raining down fist shadows incessantly.

The ground shook as smoke appeared, her terrifying strength caused the spectators to turn pale.

"Lord Chu Du!"

"Godfather!!"

Chu tribe's Gu Immortals shouted loudly in worry.

Hei Lou Lan was too powerful now, she was almost dominating the scene, Chu Du had no way of retaliating.

"Enough... stop now, Black Moon." From the pit, Chu Du's voice could be heard as he spoke with difficulty.

But Hei Lou Lan did not listen to him, she continued to punch endlessly.

"Is Chu Du admitting defeat?" Wu Guang was excited as he spoke.

"Something is not right! Master seems to be in a weird state." Chen Cheng's expression changed.

Hearing this, everyone realized that Hei Lou Lan's gaze was like a wild beast, she seemed to have lost her reasoning, she could only control this killer move through her instincts to slaughter.

Chu tribe's Gu Immortals were all happy now.

"There is still hope!"

"Great. As long as first supreme elder gets through this, he will win!"

"This killer move is too powerful. If Fairy Black Moon's killer move activation fails, she might face a backlash and even lose her life."

But right at this moment, a figure flew out.

It was Chu Du!

But what Chu Du did next was out of everyone's expectations.

He had forcefully endured the rampaging attacks, disregarding his own life to approach Hei Lou Lan and place his arm on her shoulder.

A huge vibration force was emitted, Hei Lou Lan and the dark capital strength biao were separated.

Hei Lou Lan regained her senses and her pupils shrank immediately.

She was shocked to find out that her left fist had penetrated the right side of Chu Du's chest! But Chu Du used a method to save her and prevent her from suffering the immense backlash from her killer move.

"Why?" At once, Hei Lou Lan fell into deep confusion and disbelief.

But right at this moment, the dark capital strength biao's ferocity did not lower, it appeared behind Chu Du and bit harshly.

"Stop!" Hei Lou Lan shouted internally and willed to try to stop the dark capital strength biao.

In this situation, if Chu Du was hit by it, he would definitely die!

But the dark capital strength biao was not under Hei Lou Lan's control, it was incredibly fierce.

Right when Hei Lou Lan thought Chu Du was about to die, a surge of aura burst out of Chu Du's body.

His killer move was unleashed, the dark capital strength biao was sent flying from one attack.

The immortals were shocked!

"Rank, rank eight cultivation level?!"

"Chu Du became a rank eight Gu Immortal?"

"Our first supreme elder is rank eight? When did he advance?!"

Hei Lou Lan stared with wide eyes and looked fixedly at Chu Du: "Why?"

While speaking, she retracted her left hand from Chu Du's chest and placed it on his shoulder.

A killer move was activated by Hei Lou Lan, it was not an offensive killer move but a healing method instead.

Chu Du's expression was pale, he accepted her good intentions as he smiled: "Ever since you started challenging people, I started noticing you, Fairy Black Moon."

"Do you know? Even if you did not challenge me, I would issue you a challenge as well!"

"To have a fair battle!"

"Because... strength path has been silent for far too long."

"Your emergence made me really happy. Continue on this path, Black Moon."

"Revitalize strength path and let it shine gloriously again!"

Chu Du expressed his aspirations.

Looking at his dazzling eyes, Hei Lou Lan was silent.

The dark capital strength biao had returned after being repelled by Chu Du.

But now, Hei Lou Lan regained control of it.

The dark capital strength biao was heavily damaged, it went back onto Hei Lou Lan's skin.

Hei Lou Lan looked at Chu Du deeply before leaving.

Before departing, she said: "Chu Du, you have won this battle."

This battle that caused a commotion in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal ended in Chu Du's victory, but the exact outcome of this fight was far beyond everyone's expectations.

Once Chu Du displayed rank eight cultivation level, he became a higher-up in the Gu Immortal world, be they himself or Chu tribe, their reputation soared!

And in that intense battle, Chu Du first sealed his own cultivation level to fight against Fairy Black Moon as a rank seven. He then disregarded his own life to save her.

Such actions caused the neutral Gu Immortals to gain good feelings towards him. Even those who supported Fairy Black Moon like Yin Wu Que, Chen Cheng, and Wu Guang secretly felt admiration towards him.

After returning to Chu tribe, his god-children suggested to hold a celebratory banquet and invite the immortals, to make use of this result and elevate Chu tribe's status.

But Chu Du rejected it without second thought.

He was very low-profile regarding the result of this battle.

However, news that he became a rank eight Gu Immortal still caused a huge commotion in Northern Plains' current situation.

Days later, Heavenly Court and Longevity Heaven let out even more surprising news that shook the world.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had revived successfully, while Gu Yue Fang Yuan had become a refinement path Demon Venerable!

The world was in an uproar, all the immortals were shocked.

Chapter 2215: Heaven Refining Demon Venerable!

Fang Yuan returned to Eastern Sea.

Under the setting sun, the surface of the sea was dyed red. Birds were chirping out loud, a warm sea breeze was blowing.

This place was some distance away from Eastern Sea's Xia clan, it was not considered close.

"This place will do." Fang Yuan quickly descended, landing on a relatively small deserted island.

Several investigative killer moves were activated, Fang Yuan had complete control over the island, he did not detect any threats or suspicious matters.

Fang Yuan directly took out the five regional limit formation.

Soon, five colored smoke mixed together and enveloped the island, before spreading towards the sky and sea.

If he were still rank eight, after escaping from Crazed Demon Cave, he would choose the headquarters of Eastern Sea's Xia clan, or go to immemorial white heaven in secret and hide himself to recuperate.

But Fang Yuan had rank nine cultivation level now, he was a venerable, he could do things openly without fear.

If Star Constellation Immortal Venerable or Giant Sun Immortal Venerable came to attack him now, Fang Yuan would be happy to see that happen.

Fang Yuan slowly shut his eyes as his divine sense peered into the sovereign immortal aperture.

He had already accumulated several beads of rank nine immortal essence.

Rank eight immortal essence was known as white litchi immortal essence, rank nine immortal essence was slightly larger and looked like an apricot, it was orange-yellow in color.

It was yellow apricot immortal essence!

Fang Yuan was familiar with the appearance of rank nine immortal essence since long ago, because he had obtained Giant Sun's immortal essence as well as Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's remaining immortal essence.

But now, he felt some surging emotions internally.

After all, this was his personal yellow apricot immortal essence!

Using the yellow apricot immortal essence, Fang Yuan activated a method!

Refinement path killer move — Refine Self!

A pale yellow light that was the size of a fist flowed out from the area near Fang Yuan's stomach. The yellow light flowed slowly around his entire body.

The emphasis was on Fang Yuan's injuries.

Fang Yuan had over a hundred injuries, most of them were only dealt with superficially while he was on the way back.

Even now, many of the wounds were still bleeding and covered in golden light or starlight specks, they were lingering on his bones, or his mashed up flesh.

As the pale yellow light appeared, all of the starlight and golden aurora was cleansed. This meant that the dao marks that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable left on Fang Yuan's body were all refined by him.

But the process of refinement was not comfortable, an intense pain could be felt.

Fang Yuan's body was shivering, his expression turned pale, soon, sweat covered his forehead.

Eventually, the pale yellow light lingered on the area of Fang Yuan's detached arm. After an hour, the light faded away.

Fang Yuan let out a breath of air, he finally relaxed.

After resting for a moment, he immediately used a compound killer move, man as before.

At the next moment, his injuries were fully healed, his arm was also fully restored.

But when Fang Yuan exerted strength using that arm, he still felt a sense of weakness from it.

But this was already satisfactory to him.

Fang Yuan had severe injuries but Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable were also no better.

He was almost certain that their efficiency at healing injuries was lower than him.

Because Fang Yuan had the killer move refine self, this killer move could refine all of the dao marks on the Gu cultivator's body into their own. The origin of this move was the killer move that Fang Yuan once used, self cleansing.

Using this, in the battle of Crazed Demon Cave, Fang Yuan refined all of the dao marks of the flying star killer move, countering Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's consecutive move.

His physical injuries were healed, while his soul was at its peak condition, Fang Yuan started to resolve the matter of the sovereign immortal aperture.

The sovereign immortal aperture had a tribulation earlier because of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's killer move. At almost the same time, because of Fang Yuan's secret manipulation, he challenged the Heavenly Dao and endured the chaotic disaster.

The entire sovereign immortal aperture suffered huge losses, its foundation had fallen, compared to before the Crazed Demon Cave expedition, it had about twenty percent remaining.

It was simply in tatters, this was a pitiful sight.

"But I predicted that this would happen before the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, I prepared for it!"

Fang Yuan focused his mind, thoughts were expended, he activated another compound killer move — Landscape as Before.

The year essence pools and the sub-pools in various areas of the sovereign immortal aperture all opened their dams now.

The accumulated water of the River of Time formed into a vast silhouette under the effect of landscape as before, sweeping through the mini five regions as well as all the mini nine heavens.

The silhouette of the water of the River of Time soon receded entirely, but what remained were various resource points of mountains and rivers that were completely restored.

The Gu Immortals in the sovereign immortal aperture saw this sight and cheered loudly, their morale surged.

Fang Yuan lightly let out a breath of air.

Back then, when he created the year essence sub-pools and created time path areas, he had already prepared to use landscape as before for such a purpose.

After using this method, the water of the River of Time in the year essence pools was almost used up, the sovereign immortal aperture's time difference with the outside world also fell greatly.

A considerable amount of time was needed, until the year essence pools could gather enough water of the River of Time to accelerate the sovereign immortal aperture's time again.

At this point, forty percent of the sovereign immortal aperture's foundation had just been restored.

Which meant that the sovereign immortal aperture only had forty percent in total of losses remaining, this greatly reduced the time, energy, and resources needed to reconstruct his foundation.

The forty percent of losses were created by the chaotic disaster.

Even landscape as before was not useful for this. The Gu Immortals that died from the chaotic disaster were also not able to revive through Human Sea.

He had a lot of other losses as well.

The immortal essence expenditure was huge, he once had a vast amount of rank eight immortal essence, but now, he had about ten percent left, it was way below the safety margin, he was in a dangerous state.

This was also why Fang Yuan stopped and did not continue fighting against Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

But the good news was, as a venerable, Fang Yuan produced yellow apricot immortal essence, it was much more useful than white litchi immortal essence.

The bad news was, rank eight Immortal Gu Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus that once helped Fang Yuan greatly in terms of immortal essence storage became much less useful now.

At the same time, because the sovereign immortal aperture's time slowed greatly, Fang Yuan's immortal essence production speed was not high.

During this period of time, Fang Yuan needed to rest and manage his immortal essence, he also had to refine the natural dao marks of the outside world, he would need a lot of immortal essence.

"The lack of immortal essence is huge, while immortal essence stones are barely useful to me anymore."

"If I ignore everything and raise the sovereign immortal aperture's rate of time to the limit, that will not work either!" Fang Yuan frowned slightly.

Venerables faced a grand tribulation every ten years, a myriad tribulation every fifty years, and a chaotic disaster every one hundred years.

Unless they were dream path, pill path and so on, grand tribulations and myriad tribulations were no threat to Fang Yuan. Fang Yuan was only wary about the chaotic disasters every one hundred years.

Even though he had already gone through one chaotic disaster in Crazed Demon Cave.

That was only the Heavenly Dao blockade, it was far weaker than the chaotic disasters that would occur every one hundred years!

If the sovereign immortal aperture's time was too fast, Fang Yuan would quickly have to face the chaotic disaster, if he got heavily injured in the process, or even near the point of death, the other venerables would take advantage of the chance.

The replenishment of immortal essence was a problem, other than this, Fang Yuan also lost a large number of Immortal Gu.

In the first parts of the Crazed Demon Cave fight, after Gu Immortals died, Fang Yuan did not retrieve their Immortal Gu or immortal apertures.

In fact, the seven Immortal Gu Houses that Fang Yuan took out in Crazed Demon Cave, including Rising Cloud City, were all lost as well.

Fang Yuan's losses were so severe that no super force in the world barring Heavenly Court and Longevity Heaven could afford to endure them.

Thankfully, in the later parts of the Crazed Demon Cave fight, Fang Yuan purposely reduced his losses in this aspect. For example, when Zhan Bu Du died, the will that he left behind sent many of his precious transformation path Immortal Gu into treasure yellow heaven.

Other than Immortal Gu and immortal essence, many Gu Immortals died as well.

Steel Rush Warrior, Frost Butterfly Warrior, Xiao He Jian, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch, and even Fang Yuan's clone Zhan Bu Du, they had all died in Crazed Demon Cave. There were also those who died in the sovereign immortal aperture when they defended against the tribulations.

Most of them were revived through Human Sea, they had to re-cultivate to become immortal again.

There was also a group of them who could not be revived. Among them was the old Combat Beast King, a rank eight Gu Immortal.

Even Fang Yuan felt that it was a pity.

This old man had worked laboriously without complaint, he made great contributions towards the sovereign immortal aperture. But he was killed by the black fire, Fang Yuan could not revive him.

Other than these material losses, Fang Yuan also had some hidden losses.

Most importantly, he exposed too many killer moves.

In the Crazed Demon Cave battle, Fang Yuan had no choice but to expose many of his compound killer moves, as well as trump cards like refine self, totem killer moves, and others.

For a long time, these killer moves could not be used, they needed to be modified.

When he fights against the venerables in the future, if he were to use these killer moves without modification, Fang Yuan would be taking a huge risk.

But compared to his losses, Fang Yuan's gains were much higher!

In the Crazed Demon Cave battle, Fang Yuan had immense gains, he was undeniably the biggest winner out of everyone!!

Firstly, Fang Yuan ransacked the first seven layers and obtained a vast amount of chaotic dao mark immortal materials.

In the eighth layer of Crazed Demon Cave, he used Thieves Den to gain a vast amount of rank nine immortal materials. These rank nine immortal materials were enough for him to try to refine a rank nine Immortal Gu.

The second thing was Primordial Domain.

Fang Yuan had about the same amount of the Primordial Domain as Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, which was slightly less than Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Primordial Domain was extremely valuable, especially for Fang Yuan.

The third thing was Paradise Earth's Northern Plains true inheritance, as well as his heaven path cultivation experiences. These included the method to digest truthful floating ice and raise one's own heaven path cultivation level.

The fourth was information.

After the battle of Crazed Demon Cave, Fang Yuan gained an in-depth understanding of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, as well as the Heavenly Court and Longevity Heaven that they belonged to!

He was no longer kept in the dark like before.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's methods, their combat systems, as well as Heavenly Court's Door of Life and Death immortal graveyard, Transient White Cloud City Suppression painting path formation, Ruan Dan's pill path, Longevity Heaven's Eight Extremities formation, Calamity Luck Altar's luck changing golden light path, and others.

The fifth gain was also Fang Yuan's greatest gain.

His cultivation level rose to become venerable level.

This was a peak qualitative change!

From now onwards, he went from a chess piece to a player, he could openly plot against the world and rule over the five regions.

The history of humanity and variant humans would have no choice but to remember his name.

At this point, he stood on the same plane as the ten predecessors, he was like a sun that shone throughout the ages. All other Gu Immortals, regardless of their heroism or talent, were mere stars in the sky.

Gu Yue Fang Yuan!

The eleventh venerable of the Gu cultivator world.

A demonic cultivator who became venerable through refinement path.

According to Heavenly Court and Longevity Heaven, his title was —

Heaven Refining Demon Venerable!

Chapter 2216: Crying Because of Fang Yuan

Eastern Sea.

Shen clan headquarters, purple rosewood myriad sparrow island.

An elderly Gu Immortal stood in front of a stone door as he waited patiently.

The elderly Gu Immortal radiated rank eight aura, he was the current first supreme elder of Shen clan, holding high authority — Shen Cong Sheng!

Rumble...

As the door of the secret room was opened, two Gu Immortals walked out from within.

The person in front wore a grey robe and had shoulder length black and white hair, it was Shen Shang.

As a cultivator of human path, the stay in Divine Emperor City was his fortuitous encounter. After leaving Divine Emperor City, the black fire injury in his immortal aperture was completely healed, his battle strength surged to pseudo venerable level.

Shen Shang walked out of the stone door and stayed at the side, smiling at the Gu Immortal behind him: "Please come in."

This Gu Immortal wore a grey hemp garment, it was very simple and plain, but his muscular body could not be concealed. He wore a conical hat that could not hide his pale face and weakened state.

It was Lu Wei Yin, who had survived the battle in Crazed Demon Cave.

Lu Wei Yin bowed slightly and said: "Senior Shen's human path methods are extraordinary, thirty percent of my injuries have healed already. I can only repay this debt in the future."

Shen Shang laughed heartily: "No need to worry about it, don't call me senior either. We fought together in Crazed Demon Cave, having close cooperation, with our friendship, you can just treat me as an equal."

Shen Cong Sheng laughed as well: "Seniors, the banquet has been prepared, please come with me."

Before Lu Wei Yin gave any modest reply, Shen Shang laughed and grabbed his arm, bringing him to the banquet enthusiastically.

The banquet was held outdoors in the open, at the peak of rosewood myriad sparrow island.

There were three people in the pavilion, Shen Shang sat at the main seat, Lu Wei Yin sat beside him as the guest, while Shen Cong Sheng sat at the end respectfully.

There was no need to comment about the beautiful and delicious food and wine on the table, Lu Wei Yin only took a small bite before he gazed afar.

He saw that the sea was calm as a mirror, having no waves at all, the setting sun was radiating brightly, and the evening clouds were like blazing flames.

"Such a beautiful sight." Lu Wei Yin praised.

At this moment, the countless birds and sparrows chirped on the island, countless purple rosewood branches shook with the cries of the birds, emitting beautiful sounds.

At once, the blend of sounds created a medley that spread far and wide, towards the sea and sky that stretched to the horizon.

Lu Wei Yin could not help but show an expression of indulgence, he shut his eyes to savor the moment. After a long while, he opened his eyes and let out a breath of air: "I've heard of the reputation of Eastern Sea Shen clan's rosewood myriad sparrow island. After seeing it today, it truly lives up to that reputation. After surviving Crazed Demon Cave and seeing this beautiful sight, my heart has calmed down, sigh, it is great to be alive."

Lu Wei Yin's strength was at the peak of rank eight, aside from his defense, which was firmly at pseudo venerable level.

However, the battle in Crazed Demon Cave made him feel extremely weak.

There were many crises and trials that caused Lu Wei Yin to be on the brink of death multiple times, recalling these dangerous moments, Lu Wei Yin still felt some lingering fear now.

Shen Cong Sheng showed an expression of curiosity as he inquired: "If not for Heavenly Court's and Longevity Heaven's declarations, the entire five regions would still be kept in the dark. What exactly happened in Crazed Demon Cave? Not only did Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable revive, Gu Yue Fang Yuan even became Heaven Refining Demon Venerable?"

Heavenly Court and Longevity Heaven both suffered losses, even though they had gains too, Fang Yuan was the biggest winner. Thus, they did not describe the details of Crazed Demon Cave to the rest of the world.

With this huge commotion, after the initial shock of the Gu Immortals, they started to gain deep curiosity.

Shen Cong Sheng was no exception.

Lu Wei Yin and Shen Shang looked at each other before retelling the complex story of the battle in Crazed Demon Cave together.

After Shen Cong Sheng heard their story, he became silent.

The pursuit of Limitless Demon Venerable, the scheming Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, the powerful Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, the pitiful Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable, and the immense restraint of Gu Yue Fang Yuan...

This battle was at a whole new level!

To the extent that even Demon Immortal Qi Jue, Zhan Bu Du, Qi Sea Ancestor, Lu Wei Yin, and Shen Shang were mere side characters in comparison.

The price of this battle was also shocking beyond belief.

Pseudo venerables like Zhan Bu Du and Demon Immortal Qi Jue died. Fang Yuan lost about fifty Gu Immortal subordinates, only half of Longevity Heaven's Eight Extremities were left. And in Crazed Demon Cave, countless lifeforms including Nie Kuang Feng, Bu Tian Kong, and Duan Hu had died!

Eventually, Limitless Demon Venerable failed in pursuing eternal life, while Fang Yuan ended up as the biggest winner.

Shen Cong Sheng frowned and asked the two immortals: "There are three things I do not understand. Firstly, if I were Limitless Demon Venerable, why would I rush at that moment and take such a risk? With such strength, couldn't he have suppressed the entire world and built another formation if this Crazed Demon formation was not enough to achieve his goal?"

Shen Shang shook his head slightly: "Limitless Demon Venerable is a true Dao pursuer, after a million years of preparation and planning, how could he relent without giving it a test?"

Lu Wei Yin added: "He could not last long in that condition either. Although he seemed to have revived, he was not a true living Gu Immortal. At least, after his death, he did not have a flesh-and-blood body, there was no immortal aperture either, in fact, he turned back into truthful floating ice."

"So that's it." Shen Cong Sheng nodded and asked again: "Secondly, are they really ignoring Spectral Soul Demon Venerable and letting him remain in the void of the ninth layer of Crazed Demon Cave?"

Lu Wei Yin pondered and said: "Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was first manipulated by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and experienced a surge in emotions, he almost lost his memories and only vaguely remembered Lord Paradise Earth. Afterwards, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was released from the Door of Life and Death by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, he actually went to block the hole of the world boundary of his own accord, that was out of our expectations."

"He did not regain his memories and sanity like what we anticipated. There were no changes in his emotions, it was like he was completely emotionless, but he treated the world boundary's hole as the biggest threat. He used his body to block it and ignored everything else, that was truly a strange condition, as if... he was a soul beast."

Shen Shang said: "Us two discussed between ourselves regarding Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's condition, but we had no conclusion. Now it seems that even the venerables have no answer, they can merely make guesses. After Fang Yuan gained the upper hand and snatched the final truthful floating ice, while Spectral Soul Demon Venerable focused on suppressing the world boundary's hole, the three venerables stopped fighting. After the battle of Crazed Demon Cave, they are all severely weakened, since the hole is handled by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, ignoring him is the best move for now."

Saying so, Shen Shang looked at Lu Wei Yin and said: "As for what they will do in the future and whether Spectral Soul Demon Venerable can regain his sanity, none of us can guess."

Lu Wei Yin nodded, his expression turned more solemn.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable had a deeply murderous nature, without regaining his sanity, he could only stay in the ninth layer void and not escape. But if he regained his sanity, the five regions and two heavens would fall into chaos.

Shen Cong Sheng asked his final question: "And thirdly, Fang Yuan's schemes to become a venerable were exposed by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable. But there are still things I cannot understand. How did Fang Yuan get so many new killer moves? He had an endless number of compound killer moves, totem killer moves, and even Dang Hun Luo Po Seal that made use of Dang Hun Mountain, Luo Po Valley, and Reverse Flow River. I really cannot understand it, I thought Fang Yuan was always specialized in the wisdom path aspect of blocking others' deductions. His wisdom Gu was also used up in Heavenly Court, how could he still have so many killer moves?"

"Unless he has made some important progression in wisdom path? But isn't this growth simply too big?"

"So be it if he had Dang Hun Luo Po Seal, but that killer move that allowed him to escape from the Door of Life and Death used the three secluded domains of heaven and earth as the cores, he had nearly replicated the road of life."

Lu Wei Yin and Shen Shang shook their heads, they had no idea either.

The former sighed: "If Fang Yuan was not so unpredictable, he would not have become the biggest winner in this contest."

The latter said: "Regarding this, I have some guesses."

The three immortals ate and spoke, discussing their theories.

After filling their bellies, Shen Cong Sheng took out a cup and made tea for Lu Wei Yin and Shen Shang.

Lu Wei Yin took a look and became quite curious, he asked: "Is this your six sound tea?"

Shen Cong Sheng smiled: "It is just a small creation, allow me to embarrass myself."

Lu Wei Yin had a serious expression: "Shen clan's six sound tea is famous in the world, to think that I am lucky enough to try it. There is a term in luck path called 'every cloud has a silver lining', there is also another saying 'there is bound to be great fortune after surviving a huge crisis'. Haha, I am really lucky today."

Six sound tea was a set of six tea cups.

These six cups of tea had very specific details when it came to the brewing process, temperature, cup used, sequence of drinking, and exact way to drink.

Shen Cong Sheng expended rank eight immortal materials to brew the first cup of tea, it was called autumn wood sound.

This tea was crystal clear, it was like the sky devoid of clouds, extremely pure and intact. The moment Lu Wei Yin drank it, he felt refreshed, his mind became clear, it was pure and cleansed. It was as if he had turned into a carefree flying bird, or a cool breeze, moving casually in the autumn skies, forgetting all his worries.

Shen Cong Sheng made the second cup of tea, it was called cloud flow tea.

This tea had a special texture, it was soft as cotton unlike normal tea. It melted when it entered the mouth, turning into a slightly cold stream of water that flowed down his throat, it was drunk in one mouthful without doubt.

He made the third cup of tea, it was called river mournful cry.

But halfway through, tears flowed down Shen Cong Sheng's cheeks, he failed to brew the tea successfully.

"I am ashamed, I am ashamed." Shen Cong Sheng quickly wiped his tears and apologized.

Lu Wei Yin's injuries had been treated by Shen Shang, he was also hosted so enthusiastically by them, he knew that the main show was coming, he quickly asked what they wanted to hear: "First supreme elder of Shen clan, why are you crying?"

Shen Cong Sheng answered: "Thank you for the concern, I am merely tearing up in guilt. It has been a thousand years since my Shen clan was established. To think that it would face the crisis of extermination during my generation, I, Shen Cong Sheng, am truly incompetent and useless. This beautiful rosewood myriad sparrow island and our countless clansmen are all going to perish."

Shen Shang sighed deeply.

Lu Wei Yin asked: "Are you two worried about Fang Yuan?"

"Precisely. Not long ago, information spread that this Lord Demon Venerable returned to Eastern Sea, picking a mortal island to set up his five restriction profound light qi that encompassed the surrounding ten thousand li! I am truly worried and fearful now, the whole of Shen clan is worried and fearful, in fact, the entire Eastern Sea Gu Immortal world is worried and fearful!" Shen Cong Sheng said this, a large amount of tears flowed down his face again.

Chapter 2217: Delicious Wine Becomes Flavorless

The great Shen clan first supreme elder was crying with a tearful expression now.

Part of it was definitely Shen Cong Sheng's inner fear towards Fang Yuan, but he had deeper goals as well.

With the combined announcement of Heavenly Court and Longevity Heaven, such news could not be fake.

Fang Yuan became Heaven Refining Demon Venerable, while news like Qi Sea Ancestor being Fang Yuan's clone became known throughout the world.

Before this, Eastern Sea's righteous path had been defending Qi Sea Ancestor as they made the Righteous Qi Alliance, to contest against the variant human alliance under Fang Yuan's control.

It turned out that both leaders were Fang Yuan after all, it could be said that the entirety of Eastern Sea's righteous path clans were toyed around in the hands of Fang Yuan.

After Shen Cong Sheng found out about the truth, he felt anger and humiliation, but soon, fear and unrest followed.

Shen clan was an Eastern Sea super force, it had huge businesses and seven seas under its control, but how could they face Fang Yuan?

Back when Fang Yuan was still a pseudo venerable, Eastern Sea's super forces had joined together unprecedentedly and nominated Qi Sea Ancestor to lead them. This caused their situation to stabilize.

Now that Fang Yuan was a venerable, Shen clan and the other super forces could not escape his wrath.

Because they were located in Eastern Sea, they could not move elsewhere.

Even if they wanted to move, where could they go?

Southern Border and Western Desert were impossible, since the absence of a venerable meant that Fang Yuan could chase after them if he was unhappy, and they would be doomed.

Other than those regions, Central Continent and Northern Plains each had their own venerable who could resist Fang Yuan. But they already had their own super forces, how could Shen clan and the rest develop there? If they stayed in Eastern Sea, Fang Yuan would bully them, but if they went to Central Continent or Northern Plains, would Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable not suppress them? The five regions chaotic war was bound to happen, if Shen clan joined either venerable, when war broke out, they would be used as cannon fodder.

Thus, Shen Cong Sheng gathered the elite Gu Immortals and discussed for a while, he decided that joining Fang Yuan was the best choice for them.

Even though it was quite embarrassing, Fang Yuan was now a Demon Venerable, everyone would understand their actions.

After Shen Cong Sheng made up his mind to join Fang Yuan, he thought about it more deeply: Since he was going to join Fang Yuan, Shen clan had to be the first clan to do so, it would give them more advantages. If Shen clan took the lead and worked with a pseudo venerable like Lu Wei Yin, stirring other Eastern Sea righteous path forces to join Fang Yuan, they would leave a good impression on Fang Yuan.

Shen Cong Sheng secretly told this plan to Shen Shang, after he thought about it for a while, he decided that it was possible. Thus, they had to convince Lu Wei Yin first.

Shen Shang felt that they had a good chance of convincing Lu Wei Yin.

Even though he had only met Lu Wei Yin shortly, they had a deep connection. Shen Shang had once received Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's guidance while Lu Wei Yin was his Southern Border inheritor.

If they looked at this from the Central Continent sect system, they were disciple brothers.

Furthermore, during the battle of Crazed Demon Cave, Lu Wei Yin and Shen Shang had worked together without any internal conflict. After returning, Shen Shang used his human path methods to heal Lu Wei Yin. If he were to use only his own earth path methods, it would take a long time to recover!

At once, Shen Cong Sheng cried while Shen Shang drank tea by the side, they were both waiting for Lu Wei Yin's response.

Lu Wei Yin sighed internally.

He had already understood that Shen Shang had an unclear relationship with Fang Yuan, they had worked together during the fate war to fight Heavenly Court. In Crazed Demon Cave, after Shen Shang left Divine Emperor City, he immediately cooperated and fought against Heavenly Court as a result of Fang Yuan's words.

Then what about Lu Wei Yin?

Where should he go?

Lu Wei Yin had been considering this question for a long time.

After the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, the situation of the world changed drastically.

Three venerables were in a standoff, but there was still the possibility of other venerables reviving.

Everything needed to be reconsidered.

Lu Wei Yin, who had pseudo venerable battle strength, was clear of his own situation. Fighting against a venerable was courting death. But in certain situations, pseudo venerables were still capable of influencing the victory and defeat of venerables.

The battle in Crazed Demon Cave was proof of this.

When Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable got into a deadlock, they first invited Fang Yuan before asking the other pseudo venerables to join their side. These people were the crucial pieces needed to tilt victory in their favor.

In Crazed Demon Cave, even after the three venerables stopped fighting, Fang Yuan and the other venerables did not deal with Lu Wei Yin and the rest.

Other than the fact that they were in poor condition and were wary of each other's actions, thus being unable to take risks, if they tried to kill the pseudo venerables and failed, they would be forcing them to join the other sides.

Thus, Lu Wei Yin and the rest returned safely.

Lu Wei Yin pondered for a while before saying: "If Lord Paradise Earth were still around, I would definitely follow him. The reason why I helped Fang Yuan to ambush Spectral Soul during the pursuit battle was to use his strength to help Lord Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable revive. But now, he has been killed by Fang Yuan..."

Lu Wei Yin gritted his teeth, showing anger on his face.

If Paradise Earth were to be killed by either Giant Sun Immortal Venerable or Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, Lu Wei Yin might still feel better.

But it was Fang Yuan who killed Paradise Earth.

While Fang Yuan managed to escape from Spectral Soul Demon Venerable because of Lu Wei Yin's desperate attempt to ambush him.

Shen Shang observed his expression and knew that Lu Wei Yin's emotions were surging, he understood why Lu Wei Yin felt so conflicted as well.

Shen Shang did not speak. He had received Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's help in the past, it was not appropriate to speak now.

Shen Cong Sheng had no such issue, immediately urging: "In my opinion, Lord Lu Wei Yin, you do not need to be too conflicted. Back then, you helped Fang Yuan mostly because of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's will."

After pausing for a while, he added: "Furthermore, even though Fang Yuan took Lord Paradise Earth's life, that was merely the final hit. The most important culprits were Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable."

Lu Wei Yin sighed as he looked up, he had no choice but to nod as he said: "You are right."

He smiled bitterly: "The situation has changed, the world is no longer like before. Without Lord Paradise Earth, I, Lu Wei Yin, am merely a wandering vagrant. Even though Mushroomman Paradise is still around, the mushroommen have all entered the sovereign immortal aperture already, they are Fang Yuan's hostages. I am troubled by both choices, I cannot calm down. Shen Shang, we have a deep friendship forged from battles, I wonder what your opinion on this matter is? I would like to hear your view."

Shen Shang coughed before saying: "I will not lie to you, friend, I want to join Lord Heaven Refining Demon Venerable. The truth is, back in the blue dragon whale, we had already worked with Lord Fang Yuan. Afterwards, we collaborated in both the fate war and the battle in Crazed Demon Cave. Through our multiple cooperations, Lord Fang Yuan had not let us down once. Of course, can we say that Fang Yuan is dependable? That is complete nonsense, he is still a Demon Venerable after all. But Shen clan's foundation is here, if we try to move, it will be too risky. After considering the pros and cons, this is the only thing we can do."

Gu Immortals could not cultivate without resources.

Shen clan was huge and had many Gu Immortals, they needed even more resources to maintain the cultivation of all their members, while promoting new Gu Immortal seeds as well.

Of course, each Gu Immortal had their own immortal aperture.

But just the resources inside one's immortal aperture were not enough to be self-sufficient. Otherwise, treasure yellow heaven would not be this popular with everyone.

The sovereign immortal aperture was able to be self-sufficient, but it was unique.

Even though it could be refined again, the amount of immortal materials needed, including the ten extreme physiques, and also the tribulation during the Gu refinement, made the risks and investments too great to bear.

Hearing Shen Shang's words, Lu Wei Yin's expression turned grim as he nodded: "Brother Shen has helped me a lot, since that is your decision, then I will follow you this time."

Shen Cong Sheng and Shen Shang glanced at each other while muttering internally: Sly old fox.

With these words, Lu Wei Yin wanted to use this decision to repay the favor of having Shen Shang heal his injuries.

As expected, a pseudo venerable like Lu Wei Yin was a genius among geniuses, he could not be deceived under most situations.

Shen Shang coughed and said: "It is for the best that you have decided to do this. We can help each other out in the future as well."

Shen Cong Sheng quickly made use of this conversation, suggesting that Shen Shang and Lu Wei Yin should take the lead to get all the other Eastern Sea super forces to join Fang Yuan as well.

Lu Wei Yin predicted that this would happen, he nodded and agreed on the spot.

Shen Cong Sheng brewed his six sound tea again.

After enjoying the tea, Shen Shang brought the satisfied Lu Wei Yin into their secret room again for treatment.

Shen Shang's and Lu Wei Yin's injuries were very severe.

Just one round of treatment was not enough. Even if Shen Shang was using human path methods, to get rid of these venerable dao marks on their wounds, time was needed.

On the morning of the second day, Shen Cong Sheng set off and visited the other super clans.

His plan to rope them in was quite successful.

These super forces were all based in Eastern Sea, they soon heard from Shen Cong Sheng that Shen Shang and Lu Wei Yin were going to join Fang Yuan.

With the death of Demon Immortal Qi Jue in Crazed Demon Cave, there were only three pseudo venerable battle strength experts left in the world.

Among the three of them, Shen Shang and Lu Wei Yin wanted to join Fang Yuan, while Qi Sea Ancestor, the leader of the Righteous Qi Alliance, was Fang Yuan's qi path clone!

This trend was simply too overpowering, the other Eastern Sea super clans soon joined in.

Of course, not everyone wanted to join Fang Yuan.

Xia Xuan, Xia Jia, and the other Gu Immortals had already decided to leave Eastern Sea and betray the Righteous Qi Alliance the moment they heard Longevity Heaven's and Heavenly Court's announcements.

These Xia clan Gu Immortals were truly pitiful.

First, their foundation was devoured by the variant human alliance, they then joined Qi Sea Ancestor to try and reclaim their territory. But the result was that Qi Sea Ancestor and Fang Yuan had played them entirely, killing the important Gu Immortals of Xia clan like Xia Rui Zhi.

"This demon Fang Yuan killed our clansmen and devoured our foundation, this enmity is greater than heaven!"

"Eastern Sea, we will be back one day!"

"Let's go, Zui Xian Weng is going to arrive here soon on patrol."

"Hehe, don't worry, in order to escape today, I specially found some rare wine for Zui Xian Weng. With his nature, he is going to be completely drunk today."

Xia clan's Gu Immortals conversed while secretly flying from Eastern Sea to Central Continent along the surface of the sea.

Zui Xian Weng watched as they left, until they vanished into the horizon.

This elderly Gu Immortal sighed deeply, he had a worried expression.

He had already regretted his promise to Qin Ding Ling. He was now Heavenly Court's spy that had infiltrated the Righteous Qi Alliance.

Heavenly Court had instructed him a day ago to purposely let these Xia clan Gu Immortals go.

"I succeeded this time because it was an easy mission, but next time?"

Zui Xian Weng thought about Fang Yuan, who had venerable cultivation level, all the wine that he had become flavorless.

"How did he suddenly become a venerable out of nowhere?!"

Chapter 2218: Fang Yuan As An Escape Route

A tiny bamboo stick, on which five cicadas were skewered, was placed above the fire grill.

The bamboo stick was unusual, while the fire was also not ordinary, these five cicadas were all rank five fire path Gu worms named purple smoke cicada. Once the infusion of true essence, can emit purple smoke, obscuring a piece of heaven and earth.

If in the mortal world, each purple smoke cicada would cause bloodshed among Gu Masters, but here, they were just food.

The person cooking the cicadas wore a white robe and had thick hair, he was sitting on a folding stool that displayed his tall and thin body.

It was Northern Plains' rank eight Gu Immortal Heavenly Lord Bai Zu!

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu had a hobby that was well known in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world. He loved to cook Gu worms and create these delicious dishes from time to time.

He personally cooked these dishes, other than for himself, he also gave them to his Bai Zu tribe members as a reward. Anyone who received such a reward would feel incredibly honored. This was Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's acknowledgement after all!

At times, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu would also invite his Gu Immortal friends as guests to enjoy his cooking.

At this moment, Chu Du sat in front of Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, he was the single esteemed guest that was invited!

Chu Du continued to chew as the number of purple smoke cicadas on the skewer fell to one.

"Brother Chu, how's the taste?" Heavenly Lord Bai Zu grilled his cicadas while smiling and asking.

Chu Du smiled too: "It has great flavor! To think that after grilling these purple smoke cicadas, they would actually have the flavor of chicken meat but also the sweetness of taro. It is a crunchy snack and one skewer is definitely not enough."

"Hahaha." Heavenly Lord Bai Zu laughed: "Everyone knows that I was a lone cultivator initially. Long ago, when I roamed Northern Plains aimlessly, I barely had enough clothes or food. One time, when I failed to capture a Gu worm, I accidentally crushed it with my foot. Half a month of effort became wasted as a result."

"I could not bear to leave it there! I felt angry and regretful. Thus, I cooked that Gu worm and ate it, the flavor was terrible and I had diarrhea for seven days and night, I almost died as a result."

"After that ordeal, I became more determined and ruthless. I swore that when I made it big, I would frequently eat Gu worms to take revenge."

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu had a drifting gaze.

Chu Du was solemn.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu had never said such words to him, he seemed to have the intention to go into a deeper conversation.

Chu Du knew that this was the result of exposing his rank eight cultivation level, they were on equal levels now.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu laughed again as he steered the topic back: "My grilled cicadas are just a hobby, there is good flavor but no benefits at all. This is not like those super forces with deep foundations, their famous teas and wines are passed down for generations and modified each time. Some of their better creations can even grant dao marks after consumption."

Chu Du nodded as he said analytically: "Ever since the Battle of Yi Tian Mountain and the actions of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, who has incredibly profound food path methods, Heavenly Court, which was his enemy, started to research food path and gained much result. The qi tides that swept the world also caused five or six food path inheritances that I know of to be circulated. These were mostly sold in treasure yellow heaven and were bought by many people, allowing them to benefit greatly. As a result, food path started to spread among people."

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu nodded and sighed: "With the destruction of fate, the unification of five regions, and the reign of three venerables, the chaotic war is about to start. This has never happened in human history. Food path originated from beastmen and was purposely concealed by people even when it was spread. But with the great era now, food path cannot be hidden anymore. I wonder how many food path experts will appear in the future? Food path is becoming like this, strength path will also not stay the same. Brother Chu, I know that you are focused on promoting strength path, that is impossible during normal times, but in this great era, you have a good chance of success."

Chu Du laughed involuntarily, he had fought against Fairy Black Moon earlier and risked injuries to save her, it showed his aspiration to everyone.

Chu Du's eyes glimmered: "Now is still too early. Currently, there are less than five true strength path experts in the five regions. Other than me and Fairy Black Moon, there is only the first supreme elder of Western Desert's Fang clan, who is the most famous one. To revitalize strength path, I need to get more Gu cultivators to choose strength path in their cultivation. I cannot change the environment of the world, but I can create more strength path experts to push this tide along!"

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu finally reached the topic he wanted, he interjected: "Brother Chu, you are forgetting one strength path expert. In his early days, he mostly relied on strength path methods. And now, he is high and mighty, far beyond the realm of us ordinary people."

Chu Du was stunned for a moment before realizing that Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was referring to Gu Yue Fang Yuan.

Chu Du knew what Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's intention was in mentioning Fang Yuan, he cooperated and said solemnly: "Gu Yue Fang Yuan was able to become a venerable, it is truly out of my expectations. Back when I first met him, I felt that this person was not simple, he could not be estimated with common sense."

"Afterwards, I was fortunate to fight together with him several times, I found that this person had a hardy nature, he had both brains and brawn. Anyone with such a nature would not submit to being below others."

"But he had a special identity, he was the single chosen person by heaven's will to rebirth, he also received the investment of many venerables in an attempt to destroy fate. In his life, he had encountered so many dangerous situations and predicaments that even throughout history, nobody could compare to it."

"Finally, he managed to take that final step and become one of the strongest people in the world. After my initial shock and suspicion, I analyzed this and felt that it was a natural thing."

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu listened, he nodded, saying: "You are exactly right."

Next, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu subconsciously quietened his voice as he moved his body forward, saying to Chu Du: "I wonder if Brother Chu has stayed in contact with this Heaven Refining Demon Venerable..."

Chu Du did not answer openly, he asked: "Oh? Brother Bai Zu, you mean to say..."

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu shrugged and raised both palms, smiled bitterly: "In the current situation, Brother Chu, why the need to ask an unnecessary question? We became acquainted from our initial conflict, even though we made our respective tribes, in this Northern Plains, we are ostracized constantly."

"In normal times, we both have rank eight cultivation level, other than Central Continent, as long as we are alive, our forces can stay strong in any other place."

"But now, we are in the unprecedented great era!"

"Giant Sun Immortal Venerable revived, and he has a reputation for being the most caring towards his descendants."

"My Bai Zu tribe was established by devouring Hei tribe's foundation, which is a Huang Jin bloodline tribe."

"To speak the truth, Brother Chu, I have not been able to eat or sleep well recently, I am filled with worries."

Chu Du quickly consoled: "No matter how protective Giant Sun Immortal Venerable is towards his descendants, you still have rank eight cultivation level. Longevity Heaven has been trying to unify the entire Northern Plains Gu Immortal world, if he kills you, he will lose the support of many people. If the current world were ruled by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable alone, we might be in danger. But with three venerables in power now, we have hope of surviving."

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu still had a bitter expression: "However, there are countless ways for the stronger party to deal with us. Brother Chu, ever since our tribes were created, the other Huang Jin tribes have been ostracizing us. Haven't we seen enough of their methods? Giant Sun Immortal Venerable does not need to target us, when the chaos starts, he can just push our tribes to be the cannon fodder, it is a simple thing to get rid of us."

Chu Du heard this and nodded lightly. Heavenly Lord Bai Zu had expressed his inner worry as well.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu wanted to contact Fang Yuan through Chu Du, he was not thinking of joining Fang Yuan immediately.

After all, Fang Yuan had been given the title of Heaven Refining Demon Venerable by Longevity Heaven and Heavenly Court.

Everyone in the world knew about Fang Yuan's nature, ruthlessness and cruelty was a part of it.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu wanted to leave an escape route for himself, so that he could use it when a crisis appeared.

And the truth was, Chu Du had the same idea as him.

"To speak the truth, I have not contacted Fang Yuan for a very long time." Chu Du sighed and said the truth.

Chu Du added: "Everyone knows about my relationship with Fang Yuan. It is too dangerous to contact Fang Yuan now with Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's existence. If I get exposed, disaster would strike."

Even though he said that.

Chu Du had already made up his mind, while the three venerables were resting, he would secretly contact Fang Yuan and try to create a backup plan for his Chu tribe.

The concurrent reign of three venerables shocked the world.

After the shock, most of the forces and Gu Immortals started to think about their own circumstances.

At the same time, Fang clan's first supreme elder, who was known as the most famous strength path expert by Chu Du, was also holding a meeting now.

In the study room.

Fang clan's first supreme elder Fang Gong sat down and said with a tone of lingering fear: "To think that Fang Yuan became a Demon Venerable! Thankfully, our clan did not reject him and made the transaction with him. Otherwise, if we offended him, we could have defended against him back then, but now, we would face his revenge. Our entire clan would get into a crisis of life and death."

At the side, Fang clan's third supreme elder, rank seven Gu Immortal, Fang Hua Sheng said: "The truth is, our Fang clan was deceived by Fang Yuan for so long, but that is nothing big, he is someone who became venerable after all."

Fang Di Chang snorted coldly, showing a look of displeasure.

He had deep grudges with Fang Yuan. Back then, he schemed against Fang Yuan but got killed and captured instead. Even though Fang Yuan released his soul later, that was part of the transaction that allowed him to get a vast amount of soul cores as well as Thieves Den.

Right now, Fang Di Chang had another body, even though he had rank five cultivation level, he was already preparing for his immortal ascension.

Although his cultivation level fell, his status remained unchanged. After all, his adopted son, Fang Yun, was holding up his faction, he was still trusted by the whole of Fang clan.

Even though Fang Di Chang's wisdom path methods were weaker now, he still had his unique perspective.

He smiled coldly and analyzed: "On the surface, Fang Yuan has become a Demon Venerable and the current situation is unprecedented! Something like three venerables coexisting at the same time has never happened, but even among them, there are subtle differences."

"Look, Heavenly Court exposed Giant Sun Immortal Venerable of creating and cultivating blood path, they also claimed that Fang Yuan was Heaven Refining Demon Venerable, they are the most aggressive side."

"Longevity Heaven rebuked Heavenly Court and said that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was cultivating blood path to benefit the world, it was his great benevolence. At the same time, they also called Fang Yuan a Demon Venerable."

"Among the three, only Fang Yuan has not spoken. After the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, he has been recuperating in Eastern Sea. This shows that he is the weakest among the three venerables."

"In the future, the three venerables will have a huge battle, I still have a chance of revenge. Our Western Desert is situated deep in Western Desert, we have a great location. When the five regions go to war, the boundaries of the various regions will be chaotic. We only need to lay low and develop secretly. If the three venerables have a winner among them, we will join that side. If the venerables die, our Fang clan has hope of becoming an overlord of Western Desert."

Fang Gong and Fang Hua Sheng listened to his analysis and could not help but nod slightly.

Chapter 2219: No, I Am Great Love Immortal Venerable!

After that, Fang Di Chang emphasized: "Looking at the five regions, Northern Plains, Central Continent, and Eastern Sea all have a venerable leader, while Southern Border has a righteous path alliance. Only our Western Desert is still divided and disunited."

"One can say that Western Desert is the weakest of the five regions."

"In this situation, we cannot take the lead to cause problems or show our stance."

"If other forces recruit us, we will try to balance ourselves and secretly join them while ensuring that our benefits are the priority. Back then, our Fang clan was attacked because we obtained Divine Emperor City. We cannot commit the same mistake again and become the target of everyone, that is too foolish."

Fang Hua Sheng and Fang Gong nodded again.

Even though Fang Di Chang had lost his cultivation level, he still had his wide-ranging perspective.

Southern Border.

Tian Lan Mountain, Luo clan's headquarters.

In the main hall, most of Luo clan's Gu Immortals were gathered, those that did not come personally also sent their wills instead.

Luo clan's first supreme elder had rank seven cultivation level, he looked around before speaking: "In the era of three reigning venerables, chaos will ensue. What should Luo clan do? If you have any ideas, do say them now."

Luo clan's Gu Immortals looked at each other, soon, one of them spoke.

This person cultivated space path, he was Luo clan's number one general, Luo Ran, who had peak rank seven battle strength, even surpassing the first supreme elder.

Luo Ran spoke: "Everyone, news of the reign of three venerables shocked everyone, after thinking about it, I decided to look at it from another perspective. If I were either of the three venerables, I would first devour Southern Border and Western Desert. After all, weaklings are the easiest targets, it is not good for Eastern Sea, Central Continent, or Northern Plains if the three venerables fight now. The wisest decision is to strengthen myself first and take more territory and resources before fighting the other venerables."

"Our Luo clan is at the northern end of Southern Border, we are closest to Central Continent. If Star Constellation Immortal Venerable wants to interfere in Southern Border, our Luo clan would have to face her first!"

Luo clan's immortals nodded with a cold expression.

Ever since the disappearance of the five regional walls, their pressure had been intensifying daily. They had to search for backup plans and escape routes for Luo clan.

Luo Ran continued to speak: "With the reign of three venerables, unless our Southern Border also has a venerable, even if all the Southern Border Gu Immortals worked together cooperatively, we are not the match of any of these three venerables. As for the other super forces who are deeper inside the region, they might still have the choice of staying out of the war, but our Luo clan is stuck between Southern Border and Central Continent, when conflict starts, we will need to stick to one side."

Once he said that, all of the Luo clan immortals became stirred.

One of them stood up directly and shouted angrily: "Luo Ran, are you saying that our Luo clan should surrender before fighting? Are you going to ignore the righteousness of our clan throughout the generations? We, Luo clan, defend the glory of righteousness, are you going to abandon that?"

Everyone turned to look, the person who said that was Luo Fei.

Next, many Luo clan Gu Immortals added in their comments that sided with Luo Fei.

"When our Luo clan had once prospered, we almost threatened Wu clan's position, how can we act so cowardly?"

"Indeed, venerables are no doubt invincible. But in the current era, with the reign of three venerables, and the possibility that other venerables might revive in the future, the future is certainly uncertain, we cannot give up now."

"In my opinion, none of the three venerables now are worth joining. Heavenly Court has the sect system, if our Luo clan joins them, we need to change our clan system. Giant Sun Immortal Venerable is most protective of his descendants, Bai Zu tribe and Chu tribe are being ostracized by Northern Plains' Huang Jin bloodline. Meanwhile, Heaven Refining Demon Venerable has a lot of enmity with our clan, if we lower our heads to him, I will look down on myself!"

Seeing everyone's anger and riled emotions, Luo Ran quickly waved his hand: "Everyone, I did not consider it through."

Luo Fei stared widely: "Lord Luo Ran, you are the number one expert of Luo clan, if even you have such thoughts, we will be too disappointed!"

Luo Ran had an expression of guilt: "I was wrong."

Luo Fei added: "According to my view, the situation is not very dangerous. With the reign of three venerables, they are wary of each other while being restricted, they will not make a move easily. In the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, Demon Immortal Qi Jue and people like Xiao He Jian have already died, Fang Yuan lost many powerful subordinates. Right now, his main body is recuperating in Eastern Sea without doing anything, he does not have the strength to interfere in other regions."

"Additionally, even though our Southern Border has no venerable, we have the Southern Alliance and the Alliance Leader Wu Yong. During the fate war, Lord Wu Yong led our Southern Border righteous path and did not disappoint us even once! Why can't we hold expectations towards him and ourselves for now?"

After saying these words, Luo Fei sat down.

Many Luo clan Gu Immortals also nodded slightly, agreeing with her words.

Luo clan thought positively about Wu clan.

Because back then, Luo clan suffered a loss when exploring Qi Jue grotto-heaven, they were pursued and had to seek help from Wu clan to preserve their strength.

After some time, Luo Zu announced the end of the meeting, only Luo Ran stayed behind to talk to him secretly.

"Sorry you had to do this." Luo Zu said apologetically.

Luo Ran shook his head: "Joining Heavenly Court was my true intention to begin with. I was just probing them today, but it seems that Luo clan does not want to give up yet, they think that it is too cowardly. On the other hand, that information path Immortal Gu was only the idea of Immortal Crane Sect, even if our Luo clan wants to join Central Continent, we need to contact at least Heavenly Court, right?"

Luo Zu sighed: "Our Luo clan has always been an upright and righteous force, I am too useless to lead everyone, I am worried about Luo clan's safety. But you are right, now is not the time yet, we need to continue contacting Immortal Crane Sect in secret."

Central Continent, Immortal Crane Sect.

Verdant green trees grew as clear winds blew.

In a pavilion near the middle of the mountain, a young Gu Immortal was blowing his flute.

As the sound of the flute spread, an immortal crane fluttered in the sky.

The young looking Gu Immortal wore a clean white robe, his eyebrows were green and long, extending to his waist. It was the enslavement path immortal He Feng Yang, he was known as the Winged Crane Flying Immortal.

"I succeeded in passing my tribulation and became rank seven. But to think that the moment I came out of seclusion, I heard the shocking story of the reign of three venerables."

"Not only did Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable revive, there is even a new Heaven Refining Demon Venerable!"

"Gu Yue Fang Yuan..."

He Feng Yang felt complex emotions.

Back then, he was the one who asked Lord Sky Crane to head to Southern Border's Gu Yue village, he also dealt with Fang Yuan when trying to get Hu Immortal blessed land.

"If I made up my mind back then and took action personally, could I have killed Fang Yuan?"

This thought emerged in He Feng Yang's mind constantly.

But soon, He Feng Yang shook his head. The chances were that he would fail. Because behind Fang Yuan, there was the contest of heaven's will and the other venerables. Also, even if he could have killed Fang Yuan, what was the point of saying it now?

Fang Yuan was already a Demon Venerable.

While He Feng Yang had just gotten past rank six and advanced to rank seven.

He Feng Yang felt dejected internally, but he also had other emotions like envy.

He worked so hard for so many years, but he watched as a mortal like Fang Yuan rose rapidly in strength, eventually becoming a venerable! Fang Yuan had far surpassed him, he could not even see his shadow.

But through this flute music, He Feng Yang slowly calmed down.

"Everyone has their own opportunities."

"Fang Yuan was able to reach this stage, other than fortuitous encounters, he also had wisdom and courage to fight, he saw through many chaotic situations and had often gotten into dangerous situations."

"But I am not without hope. During peaceful times, spending resources on enslavement path is wasteful for the sect. But with the arrival of the five regions chaotic war, as an enslavement path cultivator, the sect will think highly of me, they will give me more attention and resources."

"Furthermore, I acted of my own accord and secretly sent Luo clan an information path Immortal Gu in the name of Immortal Crane Sect to try to recruit them. Since Luo clan's first supreme elder has not destroyed the information path Immortal Gu yet, this shows a clear attitude."

"If this succeeds, it will be a huge accomplishment, I will get a lot of sect contribution points. By then, I can exchange for an immortal pill from Heavenly Court so that Little Nine can become an ancient desolate beast!"

He Feng Yang looked at the nine palace crane in front of him and smiled.

This nine palace crane was a desolate beast with a close relationship with He Feng Yang. Back then, it was hit by a time path Immortal Gu and regressed in age, becoming younger and younger until it became a baby. He Feng Yang tried his best to save it, paying a huge price for it to recover fully.

Eastern Sea.

Five colored smoke rumbled as it contracted, eventually going back into Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture.

Fang Yuan sat cross-legged on the nameless island, he saw a wide area before him without any smoke left.

Next, a large group of Gu Immortals came towards him. When they were a thousand steps away, they landed on the surface of the sea and kowtowed towards him, showing their subservience.

These were Eastern Sea's righteous path Gu Immortals, the various first supreme elders of the respective clans were among them.

Of course, they were led by the pseudo venerables, Shen Shang and Lu Wei Yin.

Fang Yuan was stunned for a split second before understanding the situation, he laughed: "A wise man submits to circumstances, everyone, please get up. From today onwards, I will treat you equally like my other subordinates."

The immortals showed expressions of gratitude as they said together: "We pay respects to Heaven Refining Demon Venerable, we are willing to give our lives to Lord Demon Venerable!"

But Fang Yuan shook his head slowly: "At this point, I should make a declaration to the world."

He connected to treasure yellow heaven and started to make his declaration.

"What, Heaven Refining Demon Venerable? I do not accept this title!"

Shen Shang and the rest were stunned.

"I am not in the demonic path, I am a righteous path member. All my past actions have been to seek blessings for all living beings in the world. I disregarded my own life and experienced countless crises to destroy fate, I granted freedom to everyone in the world! However, corrupt forces like Heavenly Court still try to suppress and slander me even now, they are trying to obstruct me!"

"I was best friends with Lord Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable. In the battle of Crazed Demon Cave, he entrusted me with his wishes before dying, after becoming venerable, I will emulate Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable, I will work for the harmony of the five regions!"

"Everyone, do not believe in rumors, Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable was not killed by me, Star Constellation and Giant Sun cooperated to end his life."

Fang Yuan spoke in a righteous tone.

Shen Shang and Lu Wei Yin stared at him blankly.

The other Eastern Sea righteous path leaders were also listening like this was a dream.

Fang Yuan suddenly raised his volume, he said in an energetic tone: "Everyone, I want you to remember, I, Gu Yue Fang Yuan, am Great Love Immortal Venerable! From today onwards, I will create my Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance, I will bring benefits to the world and peace to the five regions!!"

News soon spread rapidly in treasure yellow heaven, every Gu Immortal in the world heard of it.

Be they Heavenly Lord Bai Zu and Chu Du who were currently grilling food, or the three higher-ups of Fang clan who were discussing secretly, or Luo clan's immortals, or He Feng Yang, they all received this shocking news.

But Fang Yuan did not stop, he continued to speak.

He placed a list in treasure yellow heaven that contained a vast number of Gu worm names. If any Gu Master or Gu Immortal paid the appropriate price, he would refine Gu for them. For mortal Gu, he did not restrict quantity, while in regards to Immortal Gu, he could even refine rank eight Immortal Gu for them!

The five regions went into an uproar.

"This is my promise as Gu Yue Fang Yuan, a refinement path venerable!"

"Gu worms are the core of our cultivation, they are our foundation. But all along, they have been too rare and hard to refine, especially Immortal Gu."

"Because of this, the first thing that I will do to benefit the world is to refine Immortal Gu for everyone. Regardless of our past grudges or enmity, be it friend or foe, I will not mind it, I will refine Gu for everyone equally. This will prove the great love in my heart!"

"I know what you are worried about. But in fact, I have already made many transactions with various forces and Gu Immortals, I refined many Immortal Gu for them."

"For example, I've transacted many times with Western Desert's Fang clan, this is all evidence!"

In Western Desert, Fang Gong, Fang Di Chang, and Fang Hua Sheng stared with wide eyes.

Fang Di Chang, who had earlier emphasized that they should 'keep a low-profile and not cause public outrage' turned pale immediately.

"Or for example, Southern Border's Wu clan. I have refined more than one rank eight Immortal Gu for Wu Yong, the evidence is here!"

Wu Yong:"..."

Luo clan's members: "..."

Luo Fei held her head and felt like her heart had broken: "Why? Lord Wu Yong, you actually cooperated with Fang Yuan secretly... why?!"

"Or for example, Northern Plains' Bai Zu tribe, I have many possible areas of cooperation with Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, we have been in close contact." Fang Yuan continued to announce.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was like a stone statue, the skewer in his hand that he was roasting went up in flames.

Chu Du looked at him, seemingly saying: Brother, what is wrong with you? Since you have been in contact with Fang Yuan all along, why did you want to use my connection with him?

Fang Yuan continued to say: "Not just Northern Plains, Central Continent is involved too. For example, Immortal Crane Sect's He Feng Yang, I have been in contact with him since my younger days, we have truly become acquainted as a result of past conflicts."

"Slander, this is pure slander!!" He Feng Yang smashed the jade flute in his hand, he shivered intensely.

Finally, Fang Yuan said: "Whether you believe me or not, that is up to you. Risks exist all the time, but what if this is true? Why don't you try first?"

"Everyone, please give me some of your trust!"

"Since long ago, countless people have misunderstood me. Thus, allow me to prove now to the people over the world that I am truly Great Love Immortal Venerable!!"

After Fang Yuan's declaration.

Winds blew on the surface of the sea.

The kneeling Eastern Sea Gu Immortals raised their heads and looked towards Fang Yuan in a daze.

Looking at them, Fang Yuan showed a kind and sincere smile: "Everyone, please get up. You have already joined my Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance, you will receive greater preferential treatment as the first batch."

"I guarantee you that."

Chapter 2220: Blending of Black and White

Li Xiao Bai followed several information path Gu Immortals, they carefully waited in ambush.

"Xiao Bai, black and white heaven are fusing together now, the commotion is huge and the environment is dangerous. Later, when the hound groups fly over, you should focus on watching rather than taking action, do you understand?" A rank seven information path Gu Immortal instructed.

Li Xiao Bai quickly nodded: "Yes, I will listen to the seniors."

He was acting obediently, without the arrogance of a great scholar, all the information path Gu Immortals here had a good impression of him.

Li Xiao Bai had become a rank six long ago, he was an information path Gu Immortal. Because of his talent, he was also the most favored Gu Immortal junior in Profound Literature grotto-heaven.

These information path Gu Immortals came from Profound Literature grotto-heaven, they were at least second-grade officials in the grotto-heaven's Imperial Court.

Profound Literature grotto-heaven had a special system, Gu Immortals entered the Imperial Court and most of them held important positions and roles. After Li Xiao Bai became a Gu Immortal, he also started to work for the Imperial Court.

The only exception was Old Immortal Hua Yu.

He had rank eight cultivation level and stayed in the background, controlling the entire situation.

"They're here." After a while, the Gu Immortal in charge of investigation spoke.

The immortals quickly displayed several killer moves, they concealed themselves even more deeply.

Soon, Li Xiao Bai saw a group of remnant heavenly dogs running towards them while stepping on air.

These were all space path ancient desolate beasts, they ate space path Gu worms as food.

"A total of three hundred and sixty-eight remnant heavenly dogs, and four heaven swallowing hounds." Li Xiao Bai cultivated information path, he was most skilled at collecting information, after taking a glance at them, he noticed the size of this hound group.

Remnant heavenly dogs were ancient desolate beasts, after they grew to an extent, they would become heaven swallowing hounds.

Heaven swallowing hounds were immemorial desolate beasts that ate nine heavens fragments, grotto-heaven, and blessed lands as food. They had always been a huge threat to the two heavens' grotto-heavens.

As the dog group continued to approach, Profound Literature grotto-heaven's Gu Immortals started to work together, they secretly used a killer move.

This killer move had no commotion or sound, it spread out rapidly.

Initially, the dog group had no change, but after more than ten breaths of time, three heaven swallowing hounds stopped and bared their fangs, looking in the same direction with expressions of vigilance.

The final heaven swallowing hound also slowed down.

The four heaven swallowing hounds barked at the same place for a while, afterwards, three of the heaven swallowing hounds brought most of the remnant heavenly dogs to move on another route, towards a different direction.

The final heaven swallowing hound brought more than twenty remnant heavenly dogs as they continued on their original path.

The Gu Immortals of Profound Literature grotto-heaven had been hiding all along, after the dog group left their field of vision, they showed themselves and sighed in relief.

"Alright, it has been settled."

"Most of the hounds have been misled by us, they think that direction has sumptuous food, but there are soul beasts there instead."

"Haha, we have also used information path methods on those soul beasts, once the dog group goes there, they will think that the soul beasts are hiding an immortal aperture. They will kill each other without us taking action."

"The remaining heaven swallowing hound was not tricked by us, it likely has the protection of an Immortal Gu. But with this number that we lured over, Lord Hua Yu has enough to work with."

"Xiao Bai, did you see clearly? When your cultivation level rises to rank seven in the future, you need to complete such missions often as well. Our Profound Literature grotto-heaven cannot move and is placed in one spot in the sky, but we need to resolve lots of problems before they even occur."

Li Xiao Bai immediately answered: "I will work harder!"

These Gu Immortals immediately moved along the direction that the heaven swallowing hound went earlier.

This heaven swallowing hound brought a few remnant heavenly dogs with it, getting ambushed midway by the battlefield killer move that Old Immortal Hua Yu set up in advance.

After a large battle, the heaven swallowing hound died. There was a wild Immortal Gu after all, but it was destroyed in the battle.

There were some remaining remnant heavenly dogs that managed to survive, they escaped along the cracks of the battlefield killer move.

They were space path beasts after all, running away was their expertise.

But afterwards, they met with Li Xiao Bai's group.

After a few rounds of killer moves, these remnant heavenly dogs became minced corpses. Li Xiao Bai also took action, he used some immortal essence but did not play a big role.

However, he showed an expression of excitement and lingering enthusiasm, the other information path Gu Immortals looked at him and had a deeper impression of him being a cute young junior.

Old Immortal Hua Yu collected and stored the battlefield killer move as the immortals quickly greeted him.

Old Immortal Hua Yu nodded and looked at everyone, when he saw Li Xiao Bai, he smiled at the latter.

He liked this young junior a lot and appreciated his talent.

In his heart, Li Xiao Bai had a good upbringing and was the most talented Gu Immortal in the last hundred years of Profound Literature grotto-heaven's history, he was the future of the grotto-heaven.

"Sigh! To think that Qi Sea Ancestor is actually a clone of Heaven Refining Demon Venerable!"

"Fang Yuan is scheming and crafty, I was deceived by him completely. If not for Heavenly Court and Longevity Heaven exposing the truth, I would continue to be used by him."

"What Great Love Immortal Venerable, such words can only deceive idiots."

"Sigh, I cannot trust any outsider. Only these Gu Immortals in front of me are trustworthy."

Qi Sea Ancestor had once personally helped Profound Literature grotto-heaven.

Thus, Old Immortal Hua Yu respected Qi Sea Ancestor greatly. After joining the Righteous Qi Alliance, he had been following Qi Sea Ancestor's leadership enthusiastically.

But now that Qi Sea Ancestor's identity was exposed, all of that respect towards him turned into rage and humiliation!

Old Immortal Hua Yu had surging emotions, but he kept calm on the surface and controlled the situation. While ordering the Gu Immortals to clean up the battlefield of all traces, he also sent them to search the area.

They were all information path Gu Immortals, they soon cleared the battlefield of all noticeable traces or clues.

Other than that, the investigative Gu Immortals also brought back some information —

"The heavenly wind qi wall of the immemorial two heavens has mostly dissipated, the fusion of the two heavens will get more severe as time passes. Not only are the two heavens' beasts fighting more frequently, the dao marks of the two heavens are also undergoing huge changes. Some are conflicting with each other while others are fusing together and creating greater effects, they cannot be separated."

In fact, the heavenly wind qi wall had started dissipating long ago. Now that the five regional walls were gone and qi tides swept the world, the two heavens' fusion also reached the most intense moment.

This resulted in the intense commotion.

All the grotto-heavens that were in the two heavens were facing problems continuously throughout the period.

Earlier, the dog group was a huge threat to Profound Literature grotto-heaven so it was dealt with in advance.

But what worried Old Immortal Hua Yu and the other information path Gu Immortals was not just the trouble ahead of them, but also the bigger situation of the five regions and two heavens.

After Fang Yuan returned, he publicly announced himself as Great Love Immortal Venerable and set up his Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance.

Immediately, the two pseudo venerables, Lu Wei Yin and Shen Shang, brought the various super clans of Eastern Sea's righteous path and submitted to Fang Yuan.

Thus, the Righteous Qi Alliance and the variant human alliance jointly entered the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance.

Old Immortal Hua Yu and the others ended up in an awkward position.

Speaking of which, they were members of the Righteous Qi Alliance, as were Granny Skeleton and others. But all along, because their foundation was in the two heavens, they were vaguely ostracized by Eastern Sea's super forces.

But that was nothing originally.

Old Immortal Hua Yu, Granny Skeleton, and the rest only needed to continue getting Qi Sea Ancestor's support.

But now, with the exposure of Qi Sea Ancestor's identity as their greatest enemy, Fang Yuan's clone, they had all along been trying to gain Fang Yuan's favor!

Old Immortal Hua Yu and Granny Skeleton could not help but feel stunned.

Concurrently, the changes in the two heavens made them busy and tired as well.

Right at this time, Fang Yuan announced himself as Great Love Immortal Venerable and made a declaration that shook the world, the five regions' Gu Immortal world went into an uproar.

Ever since Gu Yue Fang Yuan started cultivating, he had been ruthless and slaughtered countless innocents, he was clearly a demonic path member, how could he change his identity so easily with just some words?

If changing one's faction was so easy to achieve, what was the point of the righteous path?

Old Immortal Hua Yu scoffed in his heart but he was clear of the truth.

Fang Yuan's declaration was a joke. But with his strength as a Demon Venerable, who would dare to laugh?

Look at those Eastern Sea righteous path forces who submitted at the first second!

Even if Longevity Heaven and Heavenly Court made fun of his words, what could they do to Fang Yuan?

"I cannot drag this on anymore."

"Fang Yuan has already taken in Eastern Sea's righteous path, our two heavens' forces cannot watch anymore."

"But should we join Fang Yuan, Heavenly Court, or Longevity Heaven?"

Profound Literature grotto-heaven was not in the heaven of Central Continent or Northern Plains, this was the reason why Old Immortal Hua Yu joined the Righteous Qi Alliance earlier.

Now, joining Fang Yuan was the most convenient outcome.

Yet, they would not be able to preserve Profound Literature grotto-heaven.

Why?

Everyone knew that Fang Yuan had the sovereign immortal aperture, the two heavens' grotto-heavens were his targets to annex.

Since they could not keep their homeland anyway, what was the point of joining Fang Yuan?

And honestly speaking, Old Immortal Hua Yu really hated demons like Fang Yuan.

Old Immortal Hua Yu started to think more broadly, there were many options in front of him.

But which choice should he pick? It was a tough question!

Longevity Heaven.

At the most central area, there was Calamity Luck Altar.

The four directions of Calamity Luck Altar had the Four Desolations.

And around the Four Desolations, there were eight areas for the Eight Extremities.

Above the Four Desolations was golden light that radiated and enveloped the place. Above the Eight Extremities was a spreading aura of green light.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had already returned to Longevity Heaven for some time already.

Whoosh.

A soft sound echoed.

The final few star path dao marks on Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's body went ablaze, they vanished completely.

"My injuries are finally healed." Giant Sun Immortal Venerable let out a breath of air: "Next, I need to refine the luck path dao marks of the five regions and two heavens to regain my strength as a Dao Lord!"

In the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not use genuine venerable level strength in combat.

Because they were in the void, there were no natural dao marks for them to refine.

If there were, every action of a venerable would be amplified and strengthened by the natural dao marks, they would become very terrifying.

This was like how Spectral Soul Demon Venerable had the amplification of countless soul path dao marks in the Door of Life and Death.

But strictly speaking, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was not considered a true Dao Lord, because he did not have his sanity.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had already refined all of the luck path dao marks in the world back in his time. But after his death, these dao marks went back to the control of the Heavenly Dao.

Thus, he had to refine them again before he could use them.

Chapter 2221: Fang Yuan's Principles

Longevity Heaven's luck path dao marks were originally from Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's immortal aperture, because it did not devour any nine heavens fragment, heaven's will had not taken over it.

As long as he fought in Longevity Heaven, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's strength would be even greater than Spectral Soul Demon Venerable in Crazed Demon Cave!

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's own luck path dao marks could not match Spectral Soul Demon Venerable in number. But with the colossal number of dao marks in Longevity Heaven, he surpassed Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's main body.

And most importantly, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was sane and clear-minded!

"It is a pity that I cannot fuse this original immortal aperture into my current body." Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not lack methods to move an immortal aperture.

Once he fused with Longevity Heaven, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's strength would surge immensely. His luck path dao marks would greatly surpass and suppress Fang Yuan. By then, he could travel the five regions and two heavens without any worries!

After all, Longevity Heaven was Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's peak cultivation creation, it was Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's foundation after passing three chaotic disasters.

Meanwhile, Fang Yuan had only passed one Heavenly Dao blockade, he had survived the chaos tribulation in Crazed Demon Cave, it could only be considered a small chaotic disaster.

But right now, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had a reason why he could not absorb Longevity Heaven.

Because he cultivated blood path now.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable wanted to use blood path as his main path and luck path as his specialty, his plan was to cultivate both paths.

Since he had planned this for so long already, he naturally had a superb blood-luck dual cultivation method. But he did not have the sovereign immortal body, no matter what he did, conflicts of dao marks still existed.

Right now, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had only started cultivating blood path officially for a short time, he had many luck path dao marks but few blood path dao marks, this difference was already the limit. If he fused with Longevity Heaven now, he would gain a surge of luck path dao marks that would suppress blood path entirely, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's dual cultivation plan would fail.

"Although I cannot regain Longevity Heaven now, in terms of refining natural dao marks, I have the biggest advantage, that is my immortal essence!"

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had the largest immortal essence storage of the three venerables! Currently, he had a thousand yellow apricot immortal essence beads.

Most of it was left behind in Longevity Heaven during his first life.

He had an even larger quantity stored back then, but there was continuous expenditure as time passed, because Longevity Heaven could not produce any more immortal essence after Giant Sun's demise, eventually, only less than ten percent of his immortal essence was left.

"But this quantity is definitely the highest among everyone!" Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was confident about this.

Because he knew that Heaven Refining Demon Venerable Fang Yuan had just advanced, his rank nine immortal essence storage was zero. As for rank eight immortal essence, he definitely had some but it was a small quantity as well.

It was obvious.

Ever since Fang Yuan's rebirth, his cultivation level had risen rapidly, he had almost participated in all the major fights. He also refined so many Immortal Gu and made various Immortal Gu Houses, with such an investment, how could he have a lot of immortal essence left?

And the thing that made Giant Sun Immortal Venerable most glad was that Fang Yuan got hit by his luck path killer move in Crazed Demon Cave — Fortune and Disaster Coexists.

Even though Fang Yuan made use of this killer move to end up deceiving him, it was undeniable that the sovereign immortal aperture suffered huge losses in the end. Together with the small chaotic disaster, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable estimated that the sovereign immortal aperture was definitely in a pitiful state right now!

This was Fang Yuan's situation, but Star Constellation Immortal Venerable also could not have more immortal essence than Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

The reason?

The reason was quite simple.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's era was too long ago. Even if she left behind a large quantity of immortal essence, Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals would have expended them over the years.

In fact, three Demon Venerables, Limitless Demon Venerable, Reckless Savage Demon Venerable, and Red Lotus Demon Venerable, invaded Heavenly Court after Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's era.

When Heavenly Court resisted the three Demon Venerables, could they have avoided the use of venerable methods which expended the immortal essence left by the venerable?

"Regrettably, the two heavens are fusing and the heaven path dao marks are gathering with the change of environment, I had no choice but to retrieve Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace. Otherwise, my advantage would be even greater."

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had no choice but to move Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace back.

WIth Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace in immemorial black heaven, it could continue to arrange luck path dao marks and participate in the operations of heaven and earth, as well as the luck of living beings. It could allow the black heaven above Northern Plains to become Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's territory that he could manipulate.

Back then, in the Reverse Flow River battle, Heavenly Court organized a group to head to Northern Plains, but they suffered a loss in immemorial black heaven. It was mostly the effect of Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace.

Now, with the fusion of the two immemorial heavens, the luck path dao marks that Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace arranged in the past were affected by the change, they became chaotic and broken. If he forcefully protected these luck path dao marks and resisted the changes of the Heavenly Dao, the whole of Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace would be affected and face destruction.

These days, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had been healing himself while observing the situation, he had a rather clear understanding of it now.

In the five regions and two heavens, no matter how the environment changed, the battle between the venerables was the only thing that mattered.

For Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, be it Star Constellation Immortal Venerable or Heaven Refining Demon Venerable, they were both unprecedented enemies. In the short term, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable could not find a way to exterminate these two enemies, he could only try to weaken them while maintaining his advantage.

The abundance of immortal essence was Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's advantage.

"If I use this advantage well, I will be able to refine the luck path dao marks of the world first. On this basis, if I fight against either of the two venerables, I will be able to gain the upper hand!"

"Once I gain the upper hand, I will have to heavily cripple Heavenly Court or Fang Yuan. If I can't do that, a lot of trouble will ensue."

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable felt a sense of urgency internally.

If he missed the opportunity of using this early period of advantage, as time passed, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would plot and scheme deeper as a wisdom path expert, she would get harder to deal with.

There was another point, they had to guard against Star Constellation Immortal Venerable secretly reviving the other Immortal Venerables of Heavenly Court!

This was the same for Fang Yuan too.

Right now, his immortal essence storage was at its lowest, once it started to rise, with his refinement path ability, he would refine Immortal Gu on a large scale, his strength would rise greatly, far beyond now.

"Refinement path venerable..." Thinking of Fang Yuan's declaration as Great Love earlier, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable could not help but frown slightly.

He could already predict that Fang Yuan's strength would cause a huge impact on the Gu Immortal world.

This strength was so colossal and unprecedented that even Giant Sun Immortal Venerable could not tell what the future would become because of Fang Yuan's actions.

After all, there had never been a refinement path venerable in history.

Refinement path was different from the other paths.

Gu cultivation had three major aspects, nurture, use, and refinement. Refinement path was one of these three aspects, this was a special trait that no other path had!

Heavenly Court.

"Cough, cough, cough." In a tightly shut secret room, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable coughed out several mouthfuls of blood.

The injuries from the battle in Crazed Demon Cave had not recovered yet.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable cultivated wisdom path and star path, she was not as skilled as Giant Sun Immortal Venerable in terms of healing, who cultivated blood path.

Gu Immortal injuries were usually very troublesome.

Venerables were no exception to this.

Heavenly Court did not lack outstanding healing methods, but for the case of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, very few were suitable.

Because she had too many wisdom path and star path dao marks, healing methods of all other paths were barely usable. Human path was an exception but in the whole of Heavenly Court, there were no human path pseudo venerable experts. This was the lowest requirement to heal a venerable's injuries.

Thus, other than healing herself, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had no other methods.

"I still have six hundred and seventy-one yellow apricot immortal essence beads." Star Constellation Immortal Venerable frowned: "I did not have many to begin with, some were consumed during the battle in Crazed Demon Cave as well. I still have injuries on me, if I continue healing myself, yellow apricot immortal essence beads would be rapidly expended again. After that, I still need to refine Heavenly Court's dao marks and the natural wisdom path dao marks of the world..."

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable calculated precisely.

She had sufficient immortal essence for now, but wisdom path experts calculated ten steps in advance, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was definitely deducing more than that.

The immortal essence storage was not enough for her to refine the wisdom path dao marks of the outside world.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's situation was different from Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

There were a large number of wisdom path dao marks in Heavenly Court, but they did not belong to Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Because Heavenly Court had annexed nine heavens fragments, even though Star Constellation Immortal Venerable contributed her own immortal aperture to this place, her original dao marks had all been assimilated and taken over by heaven's will.

Of course, during the process of refining dao marks in the outside world, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's current immortal aperture would still produce rank nine immortal essence continuously.

But Star Constellation Immortal Venerable felt that this was an extremely dangerous situation! Giant Sun Immortal Venerable or Heaven Refining Demon Venerable might attack at any time!

Thus, the more immortal essence she had in her storage, the better.

"Giant Sun Immortal Venerable must have more immortal essence than me. As for Heaven Refining Demon Venerable, he is the weakest among us in this aspect."

"But he cannot be underestimated! This man is... very special."

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable thought of this as she revealed a complex expression.

Fang Yuan's earlier declaration of being Great Love Immortal Venerable shook the entire world.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was wary of Fang Yuan's refinement path ability, while Star Constellation Immortal Venerable focused on his nature.

In the history of the ten venerables, Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable was noble and grand, Limitless Demon Venerable was a crazed Dao pursuer, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable enjoyed slaughter, Reckless Savage Demon Venerable was wild, Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable was indifferent, while Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable was obsessed...

But no matter what, each of these venerables had their own pride and arrogance in some way.

But Heaven Refining Demon Venerable Fang Yuan?

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable squinted her eyes, she had never seen a venerable with such a nature. He simply did not know the limit of what the word 'shameless' was, he did not care about his 'face', he distorted truth and lies, even lying with a calm expression and deceiving with a righteous tone.

What Great Love Immortal Venerable?!

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was certain that this title was part of Fang Yuan's current plan, it was a method to achieve his current goals. If it was said that anyone in the world could go from demonic to righteous, Fang Yuan was the least likely one among them all.

If he felt the need to make a move, he would do it regardless of how many innocent lives would be sacrificed.

By then, the declaration of Great Love Immortal Venerable and all related promises would be completely forgotten by him like a baseless fart.

But if he felt that going back to the righteous path had benefits to be gained, he would make another similar declaration with no shame in his heart.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had finally understood Fang Yuan clearly now.

"If I have to say that this person has a principle, then his principle is to have no bottom line."

"And if I say this person has a bottom line, then his bottom line is to have no principle!"

This was simply a thoroughly shameless person.

When Star Constellation Immortal Venerable felt a headache regarding him, this shameless fellow had already become venerable.

And the thing that made it hard for Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was that this shameless venerable had an incredibly deep understanding of the human heart, to the extent where he could predict their every thought.

His actions were bound to create a huge wave in the Gu Immortal world before gathering countless people to his side!

The temptation of Immortal Gu was too great!

Even if they could not trust him now, some risk-taking Gu Immortals would still try their luck.

Once Fang Yuan displayed sufficient sincerity, the entire five regions' Gu Immortal world would fall into his palm.

"Even Heavenly Court will not be spared from this..." Star Constellation Immortal Venerable smiled bitterly.

Chapter 2222: Fang Yuan's First Public Deal

Western Desert.

The silent desert suddenly exploded as sand flew in the air, a huge mountain-like beast appeared from underground.

This beast had the shape of a python, it had a crocodile head and six sharp eagle-like claws.

Dragon crocodile!

An immemorial dragon crocodile.

The dragon crocodile roared, the sound waves spread widely, but there was a trace of fear and panic in its voice.

The dragon crocodile had the ability to climb clouds and soar to the sky, after leaving the desert, it flew straight up.

But midway, the dragon crocodile's body shook suddenly as it spewed out a torrent of flames from its huge mouth.

The dragon crocodile growled in pain as it fell to the ground, creating a huge sand wave as a result.

After it struggled for a while, it gradually quietened down and stopped moving entirely.

After a while, three Gu Immortals came out of its mouth.

Two males and one female.

They were from three super forces of Western Desert respectively, being Shi Kang, Zuo Qiu Yan Ming, and Tuoba Feng Yan.

Shi Kang cultivated earth path while the other two cultivated fire path.

It was a fact that the most common cultivation path among Western Desert's Gu Immortals was fire path.

"The final dragon crocodile is dead."

"According to our three clans' agreement, this dragon crocodile belongs to Sister Yan Ming."

The only female here, Zuo Qiu Yan Ming, nodded as she opened her immortal aperture's entrance, placing this immemorial dragon crocodile into it.

She observed within her immortal aperture and showed a smile on her face: "This immemorial dragon crocodile's corpse is good, many dao marks are preserved. It was all thanks to Brother Feng Yan's plan that we killed it like this."

"I'm flattered." Tuoba Feng Yan smiled: "If not for Brother Shi Kang's method, we would not have been able to enter the dragon crocodile's stomach and take this risk. The biggest credit goes to Brother Shi Kang."

"I'm flattered as well, this is our mutual effort." Shi Kang smiled as he replied modestly.

Dragon crocodiles lived in immemorial black heaven, but recently with the fusion of both heavens, their living habitat was badly affected, after a dragon crocodile group lost in a territorial fight, they had to escape from immemorial black heaven.

They wandered along a route, passing Zuo Qiu, Tuoba, and Shi clans territories.

These three clans negotiated and each sent a rank seven Gu Immortal expert to get rid of these dragon crocodiles that were in poor condition already.

Shi Kang, Zuo Qiu Yan Ming, and Tuoba Feng Yan worked together, spending three days and nights to wipe out this dragon crocodile group.

But right when they were about to return to their own clans, they received orders from their clans simultaneously.

"Oh? Wan clan wants to gather the clans and attack Fang clan together?"

"Hehe, so the first one that acts is Wan clan after all."

"Now it seems, because us three are the closest to Wan clan's territory, they sent us this order together."

The three immortals discussed for a while before deciding to travel together.

"Even though this is not far from Wan clan, we still need to rest and reorganize ourselves."

"Indeed, we need to treat our injuries first."

"The dragon crocodile corpses in the immortal apertures have to be dealt with too."

Shi Kang thought about it before smiling: "On this journey to Wan clan, we will pass by myriad ore desert. That resource point is guarded by my clan's Shi Zhong, we can go there and rest."

For resting, the environment of the wilderness was definitely worse than a resource point.

Every resource point had an immortal formation, it was safer too.

Zuo Qiu Yan Ming and Tuoba Feng Yan looked at each other before turning to Shi Kang and nodding, the latter said: "Then we will trouble you this time."

Shi Kang laughed heartily: "Gladly!"

Myriad ore desert was relatively flat and the surrounding view extended to the horizon, the ground was a cracked rocky terrain with no vegetation growing.

But below the desert, there was a different world all together, a large amount of ores were gathered here, a hundred thousand rockmen were living here as miners, excavating all sorts of materials for Gu Immortals.

But these rockmen were all mortals, they were Gu Masters at best. With limited strength, they could only excavate mortal ores.

Thus, Shi clan sent a Gu Immortal to guard this place while simultaneously excavating immortal ores.

This was a tough mission, normally speaking, a Gu Immortal sent here was someone who got ostracized by the clan.

Shi Zhong was such an example.

Shi Zhong's father betrayed the clan and caused huge losses to them, not just in resources but also Gu Immortals' lives.

In order to gain trust, Shi Zhong changed his name to Shi Zhong[1] to express his loyalty to the clan. But that did not change anything.

At this moment, Shi Zhong's divine sense was moving about in treasure yellow heaven.

In treasure yellow heaven, the most eye-catching thing now was that huge piece of Primordial Domain!

"This is the legendary secluded domain of heaven and earth! In the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable sold this to Heaven Refining Demon Venerable Fang Yuan. If I can get a piece, how good would that be?"

Shi Zhong felt incredibly envious.

The reason why he knew about the origin of this Primordial Domain was because Fang Yuan had spread the news.

The idea was simple, he wanted the world to know that even Giant Sun Immortal Venerable made a transaction with him, what was there to fear?

Of course, now that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was exposed as the creator of blood path and had also started cultivating it, he was labeled as a Demon Venerable by Heavenly Court.

Above the Primordial Domain, there was a will.

This will had a human-shaped form, he wore a white robe and had black hair, his facial features were peerless, it was Fang Yuan's will.

"Heaven Refining Demon Venerable..."

"If I ask him to refine Gu, will I be able to obtain wealth Gu?"

"No, that is too risky."

"Wealth Gu is my hope of rising up, how can I give the Gu recipe to Fang Yuan. If he succeeds in the refinement but does not give the Gu to me, I will be making a stupid mistake. There is nothing I can do to a venerable!"

This thought only flashed in Shi Zhong's mind for a second.

Shi Zhong had obtained an incomplete Immortal Gu recipe of wealth Gu in his early days.

Wealth Gu was a legendary Immortal Gu, if Shi Zhong could refine it, he would soon become incredibly wealthy and accumulate lots of cultivation resources, breaking free from the clan's restraints.

In order to refine wealth Gu, Shi Zhong had secretly used humans to refine Gu. If such a demonic act was exposed, he would be in huge trouble.

Even though he took such a huge risk, he had tried to refine it for over a hundred times but all his attempts ended in failure. He was still far from success.

Shi Zhong had naturally heard Fang Yuan's declaration, but he did not dare to risk it.

Wealth Gu was all the hope he had!

"Oh? Gu Immortals are getting closer." Right at this time, the immortal formation suddenly alerted.

Shi Zhong's expression changed, he immediately went out of treasure yellow heaven and controlled the immortal formation.

At this time, Shi Kang was leading the other two immortals as they stayed in the sky, at the edge of the formation, without entering deeply as they waited.

After Shi Zhong contacted them and verified their identity, he learned of their intention.

"I am so glad that Brother Shi Kang came here. Please, everyone, come in!" Shi Zhong showed sufficient enthusiasm.

The three immortals entered the immortal formation and rested for a while, Shi Zhong held a small banquet and invited them to join.

He even specially gave the main seat to Shi Kang.

After Shi Kang rejected it a few times, he sat down on the main seat.

As the other two immortals saw this situation, they thought of a rumor and understood why.

Compared to Shi Zhong, Shi Kang was a popular person in Shi clan. Not long ago, he had defeated everyone else and obtained Sand Heap blessed land.

On this trip, after killing the dragon crocodiles, Shi Kang did not need to hand them over to the clan, he sold many of them in treasure yellow heaven directly.

Seeing such a treatment, Zuo Qiu Yan Ming and Tuoba Feng Yan felt very envious.

"This time, Wan clan is leading everyone and gathering Wan clan's forces to attack Fang clan, what do both of you think?" After some drinking, Shi Kang asked.

Zuo Qiu Yan Ming said: "Wan clan and Fang clan have deep grudges, it is not strange that they are leading this. Since they are using a proper reason, there is no issue with their action. But I think that Wan clan's decision now will cause problems in the future."

"That's right, I hold the same view." Tuoba Feng Yan put down his glass: "Firstly, with the disappearance of the five regional walls, Western Desert has several clans by the borders of the regions, it is difficult to get them to make a bold move."

"Secondly, Fang clan is not weak, their first supreme elder has rank eight cultivation level and they most excel in Immortal Gu Houses!"

"Thirdly, Fang clan has a good relationship with many clans. During the fate war, they had led everyone in the fight, causing their reputation to rise greatly!"

"And fourthly, which is the most important reason. The reason why we are targeting Fang clan is because of their trading with Fang Yuan, but this is also our fear. Who knows what their exact relationship with Fang Yuan is?"

Shi Kang nodded continuously, sighing: "Brother Tuoba's analysis is sound and clear, I agree completely."

Shi Zhong did not speak, he was in deep thought.

Tuoba Feng Yan's analysis was simple and Shi Kang knew it as well, but he had to ask this.

Because Shi Kang represented Shi clan, he had to talk with Zuo Qiu Yan Ming and Tuoba Feng Yan to see what their clan's intentions were as well.

Now that he knew their views were aligned with Shi clan, Shi Kang felt more relaxed.

"Come, drink wine, drink wine." Shi Kang raised his cup and smiled warmly.

After the meal, the three immortals thanked Shi Zhong before setting off for Wan clan.

Shi Zhong stored away the cups, he had a heavy mood.

Shi Kang's treatment by the clan was too good, it was simply the opposite of him.

Earlier, when Shi Kang was in closed cultivation, the clan provided him all the resources he needed. After Shi Kang took Sand Heap blessed land, the clan rewarded him immediately! The dragon crocodiles he killed were all kept as his property, it was a lucrative job. As for the journey to Wan clan, there were no risks and the outcome was basically decided, he would be welcomed by Wan clan. Instead of a mission, it was like a reward.

"Sigh, my hope still lies in wealth Gu. When can I refine this Gu successfully."

"Heaven Refining Demon Venerable... no, I will not ask for anyone's help. The risk is too big."

Even though Shi Zhong set such a determined goal, after a hundred failures in refining the Gu, he had already started to feel dejected.

His intuition vaguely told him that with his strength alone, the chance of refining wealth Gu was slim!

Thus, unknowingly, he entered yellow heaven again with his divine sense.

Within treasure yellow heaven, Fang Yuan's will suddenly opened his eyes as he spoke in a grand tone: "This rank seven movement Immortal Gu, capture wind Gu, has been refined as per the request of Southern Border's Wu Yong, we will make the transaction now."

"What?" Shi Zhong was shocked.

At this moment, every Gu Immortal who was inside treasure yellow heaven gasped.

Under everyone's gaze, Wu Yong's will got close to Fang Yuan's will, the latter tossed rank seven capture wind Gu to Wu Yong's will.

Wu Yong's will nodded and said nothing, he left treasure yellow heaven with the new Immortal Gu.

"Someone actually made a transaction with Fang Yuan! And it is actually Southern Border's Wu Yong." Shi Zhong had a dazed expression.

[1] Zhong means loyalty Back

Chapter 2223: Fang Yuan's Protection

Southern Border.

Wu Yi Mountain.

Wu clan's blessed land headquarters.

Wu clan's Gu Immortals were gathered, Wu Yong sat at the main seat. Most of the Gu Immortals here were present, only a few individuals had no way of coming and sent their wills instead.

"These last days, we have received letters from Ba clan, Tie clan, Luo clan, Hou clan, and the others. Take a look at them." Wu Yong waved his hand, more than ten information path Gu worms flew out.

As Wu clan's Gu Immortals looked through them, their expressions turned grim and dark.

The contents of these information path Gu worms, to put it mildly, were empty of value. They were merely using a righteous tone to condemn and question Wu Yong as to why he would make a deal with a demon like Fang Yuan! Some of them even threatened to withdraw from the Southern Alliance, arguing that Wu Yong was not qualified to take up the role of the alliance leader, they demanded that the alliance leader should be replaced by a more capable person.

"These fellows..."

"Hmph, they are shameless!"

"I can't stand this, there are many super clans involved here, most of them have once worked together with Lu Wei Yin right? Back then, Lu Wei Yin and Fang Yuan cooperated to kill Spectral Soul and escaped from Heavenly Court's pursuit. Now, they have the nerve to come and reprimand us?"

"They want to change the alliance leader? Hehe, in the whole of Southern Border's Gu Immortal world, is there anyone more suitable than Lord Wu Yong?!"

Wu clan's Gu Immortals discussed among themselves, speaking in an angry tone.

Wu Yong did not speak, he drank tea calmly as he listened to the immortals' conversations.

The immortals got louder and more riled up, their tone became agitated and they wanted to exact revenge on those clans.

Wu Yong put down his cup at this point, raising his hand slightly.

The immortals saw this and immediately kept quiet, many of the Wu clan Gu Immortals who had stood up uncontrollably in anger quickly sat down.

Wu Yong's gaze swept across everyone as the hall fell into silence.

"This is my Wu clan." Wu clan was expressionless but he was incredibly pleased internally.

Ever since he took charge of Wu clan, he had been leading them through crises, they experienced many battles and even chased after Fang Yuan. Most importantly, Wu Yong had incredible political skills, he gained the loyalty of the whole of Wu clan.

Among them, there were not just the original Wu clan Gu Immortals, but also the new lone immortal external elders, and the newly advanced rank six Gu Immortals of recent times.

In the earlier discussion, these people did not raise any objection or suggestion towards Wu Yong's decision and method.

This showed how much prestige Wu Yong had in his clan!

"Supreme elder Ba Chong, explain the situation to everyone." Wu Yong said plainly.

"Yes." As the second supreme elder, Wu Ba Chong stood up and said to the present Gu Immortals: "Days ago, Heaven Refining Demon Venerable, no, I mean Great Love Immortal Venerable, personally sent us a message, he contacted first supreme elder and insisted for him to undergo a public transaction. Thinking of Wu clan, which cannot block Fang Yuan's rage, first supreme elder had to endure the humiliation and agree to Fang Yuan's request."

Wu clan's immortals looked at each other.

Some had a change of expression, some clenched their fists, while some gritted their teeth, they could feel the immense pressure from Fang Yuan just by hearing this account.

Fang Yuan acted in an unrestrained manner, in this situation, it was logical for Wu Yong to be forced into such a transaction.

But at the next moment, Wu Yong laughed loudly: "Oh Ba Chong, no need to say this to them. We are all one family, I will tell you the straightforward truth."

The immortals tensed up and focused.

Bright light shined in Wu Yong's eyes: "This is not my first transaction with Fang Yuan. Before this, we have already done several secret transactions, Fang Yuan's evidence is not fake."

Saying so, Wu Yong paused for a second.

Seeing that the hall was silent and that every Gu Immortal still looked at him with a heated gaze, Wu Yong nodded in satisfaction, continuing: "The reason for this is very simple. Firstly, be it the previous Fang Yuan or the current venerable Fang Yuan, he is an existence that we cannot provoke. Secondly, making transactions with Fang Yuan benefited us greatly!"

"Our Wu clan gained several new Immortal Gu recently, they were all Fang Yuan's creations. If we had to refine them ourselves, we would have spent many times the immortal materials without any success."

Wu clan's immortals were silent.

Wu Yong looked around and went past Wu Ba Chong, his gaze ending up on Wu Qiao.

Wu Qiao shuddered and instantly stood up, speaking in a shivering voice: "But, but... now that these super forces are reprimanding us, how should we deal with it?"

Wu Yong smiled as he nodded at Wu Qiao: "Good question."

Saying so, he extended his hand, all of the information path mortal Gu flew back to him.

Wu Yong blew lightly, a slight breeze went in the air, destroying all of the information path mortal Gu immediately.

"These so-called accusations are completely useless." Wu Yong snickered coldly: "Will they dare to attack us?"

The immortals were stunned.

Wu Yong leaned back on his chair, he was high and mighty as his gaze swept down on everyone: "Do you still not understand? Everyone — times have changed!"

"The fate war, the pursuit battle against Fang Yuan, and the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, after all these, Heavenly Court's foundation has already been expended. Even though Star Constellation Immortal Venerable revived, she had no choice but to announce that the other two venerables were of the demonic path!"

"But both Giant Sun and Fang Yuan are also claiming themselves to be Immortal Venerables, they do not agree with the Demon Venerable title."

"What is immortal? What is demonic?"

"What is righteous path? What is demonic path?"

The immortals were all shaken.

Wu Yong laughed: "With the conflict of three venerables now, the five regions and two heavens will enter an unprecedented great era! If we still use our former judgment to differentiate righteous and demonic, we will only be devoured by the terrifying tides of the new era!"

"Didn't you see how Fang Yuan spent no effort to recruit the entire Righteous Qi Alliance? Our Southern Alliance, against these venerables, is completely useless and powerless. It is impossible to lead a group of sheep to defeat a fierce tiger. Furthermore, against these venerables, we are not even considered sheep."

"The only thing that can fight a venerable is a venerable!"

"Us pitiful worms need to survive between the cracks of the venerables. We need to work hard and absorb more nutrients to strengthen ourselves, if we can gain the pity of destiny, we might have a chance of survival."

"Give up the so-called pride of the righteous path, break free from the restraints of cheap morals and virtues, abandon your superiority complex as a Gu Immortal, these are all superficial and worthless things. Like the information path mortal Gu I destroyed earlier, a venerable can kill all of us Gu Immortals with just a simple breath as well."

Finally, Wu Yong raised his volume and said solemnly: "Work your very best, spend every minute and second of your life to fight for survival in this terrifying great era!"

"Yes, we have learned much from first supreme elder's wise words!" Wu Ba Chong, Wu Qiao, and the other Wu clan Gu Immortals stood up and replied solemnly.

Western Desert.

Wan clan headquarters.

A banquet had just ended, in the main hall with many used cups, there were only several Wan clan Gu Immortals left.

Rank six Gu Immortal Wan Zhui Qing smashed the cup in his hand on the ground in anger.

"These hypocritical and vicious clans, they are a disgrace to Western Desert! Don't they have the glory and resolution of the righteous path?!" Wan Zhui Qing shouted in anger, his face was flushed red.

"Zhui Qing." Wan Xiao frowned slightly.

"Am I wrong?" Wan Zhui Qing was still furious: "These last days, we held a small banquet every three days and a large banquet every five days, but what about these Gu Immortals? They are all giving vague replies and refuse to give definite answers!"

"Zhui Qing!" Wan Xiao shouted.

"Forget it, forget it." At this time, Wan clan's first supreme elder left his seat with a solemn expression, but his back seemed to be bent and weak.

The remaining Wan clan Gu Immortals fell into deep silence.

Outside Wan clan's headquarters, Tang Fang Ming and Tang Miao flew in the sky while looking at the stars, they were very relaxed.

"Occasionally coming out to relax is a good decision, brother." Tang Miao smiled.

Tang Fang Ming nodded, having the same feeling.

He was the rank seven Gu Immortal expert in Tang clan who received the most support, but different from Shi Kang, the reason why Tang Fang Ming was supported and placed great importance upon was because he had extraordinary talent and aptitude in dream path exploration.

This time, they went to Wan clan because Tang Fang Ming's beloved sister Tang Miao wanted to go sightseeing.

"Brother, Wan clan attended to us really nicely, they are very determined to deal with Fang clan as well. After negotiating with the various clans these days, Wan clan has already relented multiple times. When do you think the alliance army will be formed?" Tang Miao asked.

Tang Fang Ming smiled coldly: "The alliance army against Fang clan is not going to be created."

"What, why?"

"Let's take an example." Tang Fang Ming sighed, "Currently, the five regions and two heavens is like a forest with three fierce tigers that are exceptionally scary."

Tang Miao's eyes lit up: "Brother, you mean the three venerables?"

Tang Fang Ming nodded: "Other than these three fierce beasts, there are many birds, rabbits, and fish. Right now, a small bird called Wan wants to deal with a small rabbit called Fang. The bird knows it cannot win alone so it gathered other birds and rabbits to try to pay a high price, in order to bully the individual."

"However, the rabbit named Fang is currently leaning on a fierce beast. Nobody knows if the fierce beast will get angered if they touch this rabbit. If the fierce beast moves, no matter how many animals the bird named Wan gathers, they will all become food for the fierce beast."

Tang Miao was somewhat surprised: "Brother, you mean to say that this is the reason why these super forces cannot form an alliance army?"

Tang Fang Ming nodded again with a solemn expression: "No matter how harmonious the banquet is, or how intense the negotiation between Wan clan and the others get, they are all superficial in nature. The truth is that these animals are shivering in fear and deeply alert regarding the beasts. If any of them move in the forest, none of the animals can stop them."

Tang Miao took in a deep breath: "Thankfully, our Tang clan has been in contact with Lord Fang Yuan since long ago, we have undergone countless transactions. In my opinion, since Southern Border's alliance leader Wu Yong made a transaction with Fang Yuan publicly, our Tang clan can also..."

"Absolutely not!" Tang Fang Ming said: "Every action by Lord Fang Yuan contains deep meaning. The reason why he exposed evidence earlier and showed the transactions with many forces and Gu Immortals, without mentioning our Tang clan, is because he is protecting us!"

"Our Tang clan cannot compare with Southern Border's Wu clan, or even Fang clan, we are a weak force in Western Desert, because of our territorial location, we would be easily ganged up on and attacked."

"At this time, we cannot cause any commotion or raise attention to ourselves. We should only continue to work with Lord Fang Yuan in secret, we cannot waste his efforts."

"Of course, the information of Wan clan gathering the forces can be sold to Fang clan as a favor from us."

"Fang clan and Lord Fang Yuan have many transactions, from this angle, they are our natural ally."

Tang Fang Ming spoke frankly, but he had a clear view of the situation, Tang Miao listened with shining eyes, gaining realization as well.

But at this time, Tang Fang Ming's expression changed slightly.

"Brother, what's wrong?"

"Gu Immortals are transacting with Fang Yuan again in treasure yellow heaven, there are three people this time! Among which, two are from Northern Plains and Central Continent." Tang Fang Ming replied quickly with a flash of excitement in his eyes.

Chapter 2224: Power of a Refinement Path Venerable

A lump of fire was burning quietly in Fang Yuan's hand.

The fire was only the size of an infant's fist, its color changed constantly. If a refinement path expert saw it, they would shout out in shock.

Because the change in the color of the flame was only the superficial appearance, the essence was something different.

For example, red flame meant fire refinement. When it was white, that was light refinement. When it was icy blue, that was ice refinement…

Fang Yuan clenched his fist lightly, the flame disappeared instantly.

Fang Yuan kept silent as he fell into deep contemplation.

A long while later, he blinked his eyes and retracted all of his scattered thoughts.

During this period of time, he had been personally refining Immortal Gu and did not activate Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool at all. He refined more than ten Immortal Gu that were mostly rank six and seven, it was not an accomplishment for someone like Fang Yuan.

But in this process, Fang Yuan gained a considerable harvest.

His current refinement path attainment level was at supreme grandmaster! Any Gu refinement method was very easily discerned by him, he could understand their full profundity. No Gu recipes had hidden secrets in the eyes of Fang Yuan.

Right now, Fang Yuan could modify most recipes with a single attempt. Even for the more profound Immortal Gu recipes that needed some time to modify and expended a lot of effort to deduce appropriate immortal materials, by simply using Fang Yuan's refinement path intuition, he could just take a look to understand the exact direction that the Immortal Gu recipe should go in.

Fang Yuan tried many times, his attempts confirmed that this intuition gave correct answers with certainty!

This was the same for modifying refinement path killer moves and Gu refinement methods. Once, when Fang Yuan was refining Gu, he had an inspiration and thought of a new Gu refinement method, he succeeded on the first try!

When he personally refined Gu, Fang Yuan could feel a sense of control.

This sense of control greatly raised the success rate of refining Immortal Gu. When he refined the various Immortal Gu, when he got to a certain point of the refinement process, Fang Yuan would have a feeling that success was guaranteed.

Even if the Gu refinement was going to fail, Fang Yuan still had the sense of control. He could predict the failure of the Gu refinement in advance.

After all, even a refinement path venerable could fail when refining Immortal Gu.

On one hand, it was the refinement method. If any human error occurred, failure was guaranteed.

On the other hand, the various paths still had their own constraints. For example, refining fire path Immortal Gu would need a large amount of fire path immortal materials. Fang Yuan's control over the fire path immortal material would be much lower naturally since his fire path attainment level was way inferior to refinement path.

"But when I try to refine refinement path Immortal Gu, the success rate is basically a hundred percent. Of course, I have not tried to refine rank nine refinement path Immortal Gu yet."

Fang Yuan had already confirmed this point.

Refinement path Immortal Gu would use a large amount of refinement path immortal materials, Fang Yuan's control over these refinement path immortal materials was a hundred percent!

On this point, be they Old Eccentric Tian Nan, Old Immortal Kong Jue, or Long Hair Ancestor, they could not compare to Fang Yuan.

Because Fang Yuan was a refinement path venerable, he could refine the natural refinement path dao marks of the outside world.

Refinement path immortal materials contained refinement path dao marks, they were also subjected to this. Thus, Fang Yuan had perfect control over these immortal materials.

Thus, as long as there were no errors in the refinement method, with few immortal materials from other paths, the refinement path Immortal Gu's refinement would have a success rate that was infinitely close to a hundred percent!

In terms of Gu refinement success rate, Fang Yuan had already surpassed Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool.

This was under the condition that he had little practice and was not proficient in many refinement path methods and killer moves yet.

Even though Fang Yuan was a refinement path venerable now, he still had a long way to improve in terms of refinement path.

"Other than practicing more and gaining experience, in the future, when my other paths' attainment levels rise, my success rate in refining Immortal Gu of those paths will also rise rapidly as well!"

"It is a pity that I cannot retrieve the Primordial Domain in treasure yellow heaven yet."

Fang Yuan did not have a way to retrieve the Primordial Domain, thus, he kept the Primordial Domain that he obtained from Giant Sun Immortal Venerable in treasure yellow heaven, he continued to pay the fee for storing it there.

Thinking of treasure yellow heaven, Fang Yuan recalled the three Gu Immortals that transacted with him earlier.

These three came from Southern Border, Central Continent, and Northern Plains.

They had open transactions that used their real names, thus the five regions' Gu Immortals learned of the details.

The Southern Border Gu Immortal was a member from Qiao clan, which was Wu clan's vassal, the open transaction between Qiao clan's Gu Immortal and Fang Yuan was likely instructed by Wu Yong to alleviate the political pressure on Wu clan.

Other than that, there was the lone immortal from Northern Plains and demonic immortal from Central Continent.

The truth was, after Wu Yong's transaction, there were many Gu Immortals who wanted to secretly contact Fang Yuan for Immortal Gu refinement.

But Fang Yuan's rule was that the transaction had to be openly done, thus, many Gu Immortals hesitated.

Only a few Gu Immortals, because of their own nature or external pressure, accepted Fang Yuan's rule of an open transaction.

Afterwards, Fang Yuan chose these two people.

They did not have high cultivation level, they were rank six Gu Immortals that were at the bottom of the Gu Immortal world.

Maybe it was because of their identity at the bottom, these two were more inclined to take risks and try to change their current situation.

It was like how poor people often disregarded their lives, while rich people were cautious and scared of dying.

Of course, these two people were no longer in Northern Plains and Central Continent.

Nobody knew what Heavenly Court's and Longevity Heaven's reactions would be after they made a transaction with Fang Yuan. These two Gu Immortals were not stupid, they escaped to another region immediately.

In the past, this action would have many drawbacks.

But with the dissipation of the regional walls and the unification of the five regions, as well as the movement of qi tides, the heaven and earth qi of the five regions became the same, there were no longer differences.

Thus, no matter which region a Gu Immortal went to, they would not be restricted by heaven and earth qi.

"The following period is crucial." Fang Yuan did not know what the reactions of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would be, he was anticipating them with alertness and wariness.

According to his deductions, there were four possible reactions from the two venerables.

First, they could send subordinates to kill these two rank six Gu Immortals. This was easy, Fang Yuan purposely chose them back then because they were weak.

If these two died at the hands of Longevity Heaven and Heavenly Court, Fang Yuan would be very happy.

Second, the two venerables cooperate to attack Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was very wary against this situation, but he wanted to see this as well.

Third, the two venerables target treasure yellow heaven instead.

This situation would be the same as crippling the foundation of Fang Yuan's Great Love Gu refinement plan.

But the possibility was too slim, ever since treasure yellow heaven appeared, it had existed until now. During this time, Heavenly Court, Longevity Heaven, Shadow Sect, and other geniuses and outstanding experts wanted to find treasure yellow heaven, but they all failed.

Even now, Fang Yuan did not know where treasure yellow heaven was.

It was truly an extremely mysterious existence.

Fourth, which was the most likely situation that the two venerables would choose, was to ignore Fang Yuan's Gu refinement business since they could not stop it anyway. They would target other aspects, like elevating their cultivation and forces, to try and use other advantages against Fang Yuan's Great Love Gu refinement plan.

"The truth is, ever since we left Crazed Demon Cave, the contest between me, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had already begun. Whoever can develop the best will have the greatest advantage in our upcoming fights."

"Advantages may not become victory in the end, but as advantages accumulate, the eventual outcome will be affected for sure."

Fang Yuan had a clear recognition of his standing among the three venerables.

Recalling the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, Fang Yuan was aware that he could win because he had the most accurate combat tactics.

Because Fang Yuan only showed pseudo venerable battle strength, and because the venerables had been using him as a pawn all along, they did not think much of him subconsciously.

Be they Giant Sun Immortal Venerable or Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, they treated each other as the greatest threat.

This gave Fang Yuan a lot of room to maneuver.

But venerables were not so easily deceived.

Thus, Fang Yuan purposely exposed his ambition in refinement path, causing the two venerables to find out that he was trying to become venerable through refinement path.

After that, when he had sufficient accumulation in refinement path attainment level, he purposely gave up the fight over Primordial Domain in front of the two venerables.

With the refinement path portion of Primordial Domain destroyed, both venerables knew that Fang Yuan could not become venerable in the short term, they let their guard down against him.

On this basis, Fang Yuan continued to expose his weakness.

For example, Zhan Bu Du had been extremely high-profile in the few fights he was in, it caused a huge headache for Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Thus, Fang Yuan purposely let him die at Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's hands.

Or for example, reverse flow protection seal, Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress, and other methods that the venerables knew about.

Fang Yuan purposely used up these methods so that the venerables would be even less on guard against him.

Fang Yuan had even planned to sacrifice the Qi Sea clone purposely.

But even at that extent, the two venerables were still not assured about Fang Yuan, at certain times, they worked together to try to eliminate him first.

That was the most dangerous moment for Fang Yuan.

He had both internal and external threats, his life was hanging on a thread in many situations. After all, Spring Autumn Cicada could not be used.

Thankfully, Fang Yuan got through those ordeals and finally saw the light of day at the end of the tunnel.

The two venerables consumed each other's strength, while Limitless Demon Venerable's appearance and Paradise Earth's venerable ascension attempt caused the two venerables' attention to be shifted to them.

Eventually, Fang Yuan took a chance to kill Paradise Earth and repel the two venerables, becoming the greatest winner in this battle in Crazed Demon Cave.

Other than the proper combat tactics, the most important criteria for victory was that Fang Yuan had made all sorts of preparations before the battle started.

Fang Yuan obtained ability Gu and fortitude Gu, they were extremely useful in Crazed Demon Cave.

Fang Yuan raised the cultivation level of his subordinates, allowing White Rabbit and Miao Yin to fight against Duke Mei and Duke Tong.

Fang Yuan deduced and modified many killer moves like Dang Hun Luo Po Seal, road of life, several hundred totem killer moves, heaven envies heroic geniuses, and countless compound killer moves.

Fang Yuan even created the artificial earth vein and defensive food path methods, he also prepared dream path killer moves.

Most of them were used in Crazed Demon Cave, if he had not made ample preparation, even if Fang Yuan had the proper tactics, he could not last until the end.

"I became a refinement path venerable and gained the most benefits in the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable are placing a huge focus on me now."

"I need to do everything to raise my strength and develop further, that is how I can accumulate my advantage in the contest of three venerables."

The results of development now would be the crucial factors affecting the victory of the contest of three venerables in the future!

Chapter 2225: Enemies On One Hand, Cooperation On The Other

Northern Plains.

Longevity Heaven.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable held onto an information path mortal Gu as he thought to himself and sighed with a calm expression: "To think that as a venerable, I will actually be unable to do anything against a mere Northern Plains rank six lone immortal."

With Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's temper and nature, Gu Immortals publicly transacting with Fang Yuan were simply provoking him!

In the past, such a Gu Immortal would have already died countless times.

The pride of a venerable was not to be trampled.

But now…

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable summoned one of the Eight Extremities and said: "Go, secretly transmit to the Huang Jin tribes to try to recruit this person. Whoever succeeds will receive my special reward."

"Yes." The member of the Eight Extremities answered and left respectfully.

At this time, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable could not make any statements personally, it would be disadvantageous to him and Longevity Heaven.

But he could let the Huang Jin tribes take action.

This was the political skill of an experienced ruler.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable knew that Fang Yuan's Great Love Gu refinement plan could not be stopped. It was an open scheme that everyone could see, but the desires of Gu Immortals could not be suppressed.

If Giant Sun Immortal Venerable tried to stop it, or if he ordered people to kill this Northern Plains lone immortal, he would lose the hearts of the people in Longevity Heaven.

He might be able to suppress it for a while, but the more he stifled it, the deeper this discontent would accumulate, and when it erupts in the future, a huge problem would occur in Longevity Heaven.

Eventually, the result would be simple —

Northern Plains' lone immortals and demonic cultivators would find Fang Yuan for public transactions. After that, they would leave and escape to the other regions. Most likely, they would go to Eastern Sea, which was under Fang Yuan's control.

That was the same as Fang Yuan using Immortal Gu to lure these lone immortals and demonic cultivators of Northern Plains to Eastern Sea, strengthening his own Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable would not fall for such an open scheme.

"Fang Yuan is too arrogant, he does not have enough immortal essence but he dares to publicly provoke us, hmph, we need to retaliate!"

If the battle in Crazed Demon Cave let Giant Sun Immortal Venerable learn of Fang Yuan's battle strength, then currently, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable learned of Fang Yuan's shrewd and ruthless political skills.

Thinking about it, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable took out an information path Immortal Gu from his immortal aperture.

The information path Immortal Gu quickly flew towards Central Continent.

Central Continent, Heavenly Court.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was also thinking of a way to deal with Fang Yuan's method.

She called for He Feng Yang and personally talked to him before giving him a mission.

When He Feng Yang left Heavenly Court, he was still in a confused state.

The mission that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable gave him was to publicly transact with Fang Yuan and refine a new Immortal Gu!

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's countermeasure was even more simple than Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's.

Since Fang Yuan declared that he would show his great love to the world, refining Gu for enemies and allies alike, Heavenly Court would use this to their advantage. It was a fact that they could not stop his scheme, thus, making use of it to gain benefits was a wise choice.

Of course, Heavenly Court and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would not make transactions with Fang Yuan openly, this was still not acceptable. After all, they had denounced Fang Yuan as a Demon Venerable earlier.

As for the transaction between Fang Yuan and He Feng Yang, be it success or failure, Heavenly Court would stay indifferent towards it, showing a political attitude that they would not care about the actions of the ten great ancient sects in this aspect.

This way, the ten great ancient sects would get involved and obtain many Immortal Gu, that would raise the strength of Central Continent as a whole.

If Fang Yuan were to reject them or state an absurd price, it would go against his earlier declaration, causing him to lose his credibility.

Weakening Fang Yuan's credibility was also a sort of victory for Heavenly Court.

Qin Ding Ling appeared with two information path Immortal Gu.

"Oh?" After Star Constellation Immortal Venerable took a look at them, she fell into contemplation.

The first one came from Southern Border's Wu clan.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable looked into it, Southern Alliance Leader Wu Yong, the first supreme elder of Wu clan, wanted to have an open transaction with Heavenly Court.

Wu Yong seemed to have forgotten that he had led the Southern Alliance to oppose Heavenly Court during the fate war!

A hint of appreciation flashed past Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's eyes.

"This Wu Yong is truly remarkable."

"Earlier, he had transactions with Fang Yuan, now, he wants to transact with Heavenly Court too."

"His ambitions are not small…"

"But it is good too, agreeing to this will benefit Heavenly Court."

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable made a decision to hold transactions with Wu Yong immediately.

On one hand, she was showing her attitude that she was tolerant towards any transaction with Fang Yuan.

On the other hand, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was also trying to pull Wu Yong to her side. Fang Yuan and Wu Yong were very close now, if she rejected him, he might likely join his side.

This was not something Star Constellation Immortal Venerable wanted to see.

As for the second information path Immortal Gu, it came from Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

The content was simple, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable wanted to cooperate with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to take action against Fang Yuan together.

Of course, they were not going to ally without any basis.

After all, during the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had cooperated to a certain extent against Fang Yuan, who became venerable.

The battle in Crazed Demon Cave had just ended, the venerables had not gotten much stronger since.

If the two venerables joined hands against Fang Yuan now, they would only be asking for humiliation, it would not end well.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's idea was to continuously use luck path methods to survey Eastern Sea and investigate Heaven Refining Demon Venerable. If Fang Yuan made any attempt to refine rank nine Immortal Gu, a huge fluctuation in his luck would be observable, by then, they would use the chance to deal with him!

Right now, Fang Yuan was very strong, both Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would be repelled by him, but his advantage was not big enough, so the two venerables were still quite calm.

However, once he refines a rank nine Immortal Gu, he would have to expend a huge amount of immortal essence. Especially during the crucial moments of Gu refinement, if the two venerables find a chance to attack Fang Yuan's major flaw, he would be at his weakest.

If Fang Yuan fails the Gu refinement, he would suffer a terrifying backlash as well.

After all, the refinement of a rank nine Immortal Gu was extremely significant!

Regarding Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's suggestion, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable agreed without second thought.

The truth was, she had her own set of investigative methods to spy on Eastern Sea as well, she was guarded against Fang Yuan, who could be refining rank nine Immortal Gu at any time.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable placed great focus on Fang Yuan's refinement path attainment.

The contest of three venerables was neck and neck, if either side gained a rank nine Immortal Gu, their strength would rise immensely. That would no longer be a contest of equal strength, even territories could be lost then.

The truth was, even if Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not send a letter, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would have sent one to him.

If Fang Yuan was truly given the chance to display his specialty and refine a rank nine Immortal Gu, he would gain the biggest advantage.

That was something neither of the two venerables wanted to see.

This secret plan to stop Fang Yuan from refining rank nine Immortal Gu started with the subtle cooperation of the two venerables.

"If Fang Yuan takes a risk to refine rank nine Immortal Gu, we will strike."

"But even if I cooperate with Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, I still need to mind my immortal essence expenditure."

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable understood that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had more immortal essence than her, but if she expended too much immortal essence when targeting Fang Yuan, even if she spent the same amount as Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, it would not benefit her.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's biggest advantage was in immortal essence quantity after all.

If that situation occurred, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's advantage would be even bigger then.

That was also part of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's secret scheme.

Eastern Sea.

"Oh?" Fang Yuan's expression changed slightly.

Currently, he was refining Immortal Gu while communicating in treasure yellow heaven, he also considered the arrangements and development of his immortal aperture with great ease.

Now, he had received He Feng Yang's request for a transaction in treasure yellow heaven.

"He Feng Yang is actually asking me for an open transaction, it seems that this is Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's idea." Fang Yuan immediately understood the truth.

Without Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's permission, how could He Feng Yang dare to do this?

"Worthy of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable." Fang Yuan praised.

It was a wise and logical countermeasure.

The contest of forces and the fight between experts had never been as simple as allies and enemies. But according to the specific situation, one needed to have the flexibility to change sides.

Sometimes, your enemies could become your allies, you could even work together with your enemies while simultaneously plotting against them.

But this reaction was within Fang Yuan's expectations.

Regarding He Feng Yang's request for a transaction, Fang Yuan's will agreed on the spot.

If he rejected this, it would weaken his credibility and reputation.

Furthermore, what reason was there to reject it?

This was beneficial to Heavenly Court and Central Continent, but it was even more useful for Fang Yuan!

After all, he was the seller who set the price.

It was natural that Heavenly Court and Central Continent were going to benefit.

This was a mutually beneficial transaction where both sides got what they wanted. The losing side was naturally Longevity Heaven.

When Fang Yuan and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable become stronger, Longevity Heaven would be left behind.

But once Longevity Heaven sees this situation, they would want to catch up, even if they were unwilling, they would make transactions with Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan would obviously not reject them, by then, he would be the party that benefits the most out of this.

"Since you want a rank seven Immortal Gu, hand me the nine central stone forest." Fang Yuan quoted his price to He Feng Yang.

Nine central stone forest was an earth path resource point, it could be used as an earth vein node.

The exact value when compared to a rank seven Immortal Gu was not clear. For the short term, the rank seven Immortal Gu was definitely more valuable. But for the long term, a nine central stone forest that could continuously produce earth path resources definitely surpassed just one rank seven Immortal Gu.

This quote was very expensive, far higher than Fang Yuan's earlier price for refining Gu. He Feng Yang could not make a decision, but he had Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's orders.

On the whole, this price was still in the acceptable range, so He Feng Yang agreed to it.

"In the future, when Heavenly Court and Longevity Heaven transact with me further, I will ask for more earth path resource points for fixing earth veins in my sovereign immortal aperture."

The sovereign immortal aperture had already started to prosper and develop.

The current plan was to construct a water vein.

Since the Righteous Qi Alliance joined Fang Yuan, they had to show their sincerity. Fang Yuan gave orders without holding back, he asked the clans to contribute a batch of water path resource points.

"I have tens of yellow apricot immortal essence beads now. I cannot take a risk in refining rank nine Immortal Gu yet, these immortal essence beads are insufficient."

"Let's refine those heaven path rank eight Immortal Gu first."

Chapter 2226: Light Fire

Southern Border.

A group of five Gu Masters were sprinting rapidly on the road.

The leader had rank four cultivation level, he had an ordinary face but was exceptionally capable.

It was Shang clan's Gu Master Xiao Yan.

Moving fire Gu.

He was activating a fire path Gu worm now to travel. Each step he took, flames would be ignited on the ground, causing a huge trail of fire to burn along his path.

Behind him, the four Gu Masters all had rank two cultivation level, they were gritting their teeth as they followed him.

"Lord Xiao Yan, let's rest for a while, we don't have enough primeval essence." While running, a rank two Gu Master suggested.

"Mm..." Xiao Yan slowed his speed but he was still running.

This was the wilderness, if Gu Masters did not have sufficient primeval essence, they would face great risks in surviving. A rank two Gu Master was also not qualified to explore the wild, they lacked the capability and strength.

But right now, Xiao Yan had a mission to do.

"According to the information, if I am any later, the fire in the village will be unstoppable. I need to hurry there now!"

"Last time, I was misled by the enemy's information and went out to search for fire path Gu materials, causing Lady Shang Xin Ci to face great danger."

"This time, I need to work hard and complete this mission to make up for my mistake!"

Thinking of this, Xiao Yan made up his mind, he ordered: "You four, go rest, I will head there first. After you are done resting, catch up to me."

"Yes!" The four Gu Masters answered.

Xiao Yan's speed rose to its limit, he quickly went into the forest.

A few hours later, he arrived at his destination, a small village that was under Shang clan's control.

"Lord, you finally came! The village has already prepared some wine..." The village head was a rank four Gu Master, he spoke to Xiao Yan politely.

But Xiao Yan waved his hand: "The fire is more important, we need to resolve this issue first."

The village head was overjoyed: "Lord is wise! Please come with me, to speak the truth, I have been very anxious these days!"

The village head brought Xiao Yan to the back of the mountain.

Xiao Yan saw that in a crevice at the back of the mountain, there was a white dazzling flame burning intensely.

"That's right, this is light fire!" Xiao Yan stared from afar as his pupils shrank: "This light fire is too big, it covers a range of at least two hundred paces, this is beyond my capabilities."

Light fire was a type of special fire, it was a rank five Gu material. From what Xiao Yan knew, this Gu material could be used to refine rank five light path or fire path Gu worms.

From the perspective of a Gu Immortal, the essence was clear. This light fire contained fire path and light path dao marks.

"To think that I could not find any special fire earlier no matter how I searched. But once I took this mission, I found such a large area of light fire."

"Lady Shang Xin Ci purposely gave this mission to me, she is simply too kind and merciful."

"Sigh, this gratitude..."

Xiao Yan sighed internally, he gradually understood Shang Xin Ci's intention.

He slowly got closer to the light fire.

As the distance shortened, he felt deeper emotions internally, he became angry for no reason.

This was not strange.

This was the effect of the light fire, the closer one got to this Gu material, the angrier they would become.

Xiao Yan tried to use fire path methods and quickly kept away a lump of the light fire that was the size of a basin.

Xiao Yan nodded internally.

His earlier evaluation was right, such a large field of light fire could not be taken by him alone, but he could keep most of it. Afterwards, the four rank two Gu Masters would arrive and help him to complete this mission successfully.

But they had to be quick.

Gu materials like light fire would spread and grow rapidly in the day. But now was night time, the light fire's growth was suppressed.

This was also the reason why Xiao Yan rushed there at full speed while leaving his subordinates behind.

"Before they get here, I need to make arrangements in the surroundings in case of enemies." Xiao Yan immediately used his alert methods near the light fire.

Guarding against others was a necessity.

Furthermore, in order to retrieve this light fire, Xiao Yan had to use his full strength.

"Why are there still mortals in the surroundings?" While surveying the location, Xiao Yan found that there were many mortals praying within the mountain's forest, towards the fire.

The village head quickly guaranteed that he would chase these mortals away, for the following period, he would not let these mortals interrupt Xiao Yan and his subordinates.

Next, the village head explained the reason.

It turned out that because the sky had gotten strange recently without white heaven or black heaven, day and night could no longer be differentiated.

Thus, the Gu Masters of the five regions and even mortals were deeply shocked and fearful.

On a certain night, fire rain fell from the sky. Lumps of heaven flames landed in the range of ten thousand li around the village, these mortals were shocked by the phenomenon and thought that heaven was angry and punishing these mortals by burning them to death. Thus, they were all kneeling here and praying for forgiveness.

"Foolish." Xiao Yan snorted coldly but his expression became milder.

He could understand them.

When the sky first changed, he was also extremely fearful. but with the information from Shang Xin Ci, he learned that even though this was a huge event, it was not dangerous to them. Even if there were danger, it was not something that Gu Masters at Xiao Yan's level should care about.

At the same time.

Immemorial white heaven.

Or more accurately, in the fused black and white heavens.

A few tens of thousands of li away, Fang Yuan watched the huge sun from afar.

The sun seemed to be moving forward slowly, but it was traveling rapidly on a fixed route, going from east to west, before u-turning and going back from west to east, repeating the process endlessly.

Whenever the sun went to the extreme east of immemorial white heaven, or the extreme west, twelve hours would pass exactly.

With the swap of black heaven and white heaven, the five regions would be enveloped by the night sky.

And in white heaven that was above black heaven, the sun would go on the return route from west to east, spending twelve hours to reach the starting point.

By then, black heaven and white heaven would swap again.

Thus, in the view and perception of mortals, the sun had always appeared from the east of white heaven when the night sky fades. When it was dusk, the sun would vanish into the extreme west as the night emerges.

The sun was very large.

Among the eleven venerables, even Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, who had the largest body that resembled a mountain, was far inferior to the sun.

The size of the sun, in Fang Yuan's estimation, was about the size of giant hero sea area, and that was one of the largest sea areas in Eastern Sea.

Originally, in immemorial white heaven, the sun's travel route had absolutely nothing in its way.

But now, with the fusion of both heavens, the environment changed abruptly and chaotically.

While Fang Yuan was observing, a large area of black clouds blocked the sun's path. Whenever the sun moved forward by a little, a large portion of the black clouds would dissipate.

Of course, the sun was not completely unharmed, from time to time, sparks would fall off the surface of the sun.

These heaven flames would land on the black clouds or scatter elsewhere. An even smaller portion of them would land in the five regions.

From Fang Yuan's perspective, the collision of the black clouds and the sun was like the collision of two groups of dao marks. The former was dark path and cloud path, while the latter was light path and fire path.

"The black cloud is bound to lose but the sun's expenditure is also considerable. With such an intense change, it is no wonder that heaven form has turned chaotic, and is also at the brink of breaking apart."

Fang Yuan was originally refining heaven path Immortal Gu, the reason why he suddenly changed his plans and came up to the two heavens of Eastern Sea was because of heaven form.

Heaven form was left by Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable, it was considered half a Thieving Heaven true inheritance.

Back then, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable had encountered a natural heavenly spirit in immemorial white heaven by chance.

This natural heavenly spirit could not be brought out of white heaven or placed into one's grotto-heaven. It was filled with heaven's will that was constantly replenished at all times. Even Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable could not use his human will to refine it forcefully.

After thinking long and hard, he found a solution. He forcefully condensed it and created an immortal killer move, calling it — Heaven Form!

The refinement of heaven form needed a long period of time and generations of wills to cleanse. One day, it would be truly refined by a Gu Immortal, by then, it would be usable.

Afterwards, this heaven form killer move was obtained by the Heaven Surveying Five Xiangs who made the thousand year bet, eventually ending up in Fang Yuan's hands.

Heaven form was a huge help to Fang Yuan, especially in terms of invading the two heavens' grotto-heavens, as well as displaying great use during the fate war.

Heaven form was like a one-legged crane that was covered in snow-white feathers which had no dust or dirt, it had a long beak that was red in color.

When activating it, it would spread its wings and fly elegantly. When it was inactive, it would shut its eyes and stand on one leg, its neck would coil up on its back as it rested silently.

Heaven form had been kept in immemorial white heaven all along, Fang Yuan could not take it away.

Because its foundation was in immemorial white heaven.

Now that immemorial white heaven and black heaven were fusing, heaven form's foundation was affected. Fang Yuan had to help it in time and stabilize its form, otherwise, without external aid, it would be destroyed!

Chapter 2227: Fang Yuan's Loving Consolation

The white crane-like heaven form cried out in front of Fang Yuan.

It was in great pain, its body twisted and curled up at times.

Fang Yuan's fingers were spread like blooming flowers as he activated his refinement path killer move, traces of green and fragrant wind moved around the white crane like chains coiling on its body, stabilizing its form.

Heaven form was originally declining in condition, but after using this method, its collapse was slowing down.

But that was not enough.

The white crane continued to cry out.

"Don't worry, I am around, I will protect you." Fang Yuan continued to console it.

This was a killer move from an information path Gu Immortal, because it was special and had refinement path effect, Lang Ya land spirit kept a copy of it.

After Fang Yuan's modification, he abandoned the original name and called it loving consolation, it seemed like information path but was actually a refinement path method, after returning to its roots, the effect was greatly elevated.

This move could allow the Gu Immortal to use words of consolation on an incomplete Immortal Gu to affect the refinement process.

For example, if on the brink of failure, Fang Yuan consoled it repeated as such:

"I know you can do it!"

"Work hard!"

"You can definitely succeed, believe in yourself."

If these words of consolation reached the incomplete Immortal Gu that was about to break apart, its condition would stop worsening, it could even recover and succeed in refinement in the end.

However, this move had certain restrictions.

Firstly, the effect was continuous, each sentence had little effect on the process, only through an accumulation of non-stop speech could there be an evident effect. Thus, during refinement, if there was a sudden accident and this move was not used in time, or maybe the effect of this move could not catch up with the speed of deterioration, then the refinement process could not be salvaged.

Secondly, this move could only be used on an incomplete Immortal Gu. That was to say, the refinement must reach a certain stage before this could be used. Otherwise, without an incomplete Immortal Gu formed, this move could not even be used. Many Gu recipes refined Immortal Gu immediately, there was no intermediate step of forming an incomplete Immortal Gu first, thus, this could not be used in such situations.

But Fang Yuan could use it now.

Because this situation was a little special.

Heaven form was originally intact, but with the fusion of black heaven and white heaven, it suffered major injuries and could be treated as an incomplete Immortal Gu.

Of course, the basis was that Fang Yuan was a refinement path venerable and had the attainment level and methods to treat the rank nine killer move, heaven form, as a Gu worm undergoing refinement.

"Don't worry, with me around, you can rest assured." Fang Yuan continued to speak gently.

But heaven form's cries were getting louder.

Suddenly, heaven form's snow-white feathers started to blaze up. It was originally an ember but the fire soon grew after a few breaths of time, becoming the size of a human palm.

Fang Yuan immediately took action, breathing in deeply and activating his killer move as two lumps of qi that were white and blue respectively blew out of his nose.

The two breaths first landed on the feathers and extinguished the flames before turning into frost and preventing the fire from starting again.

"Thankfully, I used this refinement path killer move before, I am considerably familiar with it." Fang Yuan was glad internally.

If not for that, he would not be able to handle it in time.

The larger the fire, the greater the cost Fang Yuan would have to bear when he dealt with it. If the fire spread throughout heaven form's body, then this killer move would be destroyed, even Fang Yuan could not save it then.

"You must pull through, your master believes in you!" Fang Yuan said lovingly.

The white crane's cries became louder and sharper.

"What's going on?" Bright light shined in Fang Yuan's eyes.

Soon, he realized the problem.

A wave of black poisonous liquid appeared in the white crane's body and started spreading rapidly, corroding everything and causing the killer move to be nearly destroyed internally.

The white crane vomited intensely as black liquid came out of its mouth.

Fang Yuan grunted and knew that he could not use a fire refinement method, otherwise, it would trigger the previous fire. Thus, he pointed.

Instantly, a hundred green light specks flew into the white crane's mouth like a swarm of insects.

The green light spread around the poisonous liquid and grew rapidly.

Stalks of green grass grew rapidly, absorbing all of the poison in the white crane's body.

Fang Yuan flicked his finger again as golden light flowed like water, entering the white crane's body and cutting all the grass away.

Powder also entered the white crane's body and helped to heal it at this time.

"Everything will be over soon, there is light at the end of the tunnel, don't give up!" Fang Yuan encouraged it again.

But the white crane screeched intensely, its body started to twitch like it was shocked by lightning.

Next, its long and elegant body started to inflate like a balloon, it got larger and larger, seemingly reaching its limit and about to explode.

Fang Yuan quickly stretched out his hand and grabbed with five fingers as a huge rod appeared in his palm.

"Just one refinement path killer move is not enough!"

Fang Yuan's thoughts flashed rapidly like sparks in his mind, he manipulated the Gu worms in his immortal aperture and prepared another killer move.

At the next moment, sharp icy spikes appeared on the huge rod.

Boom.

Fang Yuan exerted strength into his arm and slammed down on the white crane's body. It immediately cried out in pain and looked at its master in utter disbelief.

But Fang Yuan was still smiling gently: "You must believe in master, believe in yourself too."

Boom.

Fang Yuan waved the rod and slammed down again, the white crane's inflated body was forcefully deflated, powerful air currents gushed out of the holes on its body that were left by the spikes.

Boom.

Fang Yuan smiled gently: "White crane, be good, work harder."

Boom!

Fang Yuan smiled sincerely: "White crane, you are so cute, persevere on, we will succeed eventually."

Boom boom!

Fang Yuan smiled mercifully: "No matter what you experience, don't ever give up. With me around, I won't let you die."

The huge rod slammed down once more, while the white crane had already broken down mentally!

Boom!

After a loud impact, it nearly fainted.

There were no movements anymore.

However, its body returned to the original size, it no longer was inflated but was covered in injuries, it was barely still alive, no longer displaying the power of a rank nine killer move.

Fang Yuan stored away the huge rod with icy spikes.

He nodded in satisfaction and muttered to himself: "Although it is my first time trying these two moves together, my refinement path venerable intuition is not wrong, there are no mistakes at all. The effect is just as strong as I expected."

"This move is not like loving consolation, it has wide usage, I can practice it more in the future!"

"Next time, if such a situation happens, I will use this again."

As if the crane heard Fang Yuan's words, its 'corpse' shook intensely and its mouth was tightly shut.

With the fusion of white heaven and black heaven, heaven form fell into a deep predicament, Fang Yuan had to guard it at all times and use refinement path killer moves to stabilize it whenever an issue occurred.

"The difficulty is not high now, but the future is uncertain. By guarding heaven form, I am also restricted greatly, the more I try to save it, the more immortal essence I will waste."

Fang Yuan did not have much immortal essence to begin with, this made the problem even worse.

"But I cannot abandon heaven form!" Fang Yuan had to preserve this killer move, from his luck inspection through Cooking Luck Pot earlier, Fang Yuan analyzed and found that heaven path was his best choice in getting past his current predicament.

Like now, while guarding heaven form, he was also refining other heaven path Immortal Gu in the sovereign immortal aperture!

A new heaven path Immortal Gu was refined!

This heaven path Immortal Gu looked like a crystal spider, it was clear and transparent with no flaws on the body. The spider's eight legs were slim and long, its body was also small and raised high by the eight legs.

Rank eight heaven path Immortal Gu — Heavenly Web!

This Gu was the core of the heaven path killer move, heavenly web protection veil. Back then in Crazed Demon Cave, Paradise Earth used it multiple times, it had outstanding defensive properties, it was definitely on par with Fang Yuan's reverse flow protection seal.

After Fang Yuan killed Paradise Earth, he found that there were only two heaven path Immortal Gu in his immortal aperture.

One was heavenly web Gu, the other was heavenly birth Gu.

Heavenly birth Gu was used by Paradise Earth to revive, it was also his core Immortal Gu when converting from earth path to heaven path.

There were also many other Immortal Gu.

Like information path Immortal Gu Summary, it could allow a Gu Immortal to deduce the general summary of a complicated information.

Or for example, rule path Immortal Gu Normal, it could allow the target to recover to their normal condition.

By using these Immortal Gu, Paradise Earth formed many heaven path killer moves like heavenly web protection veil, emotionless heaven and earth, heavenly summary earthly norm, and others.

These Immortal Gu were all destroyed by Paradise Earth's will before his death.

Currently, heavenly web Gu was refined, Fang Yuan had to refine heavenly birth Gu next.

Heavenly birth Gu could heal Immortal Gu, when used with Fang Yuan's refinement path killer moves, it could have an effect on heaven form!

Fang Yuan had his own heaven path accumulation before this: Rank eight heavenly secret Gu, heaven's envy Gu, and the heaven envies heroic geniuses killer move that he used in Crazed Demon Cave, as well as the heaven form that he was saving now.

After making huge gains from looting Paradise Earth, Fang Yuan gained a large increase in heaven path foundation.

"Especially in Paradise Earth's heaven path research results, there is a method called obscured heavenly secret that can use the power of heaven path to conceal oneself, it is very useful to me!"

Fang Yuan's greatest objective was the killer move obscured heavenly secret. After that, it was to refine heavenly birth Gu and stabilize heaven form.

Obscured heavenly secret could be modified, in theory, the more heaven path Immortal Gu used in the move, the greater the concealment effect.

Fang Yuan had to resolve his predicament of insufficient immortal essence, he had two choices right now.

One was to develop his immortal aperture. But accelerating the time in sovereign immortal aperture was not a good idea, Fang Yuan could only expand his Great Love Gu refinement plan and try to get more resource points added into his immortal aperture to raise his immortal aperture origin core and produce more immortal essence.

The other solution was to advance Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus!

Rank eight Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus was extremely helpful to Fang Yuan, without it, Fang Yuan would have run out of immortal essence in Crazed Demon Cave.

It had such an incredible effect, whoever used it would understand why it was Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable's vital Gu!

Fang Yuan was now a rank nine venerable, rank eight Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus was not suitable for him. If he advanced it, rank nine Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus would definitely allow Fang Yuan to break out of this predicament!

However, if he tried to advance it now, the information would no doubt be exposed.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable were watching him closely.

Fang Yuan knew this clearly.

He was now rank nine, rank eight Cooking Luck Pot could only barely help him. When he tries to refine rank nine Immortal Gu, his luck would fluctuate immensely, against Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, Cooking Luck Pot would not conceal the luck entirely.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was a wisdom path venerable, it was even harder to conceal the information from her.

"The moment I refine my rank nine Gu is also my weakest moment, the two of them will definitely cooperate to attack me. Thus, this obscured heavenly secret killer move is the crucial factor."

Cooking Luck Pot could not deceive Giant Sun Immortal Venerable because it was luck path.

But obscured heavenly secret was heaven path, it was like how Fang Yuan had little countermeasures against pill path and painting path.

Against heaven path, even Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would be helpless.

"But this method has a hidden threat, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had assimilated with the Dao three million years ago, while Heavenly Court has an immense foundation in heaven path research results. How long can obscured heavenly secret conceal the truth from her?"

Chapter 2228: Control of Immortal Essence Stones

Central Continent.

Three rank six Gu Immortals were surrounding an ancient cloud beast and attacking it.

"Be careful!"

The ancient cloud beast suddenly transformed and raised its speed, attacking the woman among the three immortals.

The female immortal was not fazed, her white blouse moved like a blooming flower, a vague silhouette blocking the cloud beast's attack.

But this ancient cloud beast also attacked more fiercely, even though it was blocked, it did not retreat, instead, it changed its form and enveloped the female immortal entirely.

From outside, it looked like the ancient cloud beast had devoured the female immortal.

"Fairy Lian Yun!" Shi Zheng Yi shouted and wanted to activate an information path killer move anxiously.

But beside him, Yu Yi Ye Zi stopped his action: "Wait! If you use this move and pierce the cloud beast, what if you injure Fairy Lian Yun?"

Shi Zheng Yi stopped and gritted his teeth: "Then what do we do?"

Yu Yi Ye Zi, who had the appearance of a young man, showed a solemn expression: "In this situation, I can only try to use that move."

"What move?" Shi Zheng Yi felt that it was too dangerous: "Don't tell me you are not familiar with it yet?"

But Yu Yi Ye Zi had already started preparing the move.

Sensing the aura of the killer move, the cloud beast enveloped Zhao Lian Yun and rushed towards them.

Shi Zheng Yi immediately used his method to try to stall the ancient cloud beast.

He opened his mouth wide and his tongue could be seen.

The information path killer move activated as Shi Zheng Yi spoke rapidly without stopping.

The power of words affected the ancient cloud beast's body as a formless power accumulated and stalled its movement.

After more than ten breaths of time, Shi Zheng Yi finally heard Yu Yi Ye Zi's voice, he deactivated his killer move with joy and dodged to the side.

Yu Yi Ye Zi's palms aimed at the ancient cloud beast as two beams of light shot out of them.

The beams were pale blue, after landing on the ancient cloud beast, they started to dissolve.

Zhao Lian Yun, who was trapped inside the cloud beast, struggled intensely, she put in more effort and finally broke free from it, regaining freedom.

"Alright, my turn!" Shi Zheng Yi saw that Zhao Lian Yun had escaped and quickly made his move, cooperating with Yu Yi Ye Zi and using an offensive killer move.

Two killer moves landed on the ancient cloud beast, with a loud sound, this ancient cloud beast exploded on the spot.

The ancient cloud beast's corpse turned into lumps of clouds, most were immortal materials. After Zhao Lian Yun and the rest collected the materials, they rested on the spot.

"It was my fault, I got trapped by the cloud beast and caused our immortal materials to not be high in quality." Zhao Lian Yun apologized.

"This loss is nothing. We only have rank six cultivation level but fought against an ancient cloud beast, winning is already a huge achievement, we cannot ask for more." Yu Yi Ye Zi consoled.

Shi Zheng Yi talked loudly: "Ever since the battle of Reverse Flow River, we have not been able to meet up often. While the two heavens are fusing together, with beast groups escaping from the two heavens to Central Continent, we are able to meet again to stop the calamity. Why bother fussing over the small details?"

The friendship of the three immortals was built up during the Reverse Flow River battle.

Even though Fang Yuan was the biggest winner in that battle, the three of them had performed very well in the battle, they were saved by Wei Ling Yang who risked his life, and they managed to hair-raisingly escape with their lives under the reinforcements of Central Continent later.

After they returned to their sect, they received a lot of nurturing.

Zhao Lian Yun smiled and said after Shi Zheng Yi: "Since we do not mind the small details, I would like Shi to accept this gift."

Saying so, she landed an information path immortal material to Shi Zheng Yi.

Shi Zheng Yi was very happy: "Wait, this is trash talk petal flower? This is an immortal material that I need to refine my Immortal Gu!"

He did not stand on ceremony, he took this rank six immortal material and inspected it carefully.

Zhao Lian Yun turned to Yu Yi Ye Zi and smiled as she handed him a refinement path Gu Immortal true inheritance: "I got it."

Yu Yi Ye Zi was very happy: "The refinement path inheritance I cultivate is called eight refinement gates, to think that the rumors are true, a certain generation fairy of Spirit Affinity House actually created the ninth gate on the foundation of this inheritance. Ah ah ah, Fairy Lian Yun, how can I repay you?"

Zhao Lian Yun shook her head and smiled: "This is something within my abilities, it is also your good luck. Thankfully, I am the current generation fairy, otherwise, I cannot have such authority to take the true inheritance."

"As for thanking me, of course I need something too." Zhao Lian Yun said in a casual tone like she was joking: "When you become rank seven or eight Gu Immortals, try to take care of me."

Shi Zheng Yi and Yu Yi Ye Zi's expressions turned slightly dim.

They knew about Zhao Lian Yun's situation.

Zhao Lian Yun had Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's rank nine killer move divine concealment, she was unable to undergo tribulations so her cultivation level could not advance.

In contrast, Shi Zheng Yi and Yu Yi Ye Zi's cultivation levels had increased significantly since the battle of Reverse Flow River.

Shi Zheng Yi gritted his teeth and said: "To speak the truth, I have been trying to find a way for you to break through this limitation. Gu Immortals go through tribulations because of the Heavenly Dao's balancing, heaven's will manipulate calamities and tribulations to form. Fairy, you cannot undergo tribulations because divine concealment hides you from heaven's will. The solution is simple, you just need to unravel divine concealment."

"Divine concealment is a rank nine killer move, the difficulty of breaking this killer move is too high. But with the reign of three venerables now, breaking a rank nine killer move is not impossible. But destroying the killer move is too wasteful. I think, maybe you can find Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to help, she is a wisdom path venerable, I am sure she has a solution."

Zhao Lian Yun smiled bitterly: "Star Constellation Immortal Venerable is high and mighty, how can someone like myself even get to meet her?"

"Fairy Lian Yun, do not look down on yourself. The fact that you own rank nine love Immortal Gu means that you will not be ignored." Yu Yi Ye Zi urged: "But to get Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's help, according to the rules of the ten great ancient sects and Heavenly Court, you will need to pay a huge amount of contribution points. But now, you used your contribution points to exchange for this true inheritance that you gave me, thus... I hope you will take all these cloud beast immortal materials."

Shi Zheng Yi laughed heartily: "Then I will do the same, this is just a small token of my gratitude."

Zhao Lian Yun immediately shook her head: "I understand your concern. If I bring back these cloud beast corpses and hand them over, I will get more contribution points than what I spent for the true inheritance. Even so, the amount that I lack to get Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's help is still too much."

"It is better to invest in you two first and raise your strength to rank seven or eight before you come back and help me, wouldn't that be more efficient?"

Zhao Lian Yun made a lot of sense, after listening to her, Shi Zheng Yi and Yu Yi Ye Zi decided to keep the cloud beast corpses.

"Even so, Fairy Lian Yun, please accept these immortal essence stones."

"Yeah, in the following fights, a lot of immortal essence will be expended. At the crucial moment, you can replenish it using immortal essence stones to deal with dangerous situations."

Shi Zheng Yi and Yu Yi Ye Zi spoke again.

This time, Zhao Lian Yun did not reject them, she took both of their immortal essence stones.

"I do not have many immortal essence stones indeed."

"In fact, the sect is rarely giving out immortal essence stones now. Do you know what's going on?" Zhao Lian Yun asked.

Yu Yi Ye Zi and Shi Zheng Yi shook their heads, they were in the same situation.

Shi Zheng Yi was an information path cultivator after all, he had heard some vague rumors: "The ten great ancient sects are all lower sects of Heavenly Court, all of our immortal essence stones are distributed by them. Ever since the fate war, Heavenly Court has started to reduce the amount of immortal essence stones distributed. By now, they have basically stopped giving out any immortal essence stones. The ten great ancient sects have their own immortal essence stone storage, but to save for the future, they also stopped handing them out."

Yu Yi Ye Zi also said: "Recently, when transacting refinement path immortal materials in treasure yellow heaven, I also noticed this. There are increased transactions in treasure yellow heaven, but most of them are done through resource trading, the circulation of immortal essence stones has dwindled."

"Is Heavenly Court trying to influence the five regions' Gu Immortal world through immortal essence stones?" Zhao Lian Yun's eyes shined with bright light.

All along, the immortal essence stones in the market of the five regions and two heavens were from Heavenly Court.

If Heavenly Court had control of the source, their influence would be huge.

The group that was most heavily affected were the rank six Gu Immortals, and they also had the largest number in the Gu Immortal world.

As one's cultivation level rose to become rank seven or eight, their dependence on immortal essence stones would fall.

And this was very inconvenient for Zhao Lian Yun.

There were mainly two aspects. Firstly, having the transactions in treasure yellow heaven was inconvenient. Secondly, once Zhao Lian Yun had little immortal essence, she would not be able to replenish it quickly without immortal essence stones.

"Don't tell me that Heavenly Court is trying to reduce the number of transactions among the Gu Immortals of the five regions so that they can prevent the lower ranked Gu Immortals from fighting in advance?" Zhao Lian Yun thought to herself.

The phenomenon of reducing immortal essence stones became noticed by more Gu Immortals.

Because there was only one source, which was Heavenly Court, other forces could not do anything about it.

During normal times, immortal essence stones were used as currency for Gu Immortals to trade, but during war times, they were important tactical resources as Gu Immortals could replenish immortal essence with them!

After realizing this phenomenon, the various forces of the five regions started to buy immortal essence stones and stock up on them, this made the supply of immortal essence stones became even lower than before.

Naturally, Fang Yuan had noticed this himself.

"Heavenly Court is trying to weaken the strength of the other forces before war erupts, while raising the value of their own immortal essence stones?"

He was very interested in the secret behind Heavenly Court's immortal essence stones.

Be it Shadow Sect's true inheritance, or Paradise Earth's true inheritance, he had not found any clues. Even during the fate war when Fang Yuan attacked Heavenly Court and destroyed the immortal graveyard, he did not find out the secret of the immortal essence stones.

Heavenly Court limited the flow of immortal essence stones, it caused a huge headache to countless forces and Gu Immortals, but for Fang Yuan, the problem was small.

One immortal essence stone was equivalent to one green grape immortal essence bead, each of Fang Yuan's yellow apricot immortal essence beads were worth a million immortal essence stones!

Several days had passed since Fang Yuan arrived in the immemorial heavens and stabilized heaven form.

"Let's start."

He let out a breath of air and started to prepare an immortal killer move.

Heaven path killer move — Obscured Heavenly Secret!

Chapter 2229: Giant Sun's Attack

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

Mini Eastern Sea.

Jade green water flowed like a large dragon, moving rapidly on the surface of the sea.

Several rank six Gu Immortals were chasing and trying to stop it.

"Quick, the water is flowing towards you."

"Watch this!"

Boom! The water flow rippled, a huge wave of over a hundred feet rose.

"I blocked it! But be careful."

Two rank six Gu Immortals were engulfed by the wave instantly.

"Damn it!" The remaining Gu Immortals used their methods to desperately stop it.

In the end, the jade green water flow did not manage to escape the sea area.

Once time was up, white light surrounded ten li of the sea surface.

He Chun Qiu appeared and shouted, grabbed the air with his hands.

Immediately, the surface of the sea rippled and surged with waves, after more than ten breaths of time, a water path formation was built on it.

This water path formation had a rank seven water path Immortal Gu as the core, the main formation had already expended a batch of water path immortal materials.

As the jade water flowed into the water path formation, it turned into a spiral whirlpool that moved on its own, emitting splashing sounds.

The rank six Gu Immortals here flew into the sky, after seeing this, they cheered uncontrollably.

He Chun Qiu inspected the formation again and ensured there were no issues before he also let out a breath of air.

At this point, the jade green water flow resource point had been placed here.

Jade green water flow was a rank seven immortal material, it had a very famous trait in that it would always be moving without ever stopping.

After Fang Yuan created the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance and took in the Righteous Qi Alliance, he extorted Eastern Sea's righteous path for a batch of water path resource points, this jade green water flow was one of them.

He Chun Qiu was in charge of placing this jade green water flow here. He made an immortal formation and ordered the rank six Gu Immortals to trap this jade green water flow, preventing it from escaping elsewhere. After several days of effort, it was finally completed.

From this day on, the resource point would not only produce jade green water flow, it would also be one of the water vein nodes!

With further development in the future, this might form into a jade green water flow sea area.

"Divine rift whirlpool, seven treasures sea spring, underwater thousand year profound ice island, cleansing water region, rolling pearl water treasury... These last few days, Mini Eastern Sea gained more than ten water vein nodes, only three more are needed before we can form one water vein ring."

While He Chun Qiu was thinking, one of the rank six Gu Immortals asked politely: "Master, I wonder what other instructions there are?"

He Chun Qiu waved his hand at them, a time path killer move was immediately activated, their wounds healed at once.

"You may go back." He Chun Qiu said.

The Gu Immortals left after expressing their gratitude.

They were very busy and needed to go around the place to resolve problems and stabilize the environment of the sovereign immortal aperture.

The number of missions in Star Collection Hall was innumerable.

While watching them leave, He Chun Qiu sighed to himself.

After the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, the sovereign immortal aperture faced two main problems.

The first problem was that strange phenomena were still occurring commonly. The sovereign immortal body's non-conflicting dao marks was the root cause. The more dao marks there were, the greater the problem.

After Fang Yuan became venerable by passing the mini chaotic disaster, he gained a huge number of refinement path dao marks. At the same time, he had been building resource points recently, they were also made of dao marks.

The second problem was that the sovereign immortal aperture lacked manpower.

During the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, he lost about fifty Gu Immortals. A portion of them had died in the mini chaotic disaster, they could not be revived. Among which, there was the Combat Beast King. Most of the rest revived, they were all Gu Masters now.

The current situation was quite peculiar, these people could not quickly ascend to immortal yet.

Thus, even throughout the sovereign immortal aperture, the strongest people were He Chun Qiu, Wu Shuai, Lady White Rabbit, Fairy Miao Yin, and the other rank eight Gu Immortals.

Establishing resource points and setting up formations, these were tasks that only He Chun Qiu and Wu Shuai could do.

Although they did not cultivate formation path, they were still Fang Yuan's clones and shared his attainment levels, other people simply could not do it.

He Chun Qiu had already entered the liver life formation multiple times recently, he had no time to rest at all.

"Maybe, I should ask the main body to give orders and deploy a portion of the Merman Imperial Court's merfolk Gu Immortals to help us?" He Chun Qiu thought to himself.

Compared to the humans, the variant humans were more reliant on Fang Yuan, they were less likely to betray him.

At the same time, Mini Eastern Sea did need to relocate and move in a number of merfolk as well.

Compared to the other four mini regions, Mini Eastern Sea only had hairy men on the three major continents, although the population was not small, other areas had no variant humans at all, they were too empty.

The sovereign immortal aperture was developed and managed by the clones and subordinates, while Fang Yuan's main body focused on guarding heaven form.

Boom boom boom.

Fang Yuan's huge rod continued to slam on it.

This time, there were no ice spikes on the rod, it was burning in flames instead!

Heaven form was gritting its teeth, not daring to emit any cries as it curled up into a ball. The frost that appeared on its body out of nowhere was smashed by the rod before being melted by the flames.

As the black and white heavens became fused to a greater extent, heaven form's condition was getting more unstable.

But Fang Yuan was still quite relaxed.

While stabilizing heaven form, he also activated obscured heavenly secret repeatedly to practice it and gain more insight about the move.

The obscured heavenly secret killer move that he used now was the version that Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable had.

Paradise Earth did not have heavenly secret Immortal Gu, thus he used heavenly web Gu as the core with a large amount of heaven path immortal materials.

After these heaven path immortal materials were used, Fang Yuan's body became covered in a new layer of heaven path dao marks, resembling a fishing net.

Whenever anyone made deductions or tried to investigative Fang Yuan, this layer of the fishing net made from the heaven path dao marks would rapidly change form, the lines would contract and twist rapidly, distorting everything from the original state.

"Thus, obscured heavenly secret's true effect is not to conceal myself from all deductions, but to perfectly mislead them and cause them to arrive at a wrong result."

Fang Yuan had already recognized the essence of this move.

"Once the fishing net's heaven path dao marks are depleted, this obscured heavenly secret would lose all effect."

"Conversely, the more heaven path immortal materials I consume, the more heaven path dao marks would be used to construct this fishing net, which would cause this obscured heavenly secret killer move to become even stronger and long-lasting!"

Because of this, Fang Yuan saw hope of deceiving the two venerables!

Theoretically, as long as he had enough heaven path dao marks, he would be able to prevent the two venerables from finding out that he was refining Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus.

Right now, Fang Yuan had more than a hundred yellow apricot immortal essence beads, once he reached the minimum requirement, he would start refining Gu.

Fang Yuan was anxious to refine Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus because he knew that now was the best time to do it!

The battle in Crazed Demon Cave had just ended, the three venerables' methods were all exposed, while they could not modify their methods yet. Thus, in a fight, Fang Yuan had a greater advantage.

After all, he had more dao marks than Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

If he missed this chance, once the two venerables modified their methods, the result of their fight would be uncertain.

"Immortal essence stockpile is my weakness. If I do not use this chance to fix this flaw, in our standoff in the future, my immortal essence reserves will always be below the two of them, I will always be restricted by this!"

Fang Yuan knew he had to take risks.

Longevity Heaven.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable suddenly shouted, his eyes widened, his gaze pierced through Longevity Heaven and cast down on all five regions.

"Good, with the amplification of Longevity Heaven's luck path dao marks, I can see all the luck of the lifeforms in the five regions!"

Heavenly Court first looked at Heavenly Court.

After a while, he turned to Eastern Sea but could not find Fang Yuan.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was shocked, he quickly searched and found a type of luck in the mixed black and white heaven.

This luck was burning like a furnace, there were cracks on the surface and little firewood at the bottom, there was an immortal crane that resembled a cloud or mist within it, burning slowly in turmoil.

"Heaven form?!"

Instantly, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's eyes burst out with bright light.

He laughed heartily as he understood Fang Yuan's current condition.

"This heaven form killer move is left by Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable, it was used by Fang Yuan during the fate war to invade Heavenly Court. With the fusion of both heavens, heaven form's foundation is unstable, it needs Fang Yuan's protection."

"This rank nine killer move is extraordinary, with Fang Yuan restricted by it, now is the time for me to strike!"

During the fate war, Fang Yuan exposed heaven form. Longevity Heaven had cooperated with him multiple times, thus, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable knew about this information.

After seeing this, the Northern Plains Immortal Venerable set off to Eastern Sea, he moved quickly and resolutely, without a moment of hesitation!

In the mixed black and white heaven, Fang Yuan sighed while smiling slightly.

He had sensed Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's investigation earlier, he purposely dispelled obscured heavenly secret to test it out, the result was that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable moved out to attack him.

"Since Giant Sun is coming, what about Star Constellation?" A dark light flashed in Fang Yuan's eyes.

Chapter 2230: Star Constellation's Attack

Eastern Sea.

Deep within icy sea area.

In the pitch black bottom of the sea, a huge ice mountain filled the vision of two Su clan Gu Immortals.

These two Su clan immortals had rank seven cultivation level, one was Su Chen, he was specialized in healing methods. The other was Su Ming Wan, he cultivated dark path.

The two Gu Immortals were traveling within a rank seven Immortal Gu House.

This Immortal Gu House was called Moving Frame Pavilion, it was a rarely seen strength path Immortal Gu House. The body of the house was like a pavilion, with eight big thick blue-gold pillars supporting the pavilion roof and pressing down on the pedestal. The blue-gold pillars were not straight, but bent with an obvious curvature, the two ends were inwardly curved and the middle section expanded outwardly.

On the whole, the entire Moving Frame Pavilion looked like a huge bird cage with the two Su clan Gu Immortals inside it.

The Moving Frame Pavilion emitted a layer of dark blue light, blocking the sea water that was outside it.

Even so, a cold chill still permeated the place.

After facing the icy mountain for some time, the eyebrows and hair of the Su clan Gu Immortals were covered in frost.

"So cold."

"This ice mountain is made from thousand year profound ice, Moving Frame Pavilion does not have enough defense against it, we need to act quickly!"

Su clan's Gu Immortals conversed while activating Moving Frame Pavilion together, unleashing a strength path method.

Instantly, there was a loud sound as a corner of the thousand year profound ice mountain was cracked by a formless force and floated towards the two Su clan immortals.

After reaching a certain distance, Su Chen immediately took action to move this thousand year profound ice into his immortal aperture.

Boom boom boom.

Moving Frame Pavilion continued to exert strength as pieces of the thousand year profound ice mountain were moved into their immortal apertures gradually.

But good times did not last long, the surrounding ice poison starfish were alarmed by them and quickly approached aggressively.

Su clan's two immortals tensed up immediately.

"I will lure them away, you should take as much as you can!" Su Chen immediately flew out of Moving Frame Pavilion.

In this deep sea, even though he was a rank seven Gu Immortal, trying to lure away the ice poison starfish group was still a risky thing to do.

Su Ming Wan who was left in Moving Frame Pavilion was not safe from danger either.

Who knew what would happen next?

It was not easy to retrieve the thousand year profound ice, even for a super force like Su clan which sent two rank seven Gu Immortals along with an Immortal Gu House that could rival rank eight Gu Immortals, it was still full of danger.

But there was nothing else Su clan could do.

As an Eastern Sea righteous path super force, after joining the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance, they were extorted by Fang Yuan and had to contribute water path resources.

Fang Yuan's requirement towards the water path resources was very high, he needed them to be usable as the water vein nodes.

Naturally, Su clan did not lack such resource points, but they did not want to give up their personal wealth.

Coincidentally, Su clan was situated close to icy sea area, deep within this sea area, there were abundant ice and snow immortal materials.

Thus, they planned to collect the profound ice here and hand it to Fang Yuan to satisfy his request.

"Quick, be quicker." Su Ming Wan raised his speed to the limit, but he still had insufficient thousand year profound ice.

There was no helping it, without Su Chen, his efficiency plummeted.

And worse was that a shark group in the sea got disturbed by them, they swam towards Moving Frame Pavilion.

"Sigh, we have no choice but to retreat!" Su Ming Wan sighed deeply, feeling helpless inside.

He had only found this underwater thousand year profound ice mountain after much trouble, but after this excavation, the environment would be greatly affected, causing a chain of reactions to occur.

The stable ecology would instantly become chaotic, the beast groups here would start fighting against each other. Even if they did not fight, they would be wary against each other. If any commotion occurs, they would attack together, and more terrifying, a beast tide might occur.

For the following period, trying to excavate thousand year profound ice here would have much greater risks!

Su Ming Wan and Su Chen's best choice was to leave and find other suitable targets next.

But right when Su Ming Wan was about to leave, there was a surging aura above the sea.

Su Ming Wan's expression changed intensely.

This aura was grand and imposing, it was mighty and unstoppable, all of the sharks that were swimming were intimidated, they escaped in panic.

Su Ming Wan's expression was filled with shock: "This is a venerable's aura!"

At the previous moment, he felt that a huge sun had flown above his head, across the sea area.

"Giant Sun Immortal Venerable! He is attacking Eastern Sea?!" Su Ming Wan was flustered and panicked, he quickly informed Su Chen about this.

Su Chen was not far away, he was also stunned at the moment.

"Quick, tell first supreme elder about this! Giant Sun Immortal Venerable seems to be moving towards our Su clan." Su Chen could not help but shout in fear.

"Are the two venerables' battle going to take place in our Su clan's territory?" Su Ming Wan was shocked by this guess, his face was as pale as white paper.

However, contrary to their guesses, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not move straight ahead, his speed fell quickly as he stopped above icy sea area.

Next, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's rank nine aura spread out in an unrestrained manner, showing his grand and domineering attitude.

The entire sky rippled with golden light.

The golden light spread rapidly to the sky and sea, expanding in all directions!

Sensing the terrifying aura of the venerable, almost all the underwater lifeforms escaped in panic.

Thanks to this, the two immortals' predicament was resolved.

But they were not happy about it, instead, they started to guess: "What is Giant Sun Immortal Venerable trying to do?!"

"Oh? Giant Sun stopped at icy sea area." In the immemorial two heavens, Fang Yuan quickly sensed this situation.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not conceal his traces at all, it was like he was trying to tell Fang Yuan openly — I have arrived!

Immemorial two heavens.

"So his plan is to stop above icy sea area after all." Fang Yuan had a calm expression.

After the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable recovered to some extent, but his battle strength would not have risen by much.

After leaving Longevity Heaven, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's dao marks would be far inferior than Fang Yuan.

Thus, for Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, even if he saw Fang Yuan's situation, attacking him abruptly would not have any benefits, only Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would gain from this.

It was very wise that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable chose to enter Eastern Sea.

He was currently refining Eastern Sea's natural luck path dao marks!

Once he refines all of Eastern Sea's luck path dao marks, then Giant Sun Immortal Venerable would have a territorial advantage when fighting in Eastern Sea.

Even if he was not in Eastern Sea, he could activate killer move from Northern Plains that would be effective in Eastern Sea.

One could say that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was planting a tower in Fang Yuan's base camp. It could inspect Eastern Sea's situation during normal times, and in battle, the activation of luck path dao marks would allow him to launch attacks on the entire Eastern Sea!

Fang Yuan could not do much to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

He could not leave, unless he abandoned heaven form to return to Eastern Sea and face him.

But in that case, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable only had to retreat and leave, while Fang Yuan would lose a rank nine killer move.

If Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not retreat and fought against Fang Yuan in attrition, Fang Yuan's immortal essence reserves would dwindle further!

In the event they fought, although Giant Sun Immortal Venerable would be at a disadvantage, he would not be killed so easily.

Fang Yuan had expected this to happen.

Long ago, when the heaven vein of the immemorial two heavens started to fuse, Fang Yuan had already deduced the crisis of heaven form.

This problem occurred after the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, from Fang Yuan's perspective, this situation was already very good.

The collapse of heaven form was a problem.

Fang Yuan needed to try to resolve it while using the chance to create an opportunity to refine Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus.

He did not have enough immortal essence now, it was not time to advance the Gu, thus, he could also not expose obscured heavenly secret yet.

When Giant Sun Immortal Venerable checked on Fang Yuan, he immediately retracted this move.

For a person like Fang Yuan, his own weaknesses and flaws were things he could exploit to use against his enemies.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was already influenced by him, next, it was Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's turn!

Heavenly Court.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's beautiful eyes looked at Eastern Sea.

"Giant Sun Immortal Venerable..." She muttered.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable chose to stay in icy sea area, it was really an amazing choice on his part.

Icy sea area was at the western-most part of Eastern Sea, it was closest to Central Continent. By refining the luck path dao marks of Eastern Sea, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was also trying to threaten Central Continent.

"After sensing Fang Yuan's issue, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable made a move. But he did not fight against Fang Yuan, this shows that his battle strength has not risen much, and he is also guarding against me!" Thoughts collided rapidly in Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's mind.

If there were only Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Heaven Refining Demon Venerable in existence, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable would definitely fight his way to the immemorial two heavens now and attack Fang Yuan.

After all, he had abundant immortal essence, even though Fang Yuan had higher battle strength, he could not kill Giant Sun.

A battle of attrition was very beneficial to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

After the battle, Fang Yuan's immortal essence reserves would shrink, he would not be able to utilize his advantage as a refinement path venerable, even rank nine killer move heaven form would be affected and might get destroyed.

But with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable around, the situation was different.

If Giant Sun Immortal Venerable pitted himself against Fang Yuan, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would benefit the most. From this point, it could be seen that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was helping Fang Yuan.

"Heaven form..." Star Constellation Immortal Venerable squinted slightly.

This rank nine killer move could not be allowed to exist!

During the fate war, this was the killer move that allowed Fang Yuan to break into Heavenly Court.

As long as heaven form existed, Fang Yuan could break into any grotto-heaven in the immemorial two heavens. This was a huge threat to both Heavenly Court and Longevity Heaven.

After thinking about it, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable came up with a plan.

At the next moment, she connected to treasure yellow heaven and contacted Fang Yuan.

"Great Love Immortal Venerable, I want your help in refining some Immortal Gu, what do you think?" Star Constellation Immortal Venerable said while smiling.

In the immemorial two heavens, Fang Yuan's gaze flickered slightly.

He had also expected Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to find him.

Fang Yuan understood the intention of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, he said: "What Immortal Gu do you want? Also, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, how will you deal with Giant Sun Immortal Venerable?"

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable replied immediately: "I need star thought Immortal Gu, star eyes Immortal Gu, and permanence Immortal Gu."

Fang Yuan was silent for a while before replying: "Sure, but I need to see your sincerity first."

"Okay, here is my sincerity!" Before Star Constellation Immortal Venerable finished her words, she turned into a star rainbow that flew straight for Northern Plains.

Chapter 2231: Refining Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was very daring, she flew rapidly and went deep into Northern Plains — the former location of Imperial Court blessed land.

She did not target any of the Huang Jin tribe members, she acted like Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, staying in the sky and starting to refine the natural wisdom path dao marks of Northern Plains!

At once, starlight shined in the sky, spreading rapidly to the surroundings.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not move into Longevity Heaven directly.

Although it seemed like this was the best opportunity to attack Longevity Heaven, since Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was far away in Eastern Sea, the truth was that it was not easy for Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to enter Longevity Heaven.

Grotto-heavens were condensed into one spot in the sky, unless the immortal aperture's entrance was open, outsiders could not get in easily.

This was also why heaven form had immense value.

Furthermore, even if Star Constellation Immortal Venerable managed to get inside Longevity Heaven, she could not destroy the rank nine grotto-heaven in a short period of time.

By then, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable would come back and defend the grotto-heaven, he would fight against Star Constellation Immortal Venerable. In that case, if Giant Sun Immortal Venerable gives up on Fang Yuan and fights Star Constellation Immortal Venerable instead, not only would there be risks of getting injured, he would expend more immortal essence as well.

That would benefit Fang Yuan too much!

In this contest of three venerables, they were mutually wary of each other, while thinking of ways to attack the others, these venerables also had to maintain their own development speed.

This situation was very complex now.

If one acted rashly without consideration, they would be courting death.

Having judgment was very important.

If one made an appropriate move with just the right intensity, they would gain a bit of advantage in this stalemate of the three venerables.

The three venerables knew this, thus, each of their actions contained deep meaning and considered the reactions of each other. In most cases, they reacted according to the situation.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had already calculated her current actions clearly.

This was the most advantageous move for her!

Firstly, Fang Yuan had to be weakened.

This person was too shameless and had no bottom line.

In Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's mind, even if they had the same battle strength, Fang Yuan would still be a bigger problem than Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Currently, Fang Yuan's circumstances were very troublesome. The difficulty of maintaining heaven form would only increase with time, because more than half of his heaven path research results came from Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, she knew about this clearly.

Fang Yuan had to guard heaven form while expending immortal essence. This depleted his already low reserves.

And now, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable came to Eastern Sea to refine its luck path dao marks, this was a way to weaken Fang Yuan as well.

At the same time, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable requested Immortal Gu from Fang Yuan in exchange for making a move, this was also a way to weaken him.

In addition, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was also weakened by this move.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had the advantage of immortal essence, this was something that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable knew.

With this advantage, if Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not disrupt him, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's dao mark refinement rate would always be higher than Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Additionally, for Heavenly Court, Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world had a bigger threat than Eastern Sea's Gu Immortal world, it was a well known fact that Northern Plains' Gu Immortals had outstanding battle strength and bravery, this was something that Eastern Sea lacked.

"Star Constellation!"

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable who was in icy sea area gritted his teeth, his expression turned ugly.

But he did not move from his position, he continued to refine the luck path dao marks.

Because Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not attack Longevity Heaven or the Huang Jin tribes, this was not something that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable could not endure.

If Star Constellation Immortal Venerable went beyond this, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable would return and fight with her.

This was undeniable!

If a strong enemy tried to step over one's bottom line, there had to be fierce retaliation. Otherwise, the enemy would think that one was easy to bully, then in the future, life would only get tougher.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not step over Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's bottom line, so there was no intense desire for Giant Sun Immortal Venerable to return to Northern Plains.

So what if he returned?

By then, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could just leave, but could Giant Sun Immortal Venerable chase after her and barge into Heavenly Court?

Even if he reached Heavenly Court, could he fight against Star Constellation Immortal Venerable? Would Fang Yuan not benefit from that?

If Star Constellation Immortal Venerable left and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not chase her, if he returned to Eastern Sea, what if Star Constellation Immortal Venerable went back to Northern Plains again?

If they did this repeatedly, what would be the point of it all?

Was traveling not costly on immortal essence?

If Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did that, he would not be able to refine many of Eastern Sea's luck path dao marks, yet he would spend a lot of time and immortal essence, was that not a huge joke?

The situation was different for Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Even if she attacked or retreated multiple times, she would still get Fang Yuan's Immortal Gu.

Thus, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable chose not to move, he continued refining Eastern Sea's luck path dao marks.

But at this time, Fang Yuan approached Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

"Giant Sun, why must we behave like this? We are both victims of Heavenly Court, they have the deepest foundation and Central Continent is the strongest region, this is an undeniable fact. Furthermore, not long ago, Heavenly Court denounced us as Demon Venerables! We need to join hands and deal with Heavenly Court instead."

"Look at the situation now, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable has openly gone to Northern Plains to refine the wisdom path dao marks there, she is simply disregarding your existence."

Fang Yuan urged him while suggesting: "Why don't we have a transaction, I will pay you Immortal Gu in exchange for you refining Central Continent's dao marks."

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable laughed as he replied: "Fang Yuan, it seems that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable made such a transaction with you too. Since the five regions are one, and the regional walls no longer exist, I can not only refine Eastern Sea's luck path dao marks here, but also Central Continent's. If you want me to let Eastern Sea off, I need to see how many Immortal Gu you can give."

When Fang Yuan and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable were still bargaining, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable contacted him again.

"Fang Yuan, you have already seen my sincerity. It is your turn now." Star Constellation Immortal Venerable asked for Immortal Gu directly.

Fang Yuan was silent for a moment before sending permanence Gu into treasure yellow heaven.

Speaking of which, this permanence Gu belonged to Heavenly Court at first.

Back then, Fang Yuan had obtained it after destroying Heavenly Court's Immortal Gu House, Eternal Yacht, in the River of Time.

After Star Constellation Immortal Venerable received permanence Gu, she inspected it before hearing Fang Yuan's new suggestion: If Star Constellation Immortal Venerable attacked Longevity Heaven or any of the Huang Jin tribes, he would pay her even more Immortal Gu.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable smiled: "If I do that, it will not be just three Immortal Gu." Her attitude was quite similar to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable who was talking on the other end.

Fang Yuan snorted in his heart.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was a wisdom path Immortal Venerable after all, in this situation, she was gaining the most benefits.

Fang Yuan was merely trying to stall for time now to undergo refinement.

As long as he refined rank nine Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus, these losses would all be worth it, even if he had to increase the chips!

But the problem for Fang Yuan now was that he lacked immortal essence!

"It seems that I must accelerate the time of the sovereign immortal aperture." Right now, Fang Yuan's gaze was like a hawk, he stared at heaven form sharply, it shivered in response.

Fang Yuan did not want to raise the speed of time in the sovereign immortal aperture, but there were no alternatives.

At this point, he had already paid a considerable price to get this opportunity. And Fang Yuan's biggest worry was that such an opportunity seldom knocked twice, in the future, he might not be able to do this anymore!

If the opportunity presented itself, he had to grab onto it!

Within the sovereign immortal aperture, Fang Yuan's time path clone He Chun Qiu started to use time path killer moves.

One after another, killer moves were activated, the raging water of the River of Time was drawn into the year essence pool. Next, through it, the water was diverted to the respective sub-pools.

The time path zones that the year essence pool controlled had faster time flow now, it was obvious when compared to the surroundings.

And this difference was expanding and getting more evident.

After Fang Yuan became venerable, the sovereign immortal aperture's rate of time became quite close to the five regions, but now, after he used this method, the difference became larger again.

This was a huge threat, of course.

Normally speaking, a chaotic disaster occurred once a hundred years, now, it might arrive in seventy or eighty years.

Once Fang Yuan's chaotic disaster arrived, the other venerables would find the chance to attack him together, at that time, he would face both internal and external threats!

Fang Yuan had a determined expression, he resolved himself after making this choice.

Whether this gamble was worth it would depend on the future.

As the sovereign immortal aperture's rate of time rose, the production of yellow apricot immortal essence also started to accelerate.

The development of the immortal aperture was improved greatly as well.

The three venerables were in a deadlock now.

As days passed, the five regions' Gu Immortal world focused on these three venerables, observing their actions and discussing their possible future decisions.

Because He Chun Qiu used too many time path methods in this period, he had to recuperate and rest.

Thus, Wu Shuai led the other Gu Immortals and formed the first water vein.

Fang Yuan was facing greater difficulty in maintaining heaven form now.

While Star Constellation Immortal Venerable asked him for a second Immortal Gu.

"Star Eyes, Star Thought..." After hesitating for a while, Fang Yuan chose to give star thought Immortal Gu to Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Immortal killer move — Obscured Heavenly Secret!

On this day, Fang Yuan finally used this killer move officially, it marked the start of Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus' refinement.

This time, obscured heavenly secret was modified by Fang Yuan, it contained a few more heaven path Immortal Gu. Not only was it stronger and thicker, it could even allow him to control the range of obscured heavenly secret to a certain extent.

Fang Yuan was not stingy now, he directly used sixty percent of his heaven path immortal materials.

At almost the same time as obscured heavenly secret's activation, within the sovereign immortal aperture, the refinement to advance Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus also started.

Inside Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool, Wu Shuai, He Chun Qiu, and around ten hairy man Gu Immortals got to their stations and started to wait for the refinement to start.

This was an incredible group that gathered, but they were only helping out now.

The divine sense of Fang Yuan's main body was present now, he was going to refine Gu personally!

Rumble...

Jade light shot out, surging like a flowing river.

Fragrance spread everywhere, causing people to feel delighted.

This was just the first step, but a small mountain of rank nine wood path immortal materials were already expended.

Rank nine Immortal Gu were all extraordinary, while Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus was Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable's vital Gu, it was also the most helpful Gu to Fang Yuan now.

This was a huge uncertainty!

Therefore, Fang Yuan soon sensed a huge fluctuation in his own luck.

Chapter 2232: Furnace Luck

Fang Yuan willed in his mind, rank eight Immortal Gu House Cooking Luck Pot started to activate.

Fang Yuan diverted his gaze and looked up above him.

He saw that his rank nine refinement path luck was like a furnace.

The furnace seemed to be made of clay, there were many cracks on the surface that made it look like it was poorly created.

At the bottom of the furnace, there was a pile of firewood burning intensely. This showed that Fang Yuan was currently using all of his immortal essence reserves!

Within the furnace, two lumps of clouds were intertwined.

One lump was an immortal crane cloud that was white in color with black spots inside, it resembled heaven form. This cloud was close to breaking apart, but each time it was about to collapse, heat would be emitted from the furnace to forcefully gather it again.

The other lump of cloud was smaller, it resembled a green lotus. The green lotus cloud was the opposite of the immortal crane, the latter was close to breaking apart while the former was too tightly compacted. Most of the furnace's heat was used on this green lotus cloud, it was trying to melt a piece of limestone.

The green lotus cloud was mostly condensed, only a small portion melted and spread out, flowing towards the cracks of the furnace and sinking to the bottom, as if it was trying to take root.

"The furnace is too crudely made, it is filled with cracks, that shows that my foundation is not stable, the sovereign immortal aperture also has another hidden threat, because it has not gone through an actual chaotic disaster, there is huge room for improvement."

"The immortal crane cloud is heaven form, while the green lotus cloud is my attempt at refining Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus."

"What about the luck of other venerables?"

Fang Yuan tried to look, but he could not see anything beyond the furnace luck.

When he was rank eight, his luck was like a silver light pillar, while the other three venerables' lucks were like clouds floating around him.

Right now, he had become a refinement path venerable, but he could no longer see the venerables' lucks.

Fang Yuan knew the reason.

Other than the two venerables' defensive methods, the main reason was that Cooking Luck Pot's rank was too low. It was only rank eight, it was already outstanding to be able to see Fang Yuan's own rank nine luck. Of course, there were still specific details that could not be seen through it.

If it had to observe the other two lucks and see how they related to Fang Yuan's own luck, the difficulty would be beyond Cooking Luck Pot's capability.

"But even if I can see the luck relationship, I cannot use it as reliable information." Fang Yuan thought.

Before the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, Fang Yuan used luck inspection multiple times.

Now that he recalled it, the luck phenomena regarding Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Spectral Soul Demon Venerable were quite accurate, the main reason for what he saw was that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was split into three existences, while Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was not in his normal state, and they were also not luck path cultivators.

The golden aurora luck of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was clearly not reliable.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable revived through blood path methods, but this important information was not shown in the luck phenomenon. At the same time, his combat system had a terrifying aftereffect, this was also not exposed.

The golden aurora luck that symbolized Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was suppressed most of the time.

Evidently, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had used luck path methods to conceal his own luck and mislead Fang Yuan.

He was Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, the former luck path venerable, he was also clear of how Cooking Luck Pot worked, it was not strange that he achieved this.

Fang Yuan was currently thinking of using obscured heavenly secret to deceive the two venerables. The truth was, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had already been doing this before the battle in Crazed Demon Cave!

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool.

Grey fire was burning intensely, it was huge like a mountain.

Wood path immortal materials were put inside one by one as they melted like candles.

At the bottom of the fire, there was a ten thousand year profound ice.

Rank eight Immortal Gu Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus was sealed within the profound ice!

The Gu Immortals present were tense and nervous originally, but more than ten days had passed since the refinement started, all of them were starting to feel excited and joyful.

"All of the immortal materials have successfully melted."

"At this rate of progress, in just ten or so days, the advancement will succeed!"

"What sort of incredible Gu refinement method is this! On the surface, it looks like the fusion of ice refinement and fire refinement, but in essence, this is the perfect combination of the profundity of the human isolation style and hairy man natural Gu refinement method."

"There are also many crucial points that are filled with mystery. Even if we participated personally and watched the entire process closely, we cannot understand the deep meaning contained within. Master is truly worthy of being a refinement path venerable, the difference between us is night and day!"

But right at this time, Fang Yuan's expression sank.

"Oh no, the Gu refinement is going to fail!"

An intense refinement path intuition filled his mind and body.

Fang Yuan bore no doubt towards this intuition, at the first instant, he realized the truth —

There was a problem with the processing of the wood path immortal materials!

These wood path immortal materials seemed to be fine, but there was a tiny flaw in each step of the process. As these flaws accumulated, they became significant enough to destroy the entire refinement attempt.

If he continued, there would be no point, Fang Yuan made a decision to terminate the Gu refinement attempt!

"What? Why did we stop?!"

"Everything was gone smoothly."

"Fool, master made a decision, it has to be right. We are too weak, how can we understand him? Immediately follow his orders and do it!"

Within Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool, the ten or so Gu Immortals worked chaotically as they gradually stopped the Gu refinement.

After a day and night, under the full effort of Fang Yuan and the rest, the first refinement attempt stopped.

All of the rank nine immortal materials that they invested were wasted.

The Gu Immortals all had mild injuries, even Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool was damaged.

But what made Fang Yuan feel the most loss was the expenditure of yellow apricot immortal essence.

As the main person involved in this refinement, he suffered the most severe injuries!

Immortal killer move — Refine Self.

Fang Yuan used his killer move and refined all of the wood path and refinement path dao marks while feeling glad internally.

"Thankfully, I became a venerable and gained such precise refinement path intuition, even during the process of refining a rank nine Immortal Gu, I still hold the initiative!"

Having the initiative made the situation completely different.

Like this time, Fang Yuan sensed that he would fail and immediately stopped. By doing this, he suffered much fewer losses and most importantly, their injuries were also kept to a minimum due to their precaution.

Rank nine Immortal Gu refinement was not a simple thing, without intuition, if one failed suddenly, more than half of these Gu Immortals would die, while Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool would be destroyed completely, or if he was lucky, a small portion might remain.

But Fang Yuan would suffer much deeper injuries, it was certain to incapacitate him!

But now that he took the initiative to stop, the loss of resources and Gu Immortals, and the Immortal Gu House's damage were kept to a minimum, rank eight Immortal Gu Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus was also intact with no damage taken.

Of course, this had to do with the refinement plan that Fang Yuan came up with meticulously.

This time, he chose to use ice refinement to isolate rank eight Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus first, he would only use it in the last few steps.

"If only I could get some success dao marks from Infallible blessed land, that would be great."

"Or maybe, if I can raise my wood path attainment level, my ability to process these wood path immortal materials will increase, it will help this situation!"

Fang Yuan speculated inwardly.

Even Fang Yuan had not understood completely what the secret behind Infallible blessed land's success dao marks was.

He was a refinement path venerable, theoretically, he was the number one person in refinement path in the world, his supreme grandmaster attainment level allowed him to grasp every single refinement path method in the world.

But Infallible blessed land was the racial inheritance of hairy men, even until today, Heavenly Court had not managed to take control of it, they were very wary against it. Success dao marks were too helpful for Gu refinement, according to Fang Yuan's deductions, it not only contained refinement path profundity but also the essence of human path.

This could be speculated by reading \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>.

Precisely because of the human path profundity, Fang Yuan could not replicate the success dao marks now.

After a temporary rest.

Fang Yuan healed himself while stabilizing heaven form, he also used investigative killer moves to observe the two venerables' actions.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was in icy sea area, while Star Constellation Immortal Venerable went deep into Northern Plains, they were both focused on refining natural dao marks.

"The best situation is to maintain the status-quo." For this goal, Fang Yuan was willing to pay more Immortal Gu to them.

This was a necessary investment!

"However, the two venerables are unable to fully refine the natural dao marks of both regions. I do not have much time left!"

Fang Yuan understood this clearly.

It was a simple thing, Eastern Sea and Northern Plains were huge and contained innumerable dao marks, even these two venerables could not refine them all in a short period of time.

This was an easily proven fact.

He only had to check historical records and see how long the venerables took to roam the world after reaching rank nine.

"The two venerables are limited by not just time but also immortal essence!"

"Once the two of them run out of immortal essence reserves, they will not be able to continue refining natural dao marks, they will stop then. After all, they need to keep a portion of their immortal essence for combat and potential unexpected occurrences."

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan gritted his teeth.

This Gu refinement failure was very disadvantageous to him.

Because it did not fail early but only occurred past the halfway mark, he had to start all over again.

Fang Yuan had too little time, he estimated that there was only one chance left.

"No, one chance is too few."

"It has been tested that even as a rank nine refinement path venerable, my success rate of refining rank nine Immortal Gu is far lower than rank eight."

"It seems that I need to gamble harder!"

Fang Yuan immediately ordered for He Chun Qiu to take action in the sovereign immortal aperture again.

Time path killer moves were used in succession, sovereign immortal aperture's time flow rose again!

But Fang Yuan paid a huge price for this.

Because he had just used time path killer moves earlier, the effect of the current methods were too little. In order to raise the time flow forcefully, Fang Yuan had to use other time path methods.

And the result was that He Chun Qiu's time path dao marks were all used up in the process!

It could be said that this time path clone was basically useless now.

But in the current situation, with Spring Autumn Cicada being unusable, it was not a huge concern that the time path clone became useless.

After everything was prepared, Fang Yuan started to refine Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus again while racing against time!

Chapter 2233: Black Heaven's Heavenly Spirit

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

"Quick, take my place, I can't hold on anymore."

"I'll come!"

"Huff... we finally got through another stage."

Within Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool, the assisting Gu Immortals were all breathing roughly.

After the first failure, Fang Yuan continued to experience two more failed attempts.

He had no lack of rank nine wood path immortal materials, but time was pressing, he had no choice but to use more aggressive methods.

He changed the procedure of the Gu refinement.

Rank eight Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus had to be protected, but the steps before that became more simplified. As a result, the expenditure of immortal essence became more intense, each step became more complex and needed the full effort of the assisting Gu Immortals.

Evidently, they were reaching their limit.

Fang Yuan frowned deeply.

A few days passed but the two venerables did not move, the situation was getting more troublesome for him.

Not only was there little progress in refining rank nine Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus, heaven form was also becoming harder to protect.

The fusion of the immemorial two heavens had reached the most intense moment.

In the sky above the five regions, black and white mixed together while changing rapidly. Day and night alternated at a rapid speed, mortals and beasts looked up in fear, they felt like the apocalypse was impending.

Even the sun's route had changed!

Everything that stood in its path, be they the black clouds or the soul beast army, they were all obliterated.

The heaven form white crane cried out profusely, Fang Yuan tried using refinement path methods but could only slow down the accumulation of its injuries.

Heaven form was getting more and more damaged.

But Fang Yuan had already reached his own limit, he could not modify heaven form anymore. After all, he was currently refining a rank nine Immortal Gu!

"The most crucial factor is time."

"Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable are about to stop as well."

Fang Yuan had already given the third Immortal Gu Star Eyes to Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, he could still stall for a bit of time.

Furthermore, Fang Yuan had been wasting time conversing with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, using the suggestion of transacting Immortal Gu to delay the inevitable.

During this period, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had used their own investigative methods to probe Fang Yuan's situation.

But because of the outstanding effects of obscured heavenly secret, Fang Yuan managed to conceal the truth.

Fang Yuan had already expended a lot of immortal essence, his reserves were hitting rock bottom, meaning his battle strength had also fallen. If the truth was exposed, the two venerables would join hands to attack him!

Deep in Northern Plains.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable looked at the fusing heavens as starlight flashed across her eyes.

"It is about time."

"Now is the most intense moment of the heaven veins' fusion, it is also the most important moment."

"If Fang Yuan gets through this, he may likely get to keep heaven form."

"But how can we let this happen?"

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable smiled, she moved and vanished on the spot like a stream of starlight.

She quickly returned to Crazed Demon Cave.

Because she was familiar with the place, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable easily arrived at the ninth layer void.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was trapped here, upon seeing Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, he roared and charged at her.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was prepared for this, she blocked Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's attacks while activating a method to form an opening.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable flew through this opening as Spectral Soul Demon Venerable chased after her, causing them both to arrive in Northern Plains.

"What?" At almost the same time, Fang Yuan and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had a sensation.

"Is Star Constellation Immortal Venerable thinking of releasing Spectral Soul Demon Venerable to slaughter living beings of my Northern Plains?!" Giant Sun Immortal Venerable frowned.

He had considered this possibility earlier.

But this was not the style of Heavenly Court.

As expected, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not guess wrongly, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable retreated while luring Spectral Soul Demon Venerable to the two heavens.

"Hehehe, Fang Yuan is in trouble." Giant Sun Immortal Venerable relaxed his mind, he started to observe the show as a spectator.

"Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, what are you doing?!" Fang Yuan immediately questioned her in treasure yellow heaven, speaking furiously: "I gave you three Immortal Gu earlier!"

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable smiled: "Precisely so, I will tell you this secret that nobody knows."

"Back then, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable did not want to create soul path, his goal was killing path."

"He is a person chosen by fate, he had immense innate luck and countless fortuitous encounters. Once, when he explored immemorial black heaven, what do you think he saw?"

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable spoke in a delicate tone.

Upon hearing her words, Fang Yuan's expression sank as thoughts emerged in his mind.

This was not hard to guess.

Firstly, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was not in the right state of mind, he lost his sanity and even went to fix the hole in the world boundary in Crazed Demon Cave.

Secondly, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was currently trying to lure Spectral Soul Demon Venerable to the immemorial two heavens, she wanted to give Fang Yuan trouble.

But what kind of trouble was it?

Even though heaven form could only remain in immemorial white heaven, it could still move around despite being on the brink of destruction.

Thus, in theory, as long as Fang Yuan avoided battle and brought heaven form around at a quick speed, he only had to get away from Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

By then, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable without sanity would only attack Star Constellation Immortal Venerable. After all, she was the most threatening person to him.

But now, since Star Constellation Immortal Venerable took such an action, she definitely had ways for Spectral Soul Demon Venerable to target Fang Yuan instead.

With Fang Yuan's current predicament, the most likely answer became obvious.

Fang Yuan snorted in his heart.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable explained the truth: "It seems that you have guessed it. Indeed, back then, before Spectral Soul became a Demon Venerable, he had already obtained food path methods. Once, when he explored immemorial black heaven, he by chance found immemorial black heaven's heavenly spirit."

"Spectral Soul was eager to create killing path, he sensed the opportunity of that from the heavenly spirit. Thus, he used food path methods to devour this immemorial black heavenly spirit into his stomach and fused it with himself."

Immemorial black heaven's heavenly spirit!

Back then, since Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable could find a natural heavenly spirit in immemorial white heaven, why was there no such thing in black heaven?

The reason was that Spectral Soul Demon Venerable had devoured black heaven's heavenly spirit.

"Fang Yuan, I will keep those three Immortal Gu. I need to return to Northern Plains and refine more wisdom path dao marks. I will leave Spectral Soul Demon Venerable with you." After saying this, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable turned around and left.

Seeing that she was leaving, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable showed a hesitant expression.

Staring at Star Constellation Immortal Venerable who left, he turned towards Fang Yuan as there was something that attracted him even more.

Fang Yuan's expression was grim.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was still in the heaven above Northern Plains, but he had already sensed heaven form which was in Eastern Sea. Evidently, after he devoured black heaven's heavenly spirit, although he did not manage to create killing path, he still grasped a lot of profundities that allowed him to create soul path.

When Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was trapped in the ninth layer, he could not sense the five regions and two heavens, but once he arrived in the immemorial two heavens, he clearly sensed the heavenly spirit.

"Black heaven's and white heaven's heavenly spirits originate from the immemorial two heavens, they are like a blessed land's land spirit and a grotto-heaven's heavenly spirit, they hold authority and control over the two heavens."

"Precisely so, heaven form, which uses white heaven's heavenly spirit as the core, is able to find many of the grotto-heavens in white heaven, it can even help me invade Heavenly Court."

"Now, with the fusion of both heavens, the two heavenly spirits of black and white heaven are also seemingly fusing together. No matter which side devours the other, they will gain a huge boost in strength and become the new core of the newly fused heaven!"

All sorts of reasons flashed in Fang Yuan's mind.

Over at the other side, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable made his decision, he charged towards Fang Yuan's direction, seemingly following his instincts.

He had a huge body that was no longer human, but he had genuine rank nine cultivation level, he was extremely fast and simply looked like he was teleporting in black heaven.

Fang Yuan sighed, seeing that Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was getting closer, he took heaven form and started to fly away...

The sun!

The sun was something that existed in immemorial white heaven, it was the biggest counter to immemorial black heaven.

After Spectral Soul Demon Venerable devoured black heaven's heavenly spirit, he would also face such restrictions.

Fang Yuan did not move all over the place.

Firstly, heaven form was very unstable now, if he moved quickly, it might break apart. Secondly, the sun was a favorable environment for heaven form. And thirdly, if Fang Yuan went elsewhere to fight Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, the other two venerables might sense his weakness and take action!

Fang Yuan's main focus was to refine Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus now.

He had to stall for more time and complete the refinement!

Roar—!

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable started to chase Fang Yuan.

Black colored gas spread out into countless chains that shot towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan snorted and used a bit of his attention to destroy the black chains.

His speed rose again as he approached the sun.

As the distance shortened, the intense heat and light forced Fang Yuan to shut his eyes. If not for his defensive methods, he would have already been incinerated.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable chased relentlessly.

He spit out a grand soul river while shooting countless soul spears and triggering explosions. He used all sorts of methods to stop Fang Yuan but midway, the sun's light limited the power of his methods, by the time they reached Fang Yuan, the methods broke apart by themselves.

Heaven form was crying more pitifully now.

The closer it got to the sun, the more light path and fire path dao marks there were, heaven form could not take much more.

"I can't get any closer, otherwise, heaven form is going to break apart." Fang Yuan gritted his teeth, he followed after the trail of the sun, maintaining a certain distance.

But then, after Spectral Soul Demon Venerable finally arrived, he started to fight against Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan fought as he retreated, he had to defend heaven form while dealing with Spectral Soul Demon Venerable. He also had to refine the rank nine Immortal Gu, thoughts were being consumed rapidly in his mind, his immortal essence reserves reached a critical level!

The situation was perilous!

This could not go on, if he fought now, his weakness would be exposed, obscured heavenly secret could not hide anything in that case.

A ruthless light flashed in Fang Yuan's eyes, he knew that those two venerables were currently watching the commotion here with their full attention!

"I can only sacrifice heaven form now!"

At the next moment, Fang Yuan secretly activated obscured heavenly secret.

But this time, the heaven form immortal material he chose to expend was the core of heaven form — the immemorial white heavenly spirit!

Heaven form cried out as it looked at its master in fear.

But in a few breaths of time, it vanished from existence entirely.

A vast number of heaven path dao marks that piled into a dense mountain shrouded Fang Yuan immediately.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable became enraged, Fang Yuan had destroyed heaven form in front of him and left nothing behind.

At the next moment, soul path killer moves erupted, attacks surged like a huge tidal wave in the sky.

Fang Yuan snorted coldly, he turned around and flew towards the sun!

Chapter 2234: Refinement Completed!

Immortal killer move — Seven Kills Rainbow!

Fang Yuan pushed with his palm as a rainbow light shot out.

Bam!

With a loud sound, the rainbow light expanded by tens of times its original size, the huge heavenly beam swept around and destroyed all of the surrounding soul smoke.

After getting a clear path, Fang Yuan raised his speed and successfully broke out of the soul smoke.

At once, the intense sun filled Fang Yuan's vision, the terrifying light and heat wiped out the soul smoke that trailed behind him.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable shouted furiously, tearing its thin layer of soul smoke and chasing again.

"Still following me?" Cold light flashed across Fang Yuan's eyes.

At the crucial moment, he sacrificed the white heavenly spirit, without the burden of heaven form, it was like he had put down a mountain on his back.

Earlier, he could not get close to the sun because of heaven form.

Without this worry anymore, Fang Yuan approached the sun even more closely.

The terrifying white light almost blinded his eyes. The temperature rose intensely, even with three defensive methods, Fang Yuan still felt difficulty in breathing, he was covered in perspiration.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable who was behind him activated killer moves again, hundreds of arms that were thick as huge trees appeared. Black smoke surged from his body, spreading to the surrounding few li.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable got closer to Fang Yuan while covered in thick smoke.

"He wants to use a battlefield killer move to trap me?" Surprise flashed in Fang Yuan's eyes as he took action to destroy the black smoke.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable immediately suffered a backlash, his aura weakened greatly.

Most of Fang Yuan's attention was on sovereign immortal aperture, he had not stopped focusing on the matter of refining Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus.

Frankly speaking, the current Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was giving Fang Yuan very little pressure!

The lack of sanity was Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's greatest weakness.

Like earlier, he followed his instincts and tried to use a battlefield killer move to trap Fang Yuan, it was too stupid. Fang Yuan easily broke it and caused him to suffer a huge backlash.

Earlier in Crazed Demon Cave, Fang Yuan, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, and Paradise Earth were inside the Door of Life and Death, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable had incomparable battle strength then.

But now, without the soul path environment, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's threat became much lower.

"And most importantly, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable is not in a good condition now, he must have paid a huge price to deal with that hole in Crazed Demon Cave!"

"This means that the hole has likely been fixed by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable already."

Fang Yuan knew that if there was a hole in the world boundary, the Heavenly Dao would use methods to heal itself. But because the chaos outside surged endlessly, self-healing was very difficult. The larger the hole, the more difficult it would be.

Back then, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable created a hole that needed several venerables to work together to mend it.

But the hole in Limitless Demon Venerable's Crazed Demon formation was the smallest. The formation resisted the chaos and kept the hole small, allowing Crazed Demon Cave to exist for so long.

After the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable went to fix this hole, he used his own foundation to resist the surging chaos, allowing the Heavenly Dao to have an opportunity to fix it.

Thus, there was no surprise in this outcome.

If the hole still existed, with Heavenly Court's stance, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would not lure Spectral Soul Demon Venerable away. The truth was, if the hole was still around Spectral Soul Demon Venerable would not come out either. According to Fang Yuan's deductions, he would focus on the hole as his first priority!

"It is a pity that ghostly concealment has no effect, otherwise, I can get away from Spectral Soul Demon Venerable."

Fang Yuan inherited Thieving Heaven true inheritance's ghostly concealment, but the venerables knew about this.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, and even Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had ways to counter it.

"Ghostly concealment was created in Thieving Heaven's time, after three hundred thousand years, it is already outdated in the venerables' eyes."

Fang Yuan wanted to modify it too, but he lacked theft path and soul path attainment levels.

But even without ghostly concealment, Fang Yuan could still get away from Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

At the next moment, the battlefield killer move that he prepared for a long time activated!

The killer move expanded and enveloped Fang Yuan, it then condensed into a small dot and vanished completely.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable attacked the original spot with countless attacks but there was no effect, he could only move around the area while growling in anger.

"I cannot waste this chance, such an opportunity will not come again!" Inside the battlefield killer move, Fang Yuan's eyes shined with brilliance, he started to refine Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus with his full strength.

This was his last chance.

Within Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool, flames surged as an icy river melted, pieces of rank nine immortal materials were placed into the fire like cheap vegetables.

At the core of the fire, there was a droplet of red liquid, it was as dense as molten lava.

The red molten liquid was covered in a layer of golden radiance, it slowly dripped onto Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus.

Under Fang Yuan's full control, the red molten liquid slowly permeated and spread around the surface of Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus.

All of the Gu Immortals were silent and did not dare to breathe heavily.

Because they knew that these last few steps were the most crucial!

If he fails, rank eight Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus would be heavily damaged or even destroyed.

Fang Yuan went missing!

At the moment Fang Yuan entered the battlefield killer move, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable used their strongest investigative methods.

Under the protection of obscured heavenly secret, they only saw that Fang Yuan went into the battlefield, they did not find out the truth that he was refining Gu.

"So he used this move after all..." Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was not surprised.

If Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was sane, Fang Yuan would not do something so stupid. But because he was currently unable to think, it was a brilliant decision to do this and avoid him.

"He wants to use the sun to weaken Spectral Soul?" Giant Sun Immortal Venerable guessed.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable stayed at the spot where Fang Yuan vanished, but the sun was still moving forward.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable smiled lightly, she immediately contacted Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and gave a suggestion to work together.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable could not help but feel moved.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not suggest to make a move on Fang Yuan, instead, her new target was Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was not clear headed now, he had also left the Door of Life and Death. Even though he had venerable cultivation level, he was the weakest one. Now was the best time to kill him.

If Spectral Soul Demon Venerable regained his sanity, then there would be a new chess player in the five regions and two heavens.

That was something neither of the three venerables wanted to see.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable not only contacted Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, she also spoke to Fang Yuan.

"This old woman is brewing a good scheme."

"Not only did she get Immortal Gu from me, she also refined Northern Plains' wisdom path dao marks. After destroying my heaven form, she wants to kill Spectral Soul Demon Venerable now!"

The methods of wisdom path Gu Immortals usually came consecutively, they were hard to deal with over time.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was the strongest wisdom path Gu Immortal in history, her methods and schemes made even Fang Yuan and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable wary.

However, it was undeniable that this suggestion was very tempting.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was in such a state, he had strength but not sanity, he was the best prey.

"Normally, I will definitely be moved. But now, refining Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus is the most important thing." Thinking of this, Fang Yuan still agreed to the suggestion.

It was too suspicious if he refused.

On one hand, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable might think that he was lacking immortal essence and did not want to take action, it might cause them to pincer-attack him.

On the other hand, if Fang Yuan hid in the corner, the two venerables would not truly fight Spectral Soul Demon Venerable. They did not want him to reap the benefits as a spectator after all.

Currently, in the sovereign immortal aperture, the sixth drop of red molten liquid had already entered Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus.

Fang Yuan agreed to Star Constellation Immortal Venerable while contacting Giant Sun Immortal Venerable: "Giant Sun, I'm afraid Star Constellation Immortal Venerable has a deeper scheme in mind. Don't forget that she once controlled Spectral Soul Demon Venerable. It is likely that she will use us to weaken him before attempting to take control again."

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable responded quickly: "Heavenly Court is still very strong, while Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's schemes are unfathomable. However, we must try to kill Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, if he regains his sanity, it will be a problem for us all!"

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable also agreed to Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's suggestion.

This was beneficial to him after all.

He had abundant immortal essence now, if everyone fought, they would use up immortal essence, his advantage would become even greater!

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable went into the two heavens, they started to fight against Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

After a few rounds, under the urging of the two venerables, Fang Yuan had to cancel his battlefield killer move and join in the fight with his main body.

It could not be helped.

If he did not go out, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would break his battlefield killer move together and force him out.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable could not think clearly now, he was helpless against a battlefield killer move but the two venerables were different.

Starlight shined while golden light surged, Fang Yuan's totem killer moves also followed after them.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was encircled and ganged up on, he landed in a pathetic state and lost several hundred arms.

He retaliated fiercely with soul rivers and black soul lightning balls that exploded continuously.

His main target was still Fang Yuan!

"If he devoured the white heavenly spirit, his ability to think would return. Is that why he hates me so much..."

Fang Yuan gritted his teeth but did not dodge!

Within the sovereign immortal aperture, he reached the final step.

The ninety-ninth molten liquid landed on Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus and started to spread.

Rumble...

Fang Yuan's vision turned dark, his body was covered in the cries and screams of anguished souls.

Multiple layers of defensive killer moves erupted as Fang Yuan bled from his seven orifices, his soul was shaking intensely.

"What happened?"

"Did he make a mistake?"

The two venerables retreated to the side, in the earlier situation, Fang Yuan should have had time to dodge.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable looked at each other, they did not make a move.

They would not save Fang Yuan of course, but due to conflicting dao marks, if they attacked him, they would be weakening the soul path attack.

Using this chance created by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's attack, Fang Yuan stalled for the last bit of time he needed.

Boom!!!

Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool erupted with unparalleled light, Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus was successfully elevated at this moment, its rank nine aura surged like a tsunami, spreading rapidly and filling the entire aperture!

Chapter 2235: Spectral Soul Alone Is Nothing To Fear

Rank three Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus.

Rank four Heavenly Essence Treasure Monarch Lotus.

Rank five Heavenly Essence Treasure King Lotus.

And above rank five... Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus!

The Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus that he obtained from Lang Ya Sect was finally raised to rank nine at this moment.

This rank nine Immortal Gu still had jade green lotus leaves, its surface was bright and smooth, like it had a layer of glaze. At the center of the lotus, there was the bud of a lotus flower.

The lotus flower had pure white jade-like petals, they were flawless and perfect, seemingly out of this world.

Once rank nine Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus was refined, it activated on its own, absorbing the surrounding primeval energy to convert them into clear dew beads.

These pure dew beads gathered as they flowed along the glazed leaves, gathering into the bud at the center droplet by droplet.

The white jade flower bud absorbed the dew droplets and started to turn pink at the top.

Fang Yuan personally refined this Immortal Gu, he was clear about this, the white jade flower bud would gather more dew droplets and turn from white to pink, and from pink to bright red.

When the flower petals turned red completely, it would bloom and reveal the jade green lotus pod inside.

Within the lotus pod, there would be eighty-one lotus seeds, each of them was a yellow apricot immortal essence bead!

After the yellow apricot immortal essence beads were extracted, the lotus flower would contract and turn white again. Next, it would absorb the clear dew droplets and restart the process again.

"Rank nine Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus, Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable's vital Gu, ranked sixth on the Immortal Gu list.." Information flashed past Fang Yuan's mind, all of them proved the immense value of this Immortal Gu.

But the truth was, Fang Yuan knew that this sixth placing of the Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus was too much of an underestimate.

The reason?

Before fate Gu was destroyed, venerables were invincible, they ruled their own era as the sole supreme entity.

Even though Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable had rank nine Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus and became the richest venerable in history in terms of immortal essence, this advantage was useless in his life.

In his era, he was the only venerable, he had no use for most of his rank nine immortal essence. Without any opponent, even an expert could only live his life mundanely!

But now was different, fate Gu was destroyed and the reign of three venerables appeared, others might even revive later.

"Oh Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus, in my hands, you will shine brightly like never before!"

Fang Yuan was joyous.

This result made all the earlier risks worth it.

Even though he paid a terrifying price.

Adding in his earlier failures, Fang Yuan used up thirty percent of his rank nine wood path immortal materials!

"The crisis is not over yet." Fang Yuan analyzed calmly to himself.

Surrounding him, a black soul river surged endlessly.

"Break." Fang Yuan shouted and activated his killer move, he barged out like a shooting star.

Without the Gu refinement burdening his thoughts, he had a lot of usable strength now.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable attacked again while Fang Yuan retreated.

"Fang Yuan, let's cooperate to attack him." Star Constellation Immortal Venerable reminded.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable also stared at Fang Yuan intently, he used luck path methods unceasingly to try and see how much immortal essence Fang Yuan still had.

Fang Yuan snorted coldly, his expression was livid as he said angrily: "Are you two bullying me because of my age? We were all meant to attack together, but I ended up facing the brunt of his attacks, not only did you two not help me, you even let Spectral Soul Demon Venerable go off while you watched this by the sidelines? Is this your so-called cooperation?"

Saying so, he activated a compound killer move as yellowish brown light shot out to block Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's attack.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was silent before smiling and saying: "Fang Yuan, you are mistaken. Even though we cooperated, our dao marks conflict, making a move would have had negative effects instead."

Saying this, she waved her hand as a large amount of stardust landed on Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, breaking several hundred of his arms.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable also took action, golden light descended like sand and grinded away at Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's luck.

Fang Yuan relaxed his mind at this moment, he sighed to himself as he thought: This obscured heavenly secret killer move is really useful.

The situation earlier was simply too perilous.

As long as the two venerables sensed something wrong with Fang Yuan, they would attack him without restraint. But at that worst timing, he had too little immortal essence and could not fight them.

If they attacked him, Fang Yuan would have no choice but to try and run.

Even though Fang Yuan did not have the white heavenly spirit anymore, this was still a worthwhile trade off.

Even with all of Fang Yuan's methods, it was only because he expended the white heavenly spirit that he could deceive both venerables at such a close range.

But Fang Yuan did not know how long he could continue to deceive them.

As Spectral Soul Demon Venerable roared, he activated burning soul bursting luck to block Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's golden sand.

But Spectral Soul Demon Venerable still charged at Fang Yuan!

Because Fang Yuan destroyed the white heavenly spirit, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable bore huge hatred towards him.

Fang Yuan snorted coldly, he did not fight back with force, he flew towards Star Constellation Immortal Venerable instead.

The three venerables fought against Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, they had their own positions that were far away from each other. But now, Fang Yuan and Spectral Soul Demon Venerable moved quickly, they got close to her rapidly.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable snorted coldly as starlight flew out of her mouth and rained down like a storm.

The starlight rain surrounded Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's body like a river while shooting stars of various sizes shot out of the ripples.

Instantly, countless flying stars appeared in the battlefield, it was a dazzling sight!

"Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had such a move to summon so many stardust specks in a short period of time..." Fang Yuan shook internally.

These stardust specks were harmless to him.

He only had to wipe them to refine all of these star marks, he had the perfect counter to this combat system.

But Spectral Soul Demon Venerable could not do that.

Because he was not sane, after getting hit by the stardust specks, his body became covered in injuries, he roared angrily but his injuries accumulated.

"Good chance!" Fang Yuan turned around and fought again, he unleashed another killer move.

This was a refinement path method.

The killer move shined with intense radiance, enveloping Spectral Soul Demon Venerable and eroding his soul beast body wherever the light went.

But Star Constellation Immortal Venerable frowned deeply as she shouted: "Fang Yuan, what are you trying to do?!"

The reason was that although Fang Yuan hurt Spectral Soul Demon Venerable with this move, the refinement path killer move was also used on the star path dao marks.

Fang Yuan got rid of over half the star marks that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable accumulated over this time.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable benefited from this and went back to a relaxed state.

"A small blunder, it is just a mistake." Fang Yuan laughed heartily.

After a few rounds went by, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable also frowned, he spoke with a tone of anger: "Fang Yuan, what are your true intentions?!"

Fang Yuan said innocently: "I am trying to attack Spectral Soul Demon Venerable along with you. But we have conflicting dao marks, and a lack of cooperation normally, this will get better if we continue to fight."

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable snorted coldly together.

Fang Yuan was doing this on purpose, he was acting like a nuisance, disrupting Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's attacks.

After a few more rounds.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable shouted angrily: "Fang Yuan, enough is enough! The immemorial soul beasts you released are all countered by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable. After devouring them, he recovered by thirty percent."

Fang Yuan rubbed his nose: "I did not know that he had such methods."

Saying so, he brought out a few more immemorial soul beasts.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's eyes shined with starlight specks, she stared at Fang Yuan and said in an icy cold tone: "You are still letting more out?!"

Fang Yuan smiled plainly: "Star Constellation, don't worry, I used a method on these immemorial soul beasts, this is part of my plan. Just watch."

Not long after, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable saw that Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's injuries were recovering even more rapidly, his mental energy also recovered as well.

Before the two venerables questioned him, Fang Yuan rubbed his nose: "Oh, it seems that my plan failed."

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable stayed silent while Star Constellation Immortal Venerable wanted to speak, but Fang Yuan suddenly snorted coldly: "Give me a minute I need to prepare a powerful method!"

Saying so, he flew up to the sky and looked down at the battlefield.

The two venerables looked at each other before taking action to obstruct Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

After Fang Yuan's preparation, a huge field of fire clouds appeared above him. From them, flaming meteors descended, they were all around the size of mountains, there was a long trail behind them as they crashed into Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

Following his instincts, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable roared towards the sky, but he saw that these meteors flew past him without landing on him at all!

Countless meteors flew across the battlefield, descending rapidly.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's expression turned colder as her eyes sparked like lightning, Star Constellation Chessboard appeared above her head.

A large number of pieces flew out of the chessboard and hit the flaming meteors rapidly, destroying them.

Fang Yuan was confused: "Star Constellation, what are you doing?! These flaming meteors are very useful to me, I have a second move to use with them."

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable gritted her teeth: "If I did not stop them, these meteors would have pierced the heavenly wind qi wall and landed in Central Continent."

Fang Yuan smiled coldly: "Star Constellation, we are trying to kill a venerable, are you unwilling to pay a small price like this? If this happened in Eastern Sea, I would not have interfered. With this level of sincerity, you think we can kill Spectral Soul Demon Venerable today?"

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable stared at Fang Yuan: "Fang Yuan, don't go overboard! Among the three of us, who do you think has the least sincerity?"

Fang Yuan's expression also turned cold: "Star Constellation, do you think I am such a person? To kill Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, I gave you multiple Immortal Gu and even lost my heaven form killer move!"

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable were speechless.

It was clearly Fang Yuan's poor planning that got him targeted, he was too weak and unable to protect his rank nine killer move, but now, from his tone, he wanted to seek compensation from them?

How could that be possible!

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable spoke: "Fang Yuan, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable is targeting you. The two of us are helping you to deal with Spectral Soul Demon Venerable now."

But Fang Yuan laughed heartily: "Do I need your help? I can easily take care of this. You two can return to Longevity Heaven and Heavenly Court, I will fight against Spectral Soul Demon Venerable in Central Continent and Northern Plains to the best of my abilities, and I will take his life in the end. Just Spectral Soul alone is nothing to fear!"

Chapter 2236: Secretly Unsealing Truthful Floating Ice

Fang Yuan said while unsealing more immemorial soul beasts.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable moved rapidly, grabbing these immemorial soul beasts and devouring them into his stomach.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's eyelids were twitching while Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's expression turned dark.

Earlier, Fang Yuan emphasized on the words 'Central Continent, Northern Plains', he was clearly using these regions to threaten them.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable suggested that they should kill Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, regardless of her motive, this suggestion itself was a good one.

But because of Fang Yuan's actions, he was clearly disrupting the two venerables and using it as a threat to extort something from them to make up for his losses this time.

The two venerables smiled coldly to themselves, they understood why he would do this.

If they placed themselves in Fang Yuan's perspective, they would do the same thing.

After all, Fang Yuan was a new venerable, he did not have a deep foundation like the other two, he lacked immortal essence as well, these reasons caused him to lag behind the two venerables. If they fought against Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, he would face the greatest risk.

Even if Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was killed, in terms of snatching battle spoils, because Fang Yuan lacked immortal essence and would not be able to last longer in combat, it was likely that he could not outdo these two venerables. In fact, after they kill Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, if he runs out of immortal essence, the two of them would attack him immediately!

Fighting in this situation was very disadvantageous to Fang Yuan.

As for the two venerables?

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable secretly transmitted: "Giant Sun, Heaven Refining Demon Venerable spent a lot of immortal essence to guard heaven form, he is currently at his weakest. You know that he is a greater threat than Spectral Soul Demon Venerable! Why don't we..."

Before Star Constellation Immortal Venerable finished, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable interrupted: "Star Constellation, you can make a move first, I will support you!"

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable snorted: "Giant Sun, your words lack sincerity."

Whoever attacked Fang Yuan first would face his retaliation first.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable said that nicely, but if Star Constellation Immortal Venerable attacked, would he still help? What was in his best interests was to watch Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Heaven Refining Demon Venerable fight it out.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable wanted to work with Giant Sun Immortal Venerable to fight against Fang Yuan. The truth was, she felt more wary against Fang Yuan!

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable also wanted to see Fang Yuan's death.

They all knew that Fang Yuan had the least amount of immortal essence among them.

But how low was low?

They had to make sure of this quantity first.

According to their investigative methods, Fang Yuan still had a portion of his immortal essence reserves.

If either of the two venerables wanted to kill Fang Yuan, they would need to pay a terrifying price. And in this situation with three venerables, they simply could not take the risk.

The two venerables working together was the best choice for them.

But Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not trust each other at all!

They were also worried that if they forced Fang Yuan's hand, he might attack Central Continent and Northern Plains!

Normally speaking, Gu Immortals had their own unspoken rules, they would not attack mortals or Gu Masters. This was something very disgraceful, especially for a venerable, their pride would not allow them to make such actions.

"But with Fang Yuan's principles and bottom line, he would not hesitate to do so." Both venerables agreed on this point with no uncertainty.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was the most protective of his descendants, how could he allow Fang Yuan to slaughter them openly?

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was the second Immortal King of Heavenly Court, how could she watch as Central Continent's ten great ancient sects get destroyed by Fang Yuan? She would become a great sinner of Heavenly Court!

Thus, both venerables did not dare to act excessively.

"Sigh, now it seems that we cannot kill Fang Yuan or Spectral Soul Demon Venerable this time." Star Constellation Immortal Venerable sighed to herself: "In that case, what's the point of wasting time here?"

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable wanted to retreat now, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was thinking of the same thing.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable still felt some grudge towards Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, he transmitted to her secretly: "I have to say, Star Constellation, if you really want to use Spectral Soul Demon Venerable to deal a blow to Fang Yuan, you should have stalled for more time so that he would waste more immortal essence on heaven form!"

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable snorted coldly: "The fusion of the two heavens was short and intense, now is the most unstable moment, it is extremely hard to sustain heaven form. Fang Yuan is a refinement path venerable, with his ability, he should have been able to protect the killer move while resisting Spectral Soul Demon Venerable."

"Who could have thought that he would resolutely sacrifice the white heavenly spirit and give up on this rank nine killer move!" Star Constellation Immortal Venerable showed an expression of pity.

She did not know the truth.

Fang Yuan had done his best at that time, the refinement of a rank nine Immortal Gu took too much of his attention, he had no choice but to give up on heaven form.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable sighed as well: "Star Constellation, don't you understand? Even though Fang Yuan is a demon, he is extremely cautious. He seems to be taking huge risks at times, but he is extremely vigilant inside. Although many of his actions seemed rash and risky, he had done so because of Spring Autumn Cicada, he was greatly assured!"

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable snorted coldly, she did not want to talk with Giant Sun Immortal Venerable secretly anymore, she spoke out loud: "In that case, forget about it. We'll meet again, everyone!"

Saying so, she turned around to leave.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable smiled at Fang Yuan and left just as quickly as her.

Fang Yuan purposely moved slightly slower than them, he was stunned before retreating, but Spectral Soul Demon Venerable pursued him.

Fang Yuan transmitted to the two venerables: "You two left so abruptly, you still want to talk about sincerity?! Spectral Soul Demon Venerable has lost his sanity, are you going to let him slaughter the innocent lives in the world? You two are so cruel, you are vicious people, how can you call yourselves Immortal Venerables?"

After Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable heard his words, they could not help but think of his 'mistakes' earlier which helped to heal Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable kept quiet and did not reply.

While Giant Sun Immortal Venerable smiled and said: "Fang Yuan, we underestimated you in Crazed Demon Cave which resulted in your success. But now, you have to work harder, there is no need to say such things in the future. How can simple words affect the battle between venerables? Powerless excuses will only sound like the expression of the weak."

"Good, good, good." Fang Yuan gritted his teeth and said these words forcefully before he went silent.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable bore deep hatred towards Fang Yuan, even though the two venerables left, he still chased Fang Yuan relentlessly.

After Fang Yuan toyed around with him for some time, he used the same trick to activate a battlefield killer move and conceal himself again.

After Spectral Soul Demon Venerable lost his target, he remained at the area and growled angrily, refusing to leave for a long time.

"Good, while Fang Yuan is trapped, I can use this chance to refine Heavenly Court's wisdom path dao marks." Star Constellation Immortal Venerable returned to Heavenly Court and said in satisfaction as she saw this.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was still on the way back to Northern Plains, he thought: "In this contest of three venerables, Fang Yuan suffered the greatest losses. Not only did he lose the rank nine killer move heaven form and several Immortal Gu, he also expended some immortal essence. If he was not crafty enough to help Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, he will be in a worse state."

"Star Constellation Immortal Venerable..."

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's eyes shined with bright light.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had refined many Northern Plains wisdom path dao marks, the size surpassed the luck path dao marks that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable refined in Central Continent.

The reason was because Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's emphasis was on Fang Yuan's Eastern Sea, although he refined some Central Continent luck path dao marks, the total quantity was only half of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

But Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was not assured, after returning to Longevity Heaven, he used luck path investigative methods.

With some buzzing sound, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable first checked Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's luck, it had gotten slightly stronger.

He looked at Fang Yuan's luck, it was still the same broken furnace as earlier.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable then inspected his own luck and frowned lightly.

"Even though my luck grew stronger, the external threat has grown significantly. What is going on? Where is this threat coming from?"

There were too few things that could threaten a venerable.

"Fang Yuan? No way." Giant Sun Immortal Venerable shook his head.

"The other venerables? Like the possible revival of Reckless Savage Demon Venerable or others?"

"The most likely ones are from Heavenly Court! Star Constellation Immortal Venerable gained a lot this time, while Heavenly Court's two other Immortal Venerables have yet to revive!"

"It seems that my greatest enemy is still Heavenly Court. In comparison, although Fang Yuan is a venerable, his foundation is too thin. In the contest of venerables, one step behind will cause him to lag by many steps later. In the future... if we maintain our advantage, we can just guard against his possible retaliation."

Currently, in terms of venerable battle strength, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was the least threatening.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was the strongest, especially in Longevity Heaven, using his previous life's dao marks, he could forcefully inspect the luck of the other venerables. This was something that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could not do.

But in the outside world, without Longevity Heaven's luck path dao marks, even if Giant Sun Immortal Venerable used similar methods, he could not reach such an effect.

"Maybe I can try to attack Heavenly Court?" Giant Sun Immortal Venerable suddenly had such a thought.

Once Star Constellation Immortal Venerable refines Heavenly Court's wisdom path dao marks, she would receive a greater amplification than Giant Sun Immortal Venerable!

This was because not only had Star Constellation Immortal Venerable contributed her own immortal aperture into it, all of the previous generation wisdom path Gu Immortals had also done the same, becoming part of Heavenly Court's foundation.

But Giant Sun Immortal Venerable soon shook his head, rejecting this idea.

Firstly, he did not have heaven form, the luck path method he used to invade Heavenly Court earlier had been dismantled, he could not get in easily anymore.

Secondly, fighting against Heavenly Court's Star Constellation Immortal Venerable now would expend his immortal essence, it would allow Fang Yuan to catch up.

"In the contest of three venerables, neither can make a move easily. We need more situations like today's to truly claim victory." Giant Sun Immortal Venerable sighed, he did not stay in Longevity Heaven for long, he went back to Northern Plains to refine the luck path dao marks.

Fang Yuan was still 'trapped' in the battlefield killer move, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable had not left yet.

But Fang Yuan was not anxious.

"I'll show weakness for a while longer to relax the two venerables' guard."

"But undoubtedly, this obscured heavenly secret killer move is so useful!" This was not the first time Fang Yuan praised this move.

Right now, obscured heavenly secret's temporary heaven path dao marks were extremely dense, they were like a huge fishing net that wrapped around his entire body.

Within the sovereign immortal aperture, after the first blooming of Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus, Fang Yuan gained ninety-nine yellow apricot immortal essence beads!

A flash of light sparked in Fang Yuan's eyes as yellow apricot immortal essence was rapidly expended, soon, he activated a heaven path method.

Using this heaven path killer move, he started to unseal the truthful floating ice that he obtained from Crazed Demon Cave.

Chapter 2237: Heaven Path Master

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

The blue-white truthful floating ice was shrinking inch by inch.

In the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, Fang Yuan obtained several pieces of truthful floating ice, among them, one was quite large.

As yellow apricot immortal essence got rapidly expended, his heaven path dao marks also grew in numbers rapidly!

Fang Yuan's heaven path dao marks had reached two hundred and forty thousand already, after unsealing the truthful floating ice for six hours, his heaven path dao marks grew by sixty thousand. Ten thousand dao marks per hour, it was quite a good gain.

But this was not his own gain.

Fang Yuan's rule path, wisdom path, transformation path, strength path, earth path, wood path, and others were rising.

"These paths correspond to Limitless Demon Venerable, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, Reckless Savage Demon Venerable, Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable, Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable... These venerables all went into the eighth layer of Crazed Demon Cave, they had their respective investments."

"No, that's not all." After unsealing the truthful floating ice for sixteen hours, Fang Yuan found that his other paths' attainment levels were rising too.

But the growth in the other paths was much smaller and almost unobservable. Only after a long time and with sufficient accumulation could there be any significant changes.

Among all the paths, the attainment level that rose the most was heaven path!

Fang Yuan's foundation in heaven path was actually very weak.

He had only cultivated it for a short time after all. All of his foundation were obtained from predecessors, for example, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's human executing heaven's work, or Limitless Demon Venerable's unrestrained heavenly mark killer move.

Several days later in sovereign immortal aperture, his heaven path dao marks grew to a million and two hundred thousand. His heaven path attainment level went all the way from ordinary to master level!

Fang Yuan stopped for now.

He had expended over a hundred yellow apricot immortal essence beads.

If Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus had not bloomed once more during this period, Fang Yuan would not be able to keep up the expenditure.

"I need to save some immortal essence in case of a venerable battle."

Fang Yuan carefully assessed his gains.

The heaven path master attainment level gave him a comprehensive growth!

Regarding his heaven path Gu recipes, killer moves, and the understanding of the Heavenly Dao, he had renewed insight and even deeper comprehension.

The most crucial thing was the conflict of dao marks!

His earlier intuition was not wrong, after becoming a heaven path master, he would be able to create a conflict dao mark method to completely solve the sovereign immortal aperture's problem.

The sovereign immortal aperture had many different phenomena occurring, the origin was because of the non-conflicting dao marks, they had fused too easily.

Once conflict arose, sovereign immortal aperture would be elevated to a new level, it would regain peace.

Fang Yuan immediately used wisdom path methods to fully deduce the relevant killer move.

Several days passed.

Fang Yuan stored the battlefield killer move and left the immemorial two heavens.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable stayed for a long time but eventually gave up. Now, he was rampaging in the immemorial two heavens while eating soul beast armies and also fighting against the sun.

Fang Yuan had no heaven form killer move left, he could not sense Spectral Soul Demon Venerable who was far away.

But Fang Yuan got back to Eastern Sea successfully.

He landed deep in Eastern Sea and started to refine the natural refinement path dao marks of Eastern Sea.

At once, profound light surged as rank nine aura spread like a tornado to the surroundings, the countless lifeforms nearby fled in fear.

Song clan's Gu Immortals were the first ones alerted, after seeing this, they understood: Great Love Immortal Venerable was refining the natural refinement path dao marks.

Song clan's first supreme elder quickly gathered the Gu Immortals to discuss the matter, they wanted to meet Fang Yuan and offer him a gift.

After all, Fang Yuan was currently in Song clan's territory.

However, they were soon informed by Wu Shuai that the members of the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance were not allowed to disturb Great Love Immortal Venerable now.

Song clan's members signed in relief but they also felt disappointed.

While Fang Yuan refined the natural dao marks, he also continued deducing his heaven path killer moves.

Not long after, he gained some results.

But Fang Yuan was not satisfied yet.

This newly deduced heaven path killer move was not much different from Paradise Earth's heavenly summary earthly norm.

Heavenly summary earthly norm was able to arrange heaven path dao marks to allow the target to recover to their normal condition, it was the counter to battlefield killer moves.

Fang Yuan's deductions allowed heavenly summary earthly norm to go one step further.

When used in the sovereign immortal aperture, it could allow the environment of the immortal aperture to change into the environment of the five regions and two heavens.

The natural dao marks of the five regions and two heavens were definitely conflicting. Thus, after converting them, the sovereign immortal aperture's dao marks would also conflict.

"If I use this killer move hundreds or thousands of times, my sovereign immortal aperture will become like the five regions and two heavens, it will no longer have any strange phenomena."

"But in that case, I will lose my advantage of non-conflicting dao marks, the losses will be too severe and I cannot cultivate all paths again."

That was a cost Fang Yuan could not accept.

Looking at the sovereign immortal aperture's advantage and its abnormal phenomena, the former was naturally more important.

"Can't the conflict appear and disappear according to my will? Segregating the locations of conflicting dao marks like the time path zones?"

Fang Yuan sighed internally.

He had no idea on how to start realizing this concept.

Maybe when his heaven path attainment level reaches great grandmaster or higher, he might be able to achieve this?

This time, Fang Yuan did not have any intuition regarding this, he could not be certain.

"Speaking of which, sovereign immortal fetus Gu is a human path rank nine Immortal Gu. To resolve my current problem, maybe I should target human path instead?" Fang Yuan had a flash of inspiration, he saw a new direction to move towards.

He had found the solution in terms of heaven path, but the price to pay was something that Fang Yuan could not accept.

Would human path work?

Back then, to refine sovereign immortal fetus Gu, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable sacrificed the ten extreme physiques.

Speaking of human path research results, Fang Yuan thought of his clone who was trapped in Divine Emperor City.

After Shen Shang broke out of Divine Emperor City, he only brought back news of the clone who was still lurking inside Divine Emperor City.

"In the current world, Shen Shang is definitely one of the top human path experts, if I want to get his human path research results, what sort of price should I pay?"

Heavenly Court.

"Oh? Fang Yuan left the two heavens and went back to Eastern Sea, he has started refining natural dao marks." Star Constellation Immortal Venerable soon heard of Fang Yuan's actions.

"Even though he has the least immortal essence, he became venerable through refinement path. In terms of refining dao marks, it should be his expertise." Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was very concerned with Fang Yuan's speed of refining dao marks.

If Fang Yuan's efficiency was too high, she would join up with Giant Sun Immortal Venerable to deal with Fang Yuan together.

Otherwise, if he surpassed them in this aspect, it would be a huge problem for Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable!

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not want to think about Spectral Soul Demon Venerable now.

The contest of three venerables had reached a new stage.

Whichever venerable refined the most natural dao marks would have the greatest advantage.

"When refining the dao marks, I can multitask by modifying killer moves and changing my combat system. This will grant me an advantage in the future fight between the venerables."

"Star Eyes, Star Thought, Permanence..."

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable stared at these three Immortal Gu in her immortal aperture as her gaze became focused.

After obtaining them from Fang Yuan, she had already inspected them a hundred times but found no problems.

Yet, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was still a little suspicious.

She was not a refinement path venerable after all, although she had some achievements in refinement path, she could not compare to Fang Yuan at all, this was undeniable.

It was like asking Fang Yuan to compare with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable in wisdom path, they were not on the same level.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had spent a hundred years of time to refine rank nine wisdom Gu in her previous life.

"Even if I find no issues with them, this does not mean that Fang Yuan did not tamper with them. But this possibility is quite small... I also have to use these Immortal Gu no matter what."

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable decided to take a risk.

She cultivated wisdom path primarily with star path secondarily, her combat system revolved around these two paths. But currently, her main method, the stardust killer move, was countered by Fang Yuan.

If Star Constellation Immortal Venerable wanted to gain an advantage in their future fight, she would need to modify it greatly.

In her modification plan, star thought Gu, star eyes Gu, and permanence Gu had a huge role to play. Otherwise, why would Star Constellation Immortal Venerable request for Fang Yuan to make them?

Longevity Heaven.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable retracted his gaze from Eastern Sea.

"Now, I need to pay attention to Fang Yuan's refinement progress." Giant Sun Immortal Venerable reminded himself while checking his own immortal essence reserves.

He only had over five hundred yellow apricot immortal essence beads left.

The refinement of natural dao marks expended a lot of immortal essence.

Longevity Heaven could not produce immortal essence, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was relying on his own rank nine immortal aperture, the production speed was similar to Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Be it Longevity Heaven or Heavenly Court, the revived two venerables were on the same level as Fang Yuan, they had not gone through the first chaotic disaster.

"Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture has immense foundation far surpassing me and Star Constellation. Thus, using the same amount of time, he can produce more immortal essence than us."

"Also, he has a large number of blood path Immortal Gu!"

Thinking of this, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's expression turned a little dark.

He cultivated luck path mainly with blood path on the side, he naturally needed a lot of blood path Immortal Gu.

But Fang Yuan had refined many of them already, although they were kept at rank six, Immortal Gu were unique.

This ruined many of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's wonderful plans.

Earlier, when guarding heaven form, Fang Yuan negotiated with Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, he used these blood path Immortal Gu as the bargaining chip to haggle with Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable managed to get three Immortal Gu from Fang Yuan, but Giant Sun Immortal Venerable got none.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was brooding over this.

"Star Constellation Immortal Venerable knows that Fang Yuan has the sovereign immortal aperture, as long as the latter's refinement speed is fast, I will contact her."

"It is unlikely that she will reject my offer to work together!"

"By then, I will work with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to fight against Fang Yuan again. While expending his immortal essence, I can also extort those blood path Immortal Gu from him."

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable made various plans.

He did not know that Fang Yuan was in possession of Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus, thus, he was more wary of Heavenly Court now.

But now, there was no opportunity for him to attack Heavenly Court or Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Fang Yuan's possession of those blood path Immortal Gu also greatly hindered his own blood path cultivation.

Chapter 2238: Sunken Fish, Song Yi Shi

Translator: Atlas Studios Editor: Atlas Studios

With the fusion of both heavens, the surface of the sea became light and dark at alternate times.

The sun and moon appeared together, all living beings were sent into chaos, in addition to the reign of three venerables, this was an unprecedented situation.

As tides ebbed and flowed, winds blew gently as Fang Yuan sat on a cloud, he slowly opened his eyes.

He had already spent some time refining Eastern Sea’s refinement path dao marks, he had some insight now.

Currently, he had already refined over half of Song clan’s territory in terms of refinement path dao marks, the range had spread to poetic emotion sea area in the northwest, and also Ascending Heaven Plain in the southeast.

All the refinement path dao marks in this area belonged to Fang Yuan.

Currently, even without shutting his eyes, Fang Yuan could sense many things related to refinement path.

He had an extremely clear understanding of the quantity and distribution of refinement path dao marks in this area.

All sorts of refinement path Gu materials deep under the sea, the fish and shrimps that contained refinement path dao marks, even the location of aquatic plants and others could be sensed by him.

Currently, Fang Yuan had many thoughts in his mind, he needed to test them.

He willed and stopped the refinement of dao marks, instead, he used an investigative killer move.

At the next moment, his gaze pierced through the sea and went thousands of li deep, seeing a huge fish.

This fish was as large as a building with five to six storeys of height. The fish had a sharp front and back, with a thick middle section, it was like a shuttle. The scales were grey-black and did not shine, they had a rough texture that felt like gravel.

This was a sunken fish, it contained rule path and refinement path dao marks.

The sunken fish was at least an ancient desolate beast, there were also immemorial desolate beasts among them.

Fang Yuan was looking at an immemorial desolate beast sunken fish.

The sunken fish had a special trait, every few years, it would move its tail and come to the surface to breathe fresh air, that would cause it to be swept by the currents. And because it was heavy, it would continuously sink to the bottom while the currents moved it away.

Whenever it moved its tail and exerted force to reach the surface, the scales of the sunken fish would fall off its body in the process, after it breathed enough fresh air, scales would grow on it again and it would become motionless, floating with the currents while sinking downwards.

These scales that fell off its body seemed heavy but they were light and delicate, most would float to the surface of the sea. After a long time, these scales would be swept ashore, Gu Masters would pick them up and treat them as treasure.

The sunken fish scales were crucial Gu materials to refine beauty Gu, they had high value.

On this point, they were like the feathers of the falling goose.

“But to refine beauty Immortal Gu, I will need to use both immortal materials, sunken fish scales and falling goose feathers.” While looking at this sunken fish, Fang Yuan’s lips curled into a faint smile.

He had the same sensation as earlier when he refined dao marks.

“If I refine the refinement path dao marks in the sunken fish’s body, what would happen?”

Fang Yuan had refined the dao marks of the natural world earlier, it did not include the dao marks of lifeforms like the sunken fish.

Fang Yuan tried it out immediately, he chose a refinement path killer move and modified it a little to allow him to forcefully refine this sunken fish from a far distance!

The forceful refinement had just started when the lazy sunken fish jolted like it was shocked by lightning, it moved its tail quickly and tried to swim far away.

It erupted with speed that did not match its huge size, a huge current was formed in the sea because of the force generated.

“Where are you going?”

Fang Yuan snorted coldly, he activated another method.

The sunken fish immediately stopped moving while Fang Yuan forcefully refined all of its refinement path dao marks.

After the refinement, Fang Yuan’s sensation of the sunken fish became several times clearer!

Fang Yuan let go of the restraint as the sunken fish regained freedom, but its emotions were very negative, there were fear, anger, numbness, sadness, and others, it was as if the fish was undergoing a turmoil and could not continue living its life.

“What happened?”

Fang Yuan slowly observed the sunken fish, he saw that it had stopped eating food.

The food of the sunken fish was not seaweed or fish, it was underwater sea soil.

Every few years, the scales on the fish would turn into ordinary Gu materials or fall off on their own, they could not ensure its safety. Thus, it would sink to the bottom and eat a large amount of soil.

This sunken fish that Fang Yuan tortured had lost most of its scales. Normally speaking, it should sink to the bottom of the sea and eat soil now.

“Did it lose the will to live after I brutally did that?” Fang Yuan shook his head, he quickly used a wisdom path method.

After some deductions, he understood the reason.

The sunken fish ate sea soil to fill its stomach, but also to produce more scales.

The source that produced its scales were the refinement path dao marks on its body.

Because of these refinement path dao marks, it could digest the sea soil and draw nutrients from them, converting them into thick immortal material scales.

But now, all of its refinement path dao marks were refined by Fang Yuan, it lost this ability.

Thus, even though it lacked scales, it did not attempt to eat sea soil.

In order to test his findings, Fang Yuan used a food path killer move on this immemorial sunken fish.

Soon, the sunken fish got hungry.

This time, it chose to eat the sea soil.

But good times did not last, soil soon accumulated in its stomach but could not be digested quickly. If Fang Yuan did not dispel the food path killer move in time, the immemorial sunken fish would have died from stuffing itself with sea soil without being able to digest it.

Fang Yuan used just a few methods to completely cripple an immemorial desolate beast.

“What if I return the dao marks to it?” Fang Yuan started to deduce again, he soon made a refinement path killer move that had an accompanying wisdom path killer move.

Fang Yuan first used the wisdom path killer move to raise the mood of the sunken fish and started to guide it.

Next, he used a refinement path method to teach the sunken fish to refine all of its refinement path dao marks.

Not long after, the sunken fish regained its refinement path dao marks, light returned to its eyes as its life became less bleak, the negative emotions also left it.

It quickly refined the sea soil in its body and turned them into immortal material fish scales.

Fang Yuan nodded, this result was in line with his guess.

Next, he refined the refinement path dao marks of the immemorial sunken fish again.

The sunken fish: “...”

It fell into a state of intense and complex emotions like numbness, fear, anger, and shock.

Fang Yuan used brute force to chase it away to the bottom of the sea, which had fewer refinement path dao marks that Fang Yuan had already refined.

As he expected, his sensation of this immemorial sunken fish became much weaker.

But when Fang Yuan placed this immemorial sunken fish to a place with more refinement path dao marks, his connection to the sunken fish became much clearer and stable.

Fang Yuan waved his hand, seawater erupted, the refinement path dao marks within one li were all destroyed by him.

In his sensation, this place became somewhat like a black hole.

After Fang Yuan placed the immemorial sunken fish into this black hole, he could not sense the sunken fish at all.

“This proves that my refinement path sensation is extended through the dao marks. This is like how a spider uses its webs.”

Fang Yuan’s refinement path sensation was limited to the areas where he had refined dao marks.

These last days, he stayed in the deepest part of Eastern Sea and built his own spider web. If he or his prey left the range of the web, then he would not be able to sense anything.

Fang Yuan felt quite satisfied about this discovery.

Because Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had also refined a portion of Eastern Sea’s luck path dao marks.

As long as Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not personally interact with this area of luck path dao marks, he would not have any luck path sensation, he would not be able to use the dao marks to do anything.

“Of course, I cannot rule out the possibility that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable has immortal killer moves that can allow him to bypass distance and make use of the luck path dao marks he refined in Eastern Sea.” Fang Yuan reminded himself.

After confirming many guesses, Fang Yuan had a lot of gains.

He did the same thing again and returned the immemorial sunken fish’s dao marks to it.

After that, he stopped torturing the poor fish and let it swim away in fear and panic.

Fang Yuan fell into deep thought.

“Even though refinement path dao marks are present all over the five regions and two heavens, they are not evenly distributed, some areas have more dao marks while others have fewer.”

“For me, the more abundant the refinement path dao marks, the better.”

“In that case, after I refine these dao marks, my refinement path sensation will get stronger. When fighting or refining Gu in such an environment, the amplification will be huge.”

“Huh? What was this situation?”

Fang Yuan’s expression changed slightly, he could sense an intense refinement path fluctuation from far away.

“Poetic emotion sea area.”

Fang Yuan immediately used his investigative method and saw through the truth, he quickly found the source of the refinement path fluctuation.

It was Song Yi Shi.

Poetic emotion sea area was the territory of Song Yi Shi, she had built a palace in the underwater volcano.

Currently, she was cultivating in her palace, her clothes were all taken off, exposing her snow-white flesh and slender figure.

She was activating a water path killer move, endless steam was produced.

The steam covered her entire body, making her beautiful face even more alluring than normal.

Fang Yuan understood at once: “So that’s it.”

He immediately deciphered that Song Yi Shi was practicing her water path defensive killer move.

Eastern Sea’s Song clan specialized in water path, they had a signature water path inheritance called flowing water. This inheritance had defensive killer moves like noncorroding flowing water, emotionless flowing water, flowering flowing water and others, they guarded against poison path, wisdom path, and wood path respectively. There were also killer moves like flowing water carriage for movement, thin flowing water that reduced immortal essence expenditure, flowing water wine party that mimicked food path effect, or moving cloud flowing water that helped with killer move activation.

“Song Yi Shi is currently using noncorroding flowing water. This is a passive defensive method, the essence is to carve water path defensive killer move on the body. Once a poison path attack lands, it will activate on its own.”

“This is a form of Gu refinement in essence, except that the target is the Gu Immortal’s physical body.”

“No wonder I can sense it.”

Fang Yuan realized and took a close look.

He had incredible attainment levels, he was a supreme grandmaster in refinement path and a great grandmaster in water path.

After looking for a while, he deciphered all of the profundities of noncorroding flowing water.

Fang Yuan gained some interest.

It was a great opportunity, he had new ideas to test out.

Chapter 2239: Same Origin

Translator: Atlas Studios Editor: Atlas Studios

Song Yi Shi cultivated for six hours before stopping her killer move.

She let out a breath of air and opened her eyes, she saw that a lump of steam that was vague and illusory flowed from her arms to her legs, finally stopping at her chest.

Song Yi Shi looked at the steam and felt joyful internally: “At this rate, I can complete my cultivation of this noncorroding flowing water killer move in half a month.”

“Strange, why did this cultivation session feel more effective than before? Is it just me?”

Song Yi Shi shook her head slightly.

She inspected her immortal essence.

There was little immortal essence left, she also lacked immortal essence stones now.

“Sigh, Heavenly Court is the source of immortal essence stones, once they stopped distributing those, the entire market’s immortal essence stones fell greatly in number. I have grandfather’s help in secret, but all other Gu Immortals should be having a tougher time!”

Song Yi Shi sighed to herself.

If she had enough immortal essence stones, she would use them to replenish her immortal essence now to continue cultivating the noncorroding flowing water killer move.

But now, she had to slow down and let her immortal essence produce immortal essence naturally. After it accumulates to a degree, she could resume her cultivation.

“After I complete the noncorroding flowing water killer move, I will move on to emotionless flowing water. My clan’s flowing water inheritance is our signature inheritance, it is renowned in Eastern Sea, being quite exceptional even in the five regions. Passive defensive killer moves are rare to begin with, normally speaking, Gu Immortals can only cultivate one of them, they cannot stack many passive defensive killer moves.”

“But my clan’s flowing water inheritance has a unique concept, it is ingenious. By using the same core, we can stack passive defensive killer moves.”

Thinking of this, Song Yi Shi felt a little proud of her background.

But soon, such emotions vanished.

“Sigh, I am still far from success.”

“After completing emotionless flowing water, I will undergo tribulation and reach rank seven.”

“With the contest of three venerables and the fusion of two heavens, the five regions chaotic war may erupt at any time!”

Song Yi Shi was originally the prized jewel of her clan, she was doted on by her grandfather and received the support of the clan, having no lack of resources. Her incredible appearance also made her one of the six beauties of Eastern Sea.

But her carefree life could no longer return.

The situation was changing too rapidly, Song Yi Shi felt no sense of assurance at all. Currently, all of Eastern Sea’s righteous path super forces had joined Fang Yuan’s side, this was something unimaginable in the past!

The external pressure forced Song Yi Shi, this prized jewel, to have an intense urge to cultivate.

Especially when Song clan’s first supreme elder, Song Qi Yuan, who was also her grandfather, gave Song Yi Shi some exciting news.

In the letter, Song Qi Yuan nagged endlessly before mentioning the orders of the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance, they were going to pick a number of merfolk Gu Immortals from the Merman Imperial Court to live in sovereign immortal aperture.

Even though Fang Yuan did not specify the ratio of male to female he wanted, the Merman Imperial Court purposely chose some female immortals with the most beautiful appearances and elegant demeanors.

In addition, Fang Yuan had never been known to have any love interests, he had always faced great external pressure all the way until he became a venerable, now that he could rival Heavenly Court and Longevity Heaven, his pressure fell immensely.

Along this train of thought, Song Qi Yuan mentioned Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Back then, after Giant Sun Immortal Venerable became venerable, he took in all the beauties of the world and created five harem palaces.

Afterwards, he mentioned the other venerables.

All the ten venerables had partners in their lives, only the number was different.

Even the unmarried Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had once been in love, it involved a certain variant human Gu Immortal...

Song Qi Yuan vaguely suggested an idea in order to probe the intention of his beloved granddaughter.

“If Great Love Immortal Venerable wants to choose a wife or concubine, will Song clan offer me to him?!” Initially, Song Yi Shi was very angry.

But a few days later, she calmed down and thought about it rationally: “Grandfather will not force me, he is only raising this possibility and wants to see if I am willing to do so.”

“However, if Great Love Immortal Venerable orders this personally like Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and wants to collect beauties, how can I escape? How can Song clan protect me?”

Song Yi Shi, who had always been proud as a crane, felt bitter and helpless internally after she realized this.

“If such a situation occurs, I cannot burden this clan which nurtured and raised me. Grandfather loves me so deeply, he funded me and gave me water clothing Immortal Gu secretly, if not for this Immortal Gu, how could I have modified the killer move and successfully cultivated the flowing water inheritance? How can I repay him? How can I let my unwillingness lead to Song clan’s extermination?”

“How can I be this selfish?” Song Yi Shi thought of this and felt a deep sense of guilt internally.

Along this thought, she thought of the deeper aspect.

“If Great Love Immortal Venerable has such intentions, for the sake of the clan, I need to offer myself to him. Why should I wait until then? Why can’t I go further and take the initiative instead? If I can succeed, by just sacrificing myself, I will ensure the prosperity of Song clan for countless years!”

“Sigh, I’ll stop thinking about this...”

Fang Yuan did not know that just one order from him led to such distorted thoughts of his subordinates.

In fact, Fang Yuan did not know that Song Yi Shi was having complex emotions now, he was looking at his recent gains.

When Song Yi Shi cultivated, Fang Yuan had secretly used methods through the refinement path dao marks in poetic emotion sea area to help her out.

Fang Yuan gave it a simple try, the effort was as mild as breathing, but Song Yi Shi’s cultivation gains rose by at least ten percent.

“If I use my full effort, Song Yi Shi’s cultivation efficiency will rise by tens of times!”

“She is undergoing water path cultivation, because it is a passive defensive method, it has something to do with refinement path. If this were a genuine Gu refinement attempt, my influence would be even greater.”

“This means that I can use refinement path to help others refine Gu. At the same time, I can also ruin their attempts. Or at least, without my permission, nobody can refine an Immortal Gu in my refinement path dao mark domain!”

This was terrifying.

The power of a venerable was displayed at its fullest.

Fang Yuan was overjoyed but he also had a heavy mood.

If his refinement path could have such an influence, it meant that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would have the same influence in luck path and wisdom path.

“If I refine all the refinement path dao marks in the five regions and two heavens, while invigilating the world at all times, if any Gu Immortal tries to refine Immortal Gu, I will be able to ruin the attempt. In that case, can I make it such that only my faction can refine Immortal Gu?”

Fang Yuan thought of this problem.

But soon, he shook his head.

If Gu Immortals refined Gu in their own immortal apertures, Fang Yuan could not influence them.

Because immortal apertures were isolated worlds of their own.

But if a Gu Immortal refined Gu outside, Fang Yuan would be able to sense and influence it.

Putting aside the issue of Song Yi Shi, Fang Yuan placed his attention on a certain coral group deep in the sea.

These corals contained abundant refinement path Gu materials, they were a natural refinement path resource point of heaven and earth, they had very high value but had not been discovered by anyone.

Fang Yuan pondered and searched meticulously.

He used time path killer moves to observe the formation of this coral group.

Why did such a refinement path resource point form?

Thousands of years ago, there was nothing here.

But a sunken fish died here.

The refinement path and rule path dao marks of the sunken fish spread out and influenced the surroundings.

After a few hundred years, the sunken fish’s corpse decomposed entirely, while the environment also stabilized.

Initially, all sorts of fish and shrimps came here in groups. Afterwards, middle sized and large sized beasts also moved here.

The sea currents were turbulent, causing seeds and corals to be swept over.

After thousands of years of development and natural selection, due to lucky opportunities and evolution, this resource point was created now.

Fang Yuan’s focus was on the refinement path dao marks of the coral group.

For thousands of years, the refinement path dao marks here had been increasing and decreasing, being extremely unstable. Eventually, the group grew to this size.

“As long as I replicate the development of this refinement path resource point, with enough time, I can create such a refinement path resource point anywhere in the sovereign immortal aperture!”

Of course, there was an easier method, which was to directly create a refinement path formation and consume immortal materials to create an environment that was similar to this coral resource point.

But this method needed the formation to have some Immortal Gu, it also expended immortal essence.

Meanwhile, creating a refinement path resource point through a naturally developed dao mark distribution would not expend immortal essence or require Immortal Gu.

In truth, Fang Yuan had always been using the latter method for his development of the sovereign immortal aperture, by setting up immortal formations everywhere, he instantly created resource points. For example, the earth vein nodes and water vein nodes were all formations that he created.

These formations not only used Immortal Gu, there were also formations that used immortal resources as the core.

This was a quick method that needed very little time, but the cost was very high.

While natural development had low costs (no Immortal Gu was needed, while immortal materials were slowly accumulated naturally), but the time needed was too long.

“No matter which method it is, they have the same origin, they are all just killer moves.”

Immortal formations were killer moves, while naturally derived dao mark distribution was also a type of passive killer move. It was just that this killer move was not defensive but was used to develop an environment.

“Wait.” Fang Yuan thought of the killer moves divine concealment, ghostly concealment, and spaceless tunnel.

Divine concealment and ghostly concealment both created thick and dense clothing of dao marks on the soul, they were like tightly weaved silk clothing. They did not expend immortal essence and were passive defensive killer moves.

Additionally, spaceless tunnel was created by Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable as well, it was used in various places of the five regions and two heavens, shortening travel distance. This killer move from three hundred thousand years ago was still active now, but with the fusion of two heavens, it should have already been mostly destroyed.

“The essence of these killer moves has no difference from the coral resource point.”

Fang Yuan thought of fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu.

This Immortal Gu was a consumable Gu that could give the Gu Immortal immense luck to rival the heavens after use, no longer consuming immortal essence anymore.

What was the difference in essence between it and the coral resource point?

Fang Yuan then thought of the incomplete Refinement Sea.

This was the refinement path secluded domain of heaven and earth that Lang Ya land spirit wanted to create with all his effort!

“What is a secluded domain of heaven and earth? It is merely an agglomeration of dao marks of a specific path to form a certain special effect. Dang Hun Mountain produces guts Gu, while Qian Kun Crystal Wall can reflect everything that happens in this world.”

“Secluded domains of heaven and earth are the extreme form of resource points, they are also the other aspect of Gu worms and killer moves.”

“Thus, everything has the same point of origin?”

Chapter 2240: Refinement Main, Heaven Specialty

“Knowledge obtained from theory always feels shallow, one needs practice to understand it completely.” Fang Yuan muttered to himself.

Understanding that all things had the same point of origin was one matter, putting it into practice was another.

Fang Yuan completely comprehended the essence of killer moves like divine concealment and ghostly concealment, but he had done so through refinement path. Because of the limitation of theft path attainment level, he could not modify ghostly concealment yet.

He had the ability to create refinement path killer moves similar to divine concealment and ghostly concealment, although it would be a difficult process and the price to pay would be great.

During this period where the three venerables contested, if Fang Yuan invested a lot of his time and energy into creating a top tier refinement path killer move, it would be too risky.

The timing and opportunity did not allow Fang Yuan to do so.

However, the refinement path resource points of the five regions and two heavens had a lot of value to him as references.

After Fang Yuan simplified them and took out the true core, he would be able to modify them into mature passive killer moves that could be used to develop the immortal aperture.

Basically, these passive killer moves were very rare among killer moves, they had great value.

The most common ones were defensive methods.

Song Yi Shi’s pride came from this reason.

Duke Long only had one of such a move too, it was called nine dragons protection.

As far as Fang Yuan knew, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable created no more than five of such killer moves like divine concealment and ghostly concealment in his life.

The creation of a killer move starts with the use of multiple Gu worms by a predecessor to gain experience gradually. The Gu cultivation predecessors took reference to the innate abilities of the living beings in the five regions and two heavens to rapidly establish the foundation of killer moves.

Until today, the Gu cultivators had already hit the limit of this world.

For example, Duke Long created the dragonman race, Lang Ya land spirit created an artificial secluded domain, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable created soul beasts, he turned all sorts of soul path killer moves into dao marks that were carved onto soul beasts to grant them innate abilities.

All of these accomplishments showed that Gu cultivators had already rivaled the natural world, they were able to grasp the profundity of heaven and earth.

And Limitless Demon Venerable went one step further.

He made an arrangement in Crazed Demon Cave, breaking the world boundary to create a hole and even making brand new heaven path dao marks. He had surpassed the entire Gu cultivator world singlehandedly.

This was the first time Fang Yuan was refining the refinement path dao marks of the outside world.

With his supreme grandmaster attainment level and manual practice, Fang Yuan gained a lot of insight.

To conclude —

The five regions and two heavens had a vast number of refinement path dao marks, but they were not evenly distributed, some places were dense while others were sparse. These refinement path dao marks were very stable and hard to change, normally speaking, their growth was extremely slow and needed a lot of time to accumulate.

These refinement path dao marks could be seen as the basis of the entire world’s refinement path foundation.

On this foundation, a large number of beasts, plants, and lifeless Gu materials were produced and nurtured.

These beasts and plants were related to refinement path, they were refinement path resources.

Normally speaking, in places with dense refinement path dao marks, the relevant resources would also be more abundant and high quality. In places with sparse refinement path dao marks, there would be fewer refinement path resources and of lower quality.

The refinement path dao marks and resources had a deep influence on each other. For example, the coral group that Fang Yuan saw earlier was a refinement path resource point, the source was an immemorial sunken fish that died thousands of years ago, its refinement path dao marks scattered in the surroundings and a portion was left behind in that location.

The dao marks that Fang Yuan refined here were the refinement path foundation of the world.

Refinement path resources were not included in this.

The natural dao marks that Fang Yuan refined were like a huge spider web. As long as Fang Yuan was in range, he would be able to sense all refinement path activities within the web.

This was the so-called refinement path sensation.

Fang Yuan had a vague sensation of the refinement path resources, he could also sense the refinement path activities of Gu cultivators.

In places with dense refinement path dao marks, the sensation would be more intense, stable, and clearer. For example, he would be able to find small-scale ordinary refinement path Gu materials.

Conversely, if the refinement path dao marks were sparse, the refinement path sensation would be weaker. In those regions, Fang Yuan would only be able to sense refinement path immortal materials.

If there was a hole in the spider web, or if a Gu Immortal refined Gu in their immortal aperture, Fang Yuan would not sense anything.

Using the refinement path dao marks that he refined, Fang Yuan could influence everything in that range, he could interfere with the living beings as well as the natural environment.

For example, he could help Song Yi Shi cultivate, strengthen refinement path resource points like the coral group, or even create a top tier refinement path passive killer move (like spaceless tunnel) that could exist indefinitely.

Simply using refinement path dao marks to amplify his own strength was only the most basic use.

“From the angle of refinement path, in the entire Gu cultivation world, the five regions and two heavens are just a giant immortal material. This immortal material comprises everything, it has dao marks of all paths.”

“Even though I became a refinement path venerable, I can only refine a portion of this huge immortal material. This is true for Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, and all other venerables.”

“Owning a portion of heaven and earth, this is what a Dao Lord entails!”

“The other venerables are only able to become the Lord of one Dao, but I am different.”

Fang Yuan’s sovereign immortal body had non-conflicting dao marks, he cultivated all paths. The other venerables could do one main path and one specialty path at best, their main path would become their venerable path, while their specialty path would be used to fight and compete.

In theory, Fang Yuan could cultivate all the paths and become a venerable of all paths!

This was the intention of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable when he spent all his effort to refine sovereign immortal fetus Gu.

Fang Yuan had incomparable potential, the limit of his growth was unimaginable.

“The other venerables also know this, the only reason why they did not kill me is because I displayed incredible battle strength in Crazed Demon Cave, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable knew that the price to kill me was too great, they could not take the backlash.”

Fang Yuan did not continue to refine dao marks.

He decided to stop for now.

Even though Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus had bloomed again in the sovereign immortal aperture and gave him nearly a hundred immortal essence beads again.

Even though he had all sorts of refinement path methods to raise his refinement efficiency by many times, far surpassing the venerables.

This was obvious.

Refinement path most excelled in this aspect.

In terms of refinement path, he far surpassed the other two venerables, this was the advantage of refinement path to begin with.

“However, I cannot display my advantage now, it will overly agitate those venerables.” Fang Yuan thought to himself.

Once he used his advantage, the two venerables would move.

Although they felt that they had some advantage, if they saw that Fang Yuan’s dao mark refinement speed was so fast, they would not sit still, they would have to come and stop him.

Fang Yuan was not afraid of getting attacked by them.

After all, he had enough immortal essence reserves now, although the quantity was not high, the two venerables could not kill him in a short time, as they fought, Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus would gradually accumulate an advantage for Fang Yuan.

But there was no point in going this far!

Most importantly, it would cause Fang Yuan’s secret to be exposed, the existence of obscured heavenly secret, the loss was not worth the gain.

Blindly using one’s advantage was the biggest trap in life.

Fang Yuan knew deeply that assessing the situation was most important.

“Next, I need to refine dao marks with a slower speed, my efficiency should be around the same level as the two venerables, but I need to stop multiple times to pretend that I am out of immortal essence. Of course, I cannot be overly weak, otherwise, they will want to work together to get rid of me.”

Fang Yuan had a good grasp of this situation, he knew what to do.

He had abundant life experience after all.

Especially in the five hundred years of his previous life, all sorts of failure, pain, and losses became the valuable foundation that supported him.

“Keeping a low profile while profiting greatly! By the time I expose this secret, I am sure the two venerables will not be able to keep their cool.”

Fang Yuan activated Cooking Luck Pot to inspect his luck again.

His luck still resembled a furnace.

Fang Yuan had inspected this many times already, he had some guesses about it.

This was caused by his status as a refinement path venerable, his luck’s appearance was stabilized and would not change for a period of time.

The furnace was still quite crude, it had cracks remaining.

But from the vast number of cracks, two or three of them had mended.

This was because the sovereign immortal aperture had already completed the first earth vein, the second one was on the way. It had also completed the first water vein.

These were all helping to stabilize his foundation.

And compared to the past, there was a huge change on the surface of the furnace, there was a lotus flower pattern.

The lotus flower pattern was clearly referring to rank nine Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus. It showed how significant this Immortal Gu was to Fang Yuan!

The lotus flower pattern went one round around the outer layer of the furnace, it extended to the bottom and turned into several lotus roots.

These lotus roots went deep into the bottom of the furnace and burned together with the firewood that represented immortal essence.

Compared to the weak fire earlier, the furnace was fully lit now, the flames expanded by several times, showing great growth.

There was no lid on the furnace, the scene inside could be seen.

The immortal crane cloud that symbolized heaven form and the green lotus cloud that was Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus were both gone now.

Instead, there was a piece of blue-white ice, symbolizing the truthful floating ice. The blue-white ice was heated in the furnace, slowly melting and generating a beautiful halo.

At the top of the furnace, there was a large amount of reddish brown sand dust, floating like a cloud.

The reddish brown sand dust condensed into one lump and slowly went into the furnace.

It was easily melted and infused into the furnace, fixing the cracks and slowly making the furnace smoother from its crude state.

“This should be referencing my action of refining natural dao marks. If I go all out on this, the sand dust will pour down rapidly and block my opening of my furnace, it can even put out the fire at the bottom. Excessive progress is not good, this shows the terrible outcome of facing two venerables’ suppression at the same time.”

Fang Yuan had used luck inspection many times, he was able to reference the phenomena he saw to actual events that were happening more easily.

Even though rank eight Cooking Luck Pot was too low in rank and did not suit the current Fang Yuan, it still displayed the profundity of luck path, reminding Fang Yuan that the most important variables to him now were refining dao marks and also heaven path development!

“The refinement of dao marks can progress slowly, but I also need to unseal the truthful floating ice in secret. Right now, immortal essence is not my burden, it is my advantage instead. I need to use all my immortal essence and convert my resources into foundation and strength.”

Venerables all had one main and one specialty path.

Fang Yuan had planned from long ago to use refinement path as his main, and heaven path as his specialty.

Refinement path was his main cultivation, but refinement path itself was weak in the fighting aspect.

This was a publicly known fact.

In this situation, Fang Yuan needed another path to support his battle strength. This path should have few cultivators, for example, painting path. That would allow him to catch enemies off-guard and prevent them from having precaution against him.

Even though there were many paths in existence, Fang Yuan did not have many choices, looking at his situation, heaven path was the best choice!

There were almost no heaven path cultivators, the criteria was too hard to achieve.

Heaven path itself was very special and had extraordinary potential, its might was also unrivaled.

Refinement path as main, heaven path as specialty.

This was Fang Yuan’s current cultivation plan.

The Heaven Refining Demon Venerable title that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable gave to Fang Yuan was truly appropriate.

Chapter 2241: Too Beautiful

“We pay respects to Lord Alliance Leader.” A group of mermaid Gu Immortals showed a respectful attitude as they bowed before Fang Yuan’s feet.

Fang Yuan looked around and was a little surprised.

He found that all these merman Gu Immortals were female, they were either seductive, innocent, or cold. The two strongest ones had rank seven cultivation level, the other four were rank six.

“All female immortals...” Fang Yuan thought.

This was not good.

He let these mermen enter the sovereign immortal aperture in order to procreate and develop in numbers. Without male merman Gu Immortals and a total of six female immortals, they could not grow properly.

However, Fang Yuan recalled that in merman society, females had higher status than males. They would elect a saintess but not a saint.

In addition, the Merman Imperial Court sent these female immortals without any males as a form of reverence towards Fang Yuan as well.

“You are all members of the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance, after entering the sovereign immortal aperture, we will be one big family. Remember the rules and abide by them, you will be informed of the details later.”

Saying this, Fang Yuan opened his immortal aperture’s entrance.

“We will obey alliance leader’s teachings!” The female immortals quickly responded before entering obediently.

At the next moment, their vision changed completely, they found that they were in the vast sky, below them was cloud soil and a city was far away, it resembled a huge sea snail that radiated with starlight specks.

“Did you raise your head earlier?”

“No, I’ve never been so close to Lord Alliance Leader, I lowered my head the entire time.”

“I mustered my courage and took a peek at him before entering the immortal aperture, oh goodness, Lord Alliance Leader is simply... too beautiful!”

“Lord Alliance Leader has venerable cultivation level, he also takes care of us variant humans, and most strikingly, he is so beautiful. I’ve never seen such a beautiful and gentle higher-up before.”

These two rank six mermaid Gu Immortals were quite close, they spoke with excitement and expressed their reverence and adoration towards Fang Yuan.

As for the other two rank six female immortals, they had solemn expressions and did not speak.

“Silence.” One of the two mermaid leaders said unhappily: “Is Lord Alliance Leader someone you can talk about so casually? We are inside the sovereign immortal aperture now!”

The female immortals lowered their heads and stopped speaking, but they communicated with their expressions, unable to conceal their excitement.

The other leader, Lian Ke Xin, stretched out her hand and grasped Yu Zi’s hand, consoling her.

Lian Ke Xin, Yu Zi, and Xie Ning Si were the three leaders of the Merman Imperial Court, this time, when Fang Yuan decided to move some of them into the sovereign immortal aperture, how could the Merman Imperial Court refuse?

After receiving the orders, the Merman Imperial Court held an emergency meeting for a day and night.

Eventually, the Merman Imperial Court chose two of their leaders and four mermaid immortals with outstanding beauty to offer to Fang Yuan. To do this, they broke up two couples, one of which was already close to getting married.

The Merman Imperial Court did not have any rank eights, their top battle strengths were the three leading first supreme elders with rank seven battle strength, by sending two away at the same time, it showed how resolute they were.

After that, they omitted the males and only chose the most beautiful female immortals, they were trying to get closer to Fang Yuan to curry his favor.

This was not strange.

Humanity was the undisputed overlord of the world, the Merman Imperial Court had already gotten used to such a subservient lifestyle after many years.

Back then, Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable took action to protect the Merman Imperial Court. After his death, his influence dwindled and the Merman Imperial Court started to have alliance marriages with Eastern Sea’s righteous path forces, they also liked to take in lone immortals of Eastern Sea through marriage.

The Merman Imperial Court was used to such treatment.

Because of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable, they were accepted by Eastern Sea’s human forces. Now that Fang Yuan was venerable and took control of Eastern Sea, the Merman Imperial Court was unlike other human forces, they could not join Giant Sun Immortal Venerable or Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, they could only choose Great Love Immortal Venerable, who was closer to variant humans.

Thus, even though the two female immortals bore grudges after getting separated from their partners, for the sake of their people, they still chose to sacrifice their own happiness!

But earlier, when they met with Fang Yuan, they suffered a huge blow.

The mermaid immortals knew about Fang Yuan’s appearance, be it Heavenly Court or other forces, they had shown videos of him. The female immortals knew about Fang Yuan’s beautiful appearance, but after meeting it, they were still shocked by his peerless features!

This was not just external beauty, there was also the fact that he contained abundant dao marks, each of his actions had the aura of the Great Dao, he emitted extraordinary charm from his entire body, his incomparable capacity and aura subdued everyone that he met.

Even Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, despite having many dao marks, would not be as charming to merfolk.

Because mermen were born with water path dao marks, while Fang Yuan had over two million of them, this brought them closer naturally.

Yu Zi was one of the leaders this time, she was the one who most advocated to contribute everything and use beauty to get closer to Fang Yuan.

However, after seeing Fang Yuan, she was deeply shocked, she felt that she was mud when compared to the pure cloud-like Fang Yuan, she felt ashamed of herself.

Lian Ke Xin and Yu Zi were very close, along with her personal experiences, she understood why Yu Zi was feeling this way.

She grabbed Yu Zi’s hand and secretly transmitted: “No matter how beautiful Lord Fang Yuan is, he is still a man. As long as this fact remains, we have hope. Think of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.”

Yu Zi nodded and slowly regained her calm.

At this time, a hairy man Gu Immortal flew over.

“I am Twelfth Hair, I have come to receive you.” Twelfth Hair spoke.

Yu Zi quickly smiled, after a short conversation with Twelfth Hair, she cast a glance at Tang Qiong.

Tang Qiong was a supreme elder of the Merman Imperial Court, she had yellow scales and was gentle and beautiful, her smile showed dimples that amplified her cuteness. Even though her status was lower than Yu Zi, Lian Ke Xin, and Xie Ning Si, she was only below these three. She was given great authority by the three of them, she spent her time on managing the political affairs, she had outstanding interpersonal skills.

After getting Yu Zi’s approval, Tang Qiong went up and handed Twelfth Hair a seashell.

Twelfth Hair saw that this shell was a rare rank seven refinement path immortal material, he took it with a smile and showed a warmer attitude: “Everyone, please come with me. Your first stop will be Star Collection City, this is the central control area of the sovereign immortal aperture.”

Star Collection City was not on a huge piece of cloud soil, after flying for some time, they quickly entered it.

Under Twelfth Hair’s guide, the mermaid Gu Immortals went into the main hall and greeted the person in charge.

The Gu Immortal in charge of this main hall was a woman who cultivated sound path, her rank eight aura spread throughout the hall.

She was wearing a pink dress, her eye sockets were deeper than normal, her nose had a tall bridge, she also had a pair of seductive and moving eyes, it was Fairy Miao Yin.

The mermaids quickly greeted her.

Fairy Miao Yin sat at the top seat and looked down at these Gu Immortals, she spoke with a solemn expression: “You have just arrived here, you need to learn about the rules of our sovereign immortal aperture and obey them forever. The sovereign immortal aperture does not raise useless people, no matter who you are, you need to work hard to gain anything. The contribution board has a clear list of tasks that you can do, the worst thing you can do is slack off. Do you understand?”

“Yes, we will remember Lady Miao Yin’s teachings.” The mermaids responded.

Fairy Miao Yin nodded before casting her gaze at Twelfth Hair: “Since you took the mission to lead the mermaid Gu Immortals, you will bring them around and get familiar with Star Collection City’s arrangements.”

Saying this, Fairy Miao Yin waved her hand, dozens of Gu worms flew out.

Twelfth Hair acknowledged and took these Gu worms, he said to the female immortals: “Follow me.”

The mermaid immortals took their leave and followed Twelfth Hair, they all let out a sigh of relief.

“This Fairy Miao Yin was originally a rank seven Gu Immortal in Southern Border, but after following Great Love Immortal Venerable, she became a rank eight.”

“She spoke in such a tone, I’m afraid she knows our intention, so she wants to suppress us.”

Lian Ke Xin and Yu Zi transmitted to each other.

On the other hand, Tang Qiong carefully asked Twelfth Hair about Fairy Miao Yin’s status, was she the Star Collection City Lord?

Before coming, the Merman Imperial Court made ample preparation. They had prepared gifts for Fang Yuan’s well known subordinates like Fairy Miao Yin and Lady White Rabbit, but because of the tense atmosphere earlier, Tang Qiong could not offer the gift.

Twelfth Hair shook his head: “Originally, the Star Collection City Lord was the noble Combat Beast King, but he died during the tribulation. Now, Miao Yin, White Rabbit, Wu Shuai, Qi Sea, and the other rank eights are taking turns to station in Star Collection City.”

After hearing this, the mermaid Gu Immortals let out sighs of relief again.

This Fairy Miao Yin was not the Star Collection City Lord, she did not have too much authority.

Yu Zi’s eyes brightened, she knew that the chance to meet Fang Yuan’s main body was too rare, but his clones were inside the sovereign immortal aperture, if she could get close to one of them, the goal would be achieved.

The mermaid immortals followed Twelfth Hair and arrived at Star Collection City’s central square.

In the square, there were three huge pillars.

There were countless words moving around the surface of the pillars, they made up three large boards.

Before the mermaid Gu Immortals looked at them closely, Twelfth Hair already handed out Gu worms.

These were the Gu worms that Fairy Miao Yin gave to Twelfth Hair earlier. Each of the mermaid Gu Immortals obtained five of them, they were rank five mortal Gu.

Three of the Gu worms were familiar to the mermaids, they knew that these were used for the contribution board, mission board, and exchange board respectfully.

Fang Yuan listed three boards, they did not just exist in the sovereign immortal aperture, be it the variant human alliance or Righteous Qi Alliance, there were such arrangements. Thus, the mermaid immortals knew them.

Twelfth Hair spoke: “You will live in the sovereign immortal aperture from now on, your lives will be quite different. From now on, unless master gives orders, you will not go outside. You can take a look at these three boards, these are our internal boards, the external boards in the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance are quite different from them.”

Right now, be it the Righteous Qi Alliance or variant human alliance, they had all joined the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance.

These were two conflicting forces, but now, they were one force.

Everyone felt very complex emotions.

But under Fang Yuan’s venerable cultivation level, regardless of their willingness, they had to follow him!

Chapter 2242: Sovereign’s Three Boards

Star Collection City Square.

Yu Zi and Lian Ke Xin looked at a contribution board at the same time.

This contribution board had a lot of reference material, whoever stood at the top would be the most important subordinates, Fang Yuan’s capable generals, they were targets that the mermaid immortals had to befriend.

Looking at the contribution board, they could also roughly see the power levels of the factions of Fang Yuan’s subordinates and gain more insight.

Thereafter, they saw the number one name on the contribution board — Sixth Hair!

“A hairy man?”

“This person’s contribution points are far above the second person. For the time being, nobody can catch up to him.”

Even though Yu Zi and Lian Ke Xin had just arrived, they could see that Sixth Hair’s foundation and accumulation were immensely deep.

“Starting from the second place, the difference in points is not huge anymore.”

Lian Ke Xin quickly saw some familiar names from the top ten contributors.

Like Fairy Miao Yin, Lady White Rabbit, Mo Tan Sang, Xue Er, Shi Shi Cheng, and others.

What made Yu Zi and Lian Ke Xin take notice was that there was a strange name in the top ten positions.

“Lang Ya land spirit? Is this Lang Ya blessed land’s land spirit?”

“A land spirit can be ranked on the contribution board as well?”

“This shows how magnanimous Lord Fang Yuan is, he treats humans, variant humans, and land spirits equally.”

The top ten members of the contribution board were mostly variant human Gu Immortals. This had deep political meaning, the two former rulers of the Merman Imperial Court were very pleased about this, they felt a sense of excitement.

They also saw Twelfth Hair’s contribution points soon, he was eighteenth place.

The nineteenth place was the black hound land spirit.

At the next moment, the nineteenth place black hound land spirit took over the position of Twelfth Hair and knocked him down.

Twelfth Hair noticed this too, he coughed in embarrassment and said with a tone of slight envy: “This black hound land spirit is really lucky. Right now, with the fusion of two heavens, remnant heavenly dogs and heaven swallowing hounds are escaping in groups, they have been constantly caught by Gu Immortals and brought into our sovereign immortal aperture. Currently, these hound groups are taken care of by the black hound land spirit, after they are healed and inspected, they will be released into Mini White Heaven. This is why the black hound land spirit is getting so many contribution points.”

Lian Ke Xin and Yu Zi nodded repeatedly, while thinking to themselves: “Actually, there is no need to explain this. We don’t really care about how a land spirit beat you in contribution.”

They were concerned about Fairy Miao Yin, Lady White Rabbit, and the most important person — snowman Gu Immortal Xue Er.

The reason was that Bing Yuan had been bragging in the variant human alliance whenever she could that Xue Er was Fang Yuan’s fiancée, this was widely spread news.

As their former enemy, the Righteous Qi Alliance had been collecting such information, they also paid huge attention to this.

Thus, the mermaid immortals learned of this.

However, when they were about to ask for the information of these crucial people, a wave of screams could be heard near them.

Yu Zi frowned and was about to scold them, but she heard the four mermaid immortals say together: “Leaders, look at the exchange board.”

Lian Ke Xin and Yu Zi could not help but turn their attention away, immediately, their pupils contracted as they revealed expressions of shock.

The exchange board of the sovereign immortal aperture was truly different from the one in Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance.

There were too many good things!

Lian Ke Xin and Yu Zi were getting dizzy from browsing the list.

There were all sorts of rewards listed, Gu worms of all paths were available, there were lots of rare and extinct mortal Gu, there were over a thousand Immortal Gu available from rank six to eight. There were countless Immortal Gu recipes, immortal materials, and immortal killer moves. There were hundreds or thousands of Immortal Gu House construction methods, and the immortal inheritances even made Yu Zi and Lian Ke Xin stare with wide eyes.

“This is water path great expert Chang Guan Shui’s inheritance, he cultivated water path mainly with information path on the side. He has a killer move called one watery chapter[1], it is extremely famous in history!”

“This is the inheritance of our merfolk expert, Third Princess, she was the most powerful mermaid of the Remote Antiquity Era, she had resisted Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable on many occasions, she created the water path rank eight immortal material, too much water, it has already gone extinct, to think that we would see it here.”

Yu Zi’s and Lian Ke Xin’s hearts palpitated as they read on.

Fang Yuan promoted himself as Great Love Immortal Venerable, he started to do transactions of Gu refinement in treasure yellow heaven, all of the mermaid immortals knew of the prices he set.

Although the prices were fair, they were incomparable to this.

“Using contribution points to exchange for things we want, this is much easier than making transactions in treasure yellow heaven or exchanging with the external board.”

“What did I see? We can apply for Lord Fang Yuan to personally help us pass tribulations! He is truly Great Love Immortal Venerable!”

Lian Ke Xin and Yu Zi licked their lips uncontrollably, their desire towards contribution points rose to an unprecedented level.

They cast their heated gazes towards the mission board along with the other four female immortals.

Evidently, if one wanted to get cultivation resources from the exchange board, they would need contribution points, while the source of contribution points were missions.

There were many missions on the mission board.

Within Mini Purple Heaven, a large number of ancient desolate beast mixed heavenly eagles had turned into immemorial desolate beasts for some reason, the mission was to investigate the truth.

Dog shit was falling from the sky in Mini Northern Plains, piling into mountains and polluting the frost dragon’s lake, the mission was to investigate the cause of the dog shit and get rid of it.

The dragon scale sea area in Mini Eastern Sea was flowing in reverse, a lot of seawater had entered the mini nine heavens, the mission was to fix the immortal formation and rebuild dragon scale sea area.

Inkman City Lord Mo Tan Sang got pregnant inexplicably, an expert in abortion was needed now.

...

The mermaid immortals looked at the mission board and fell into temporary silence.

The quantity of these missions was out of their expectations.

In normal situations, the immortal apertures of Gu Immortals were calm and peaceful, they only had to rebuild areas after going through tribulations or when they had new resource points added. They were not like the sovereign immortal aperture, which had strange events occurring at every moment.

The mermaid immortals looked for a while, they felt worried but also happy.

The worry was that even though the sovereign immortal aperture was Great Love Immortal Venerable’s immortal aperture and was renowned in the world, it was not peaceful at all, there were chaos everywhere, it would not be easy to live in here.

But they were happy because the chaos meant an uncountable number of missions, they had no lack of contribution points to earn.

Twelfth Hair had been observing the mermaid immortals’ expressions, he sighed: “I’ll speak the truth, the sovereign immortal aperture is currently in a state of peace. You have not seen the situation when master annexed the two heavens’ grotto-heavens, when he gained a huge number of dao marks, strange phenomena occurred endlessly. Inside the sovereign immortal aperture, there was not a single idle person at that time.”

“Currently, even though there aren’t many situations occurring, after the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, we lost many Gu Immortals, although most of them revived, they cannot ascend to immortal yet. You can see for yourselves, there are many many missions now, but some areas need people to guard them. For example, Star Collection City is too important, we cannot lose it. In addition, with many strange situations occurring, we need at least one rank eight Gu Immortal guarding the aperture at all times, because there are too many missions, master brought all of you into the sovereign immortal aperture to help out.”

“Earlier in the hall, Fairy Miao Yin spoke bluntly but she was not wrong. If you want to gain the acknowledgement of the existing Gu Immortals, you need to work hard and make achievements, use your actions and contribution points to prove your loyalty to master!”

The mermaid immortals heard his words and nodded.

Lian Ke Xin and Yu Zi looked at each other, they had finally understood Fang Yuan’s intention.

Tang Qiong quickly expressed gratitude to Twelfth Hair and handed over a gift again.

The other mermaid immortals asked at this time: “Lord Twelfth Hair, you gave us five Gu worms each, three are used for the boards, what about the last two?”

Twelfth Hair received the gift while smiling and explaining: “One of them is used to connect to treasure yellow heaven. Within the sovereign immortal aperture, all Gu cultivators need to use this Gu worm to access treasure yellow heaven. The other one is used to monitor you, it has to be kept on you at all times. If it is destroyed, you need to report it immediately, we will hand out a replacement in Star Collection City.”

After pausing for a while, Twelfth Hair continued: “No need to think too much about it, not just all of you, we have it too. It might be a mortal Gu but it has saved many of our lives already. We face danger when we handle those strange phenomena, it is possible that we will die during the missions.”

“For example, look at this mission on the board.”

The mermaid immortals looked at where Twelfth Hair pointed and saw the Mo Tan Sang abortion mission.

Twelfth Hair showed a strange smile: “You might not be familiar with Mo Tan Sang, but his status is not low, he is the Gu Immortal leader of Mini Western Desert. He is a male inkman, but while handling a sudden situation, he got mysteriously pregnant. Now, he is offering a huge price to undergo an abortion, many people are interested but were unable to do anything about it. If the abortion fails, he might lose his life after all!”

The mermaid immortals opened their mouths, they were dumbstruck.

“Alright,” Twelfth Hair continued: “Follow me, I will bring you to a place. In a way, this place is more important than the three boards!”

The mermaid immortals immediately gained deep interest, they followed Twelfth Hair as they left the square and arrived at a sub-hall of Star Collection City.

They saw that there were many Gu Immortals at the sub-hall.

Many Gu Immortals were holding onto each other, some were bending their backs as they dragged themselves into the sub-hall while looking extremely enervated.

Afterwards, these Gu Immortal walked out of the hall with a revitalized appearance, they looked highly spirited.

Even though there were still deep eye bags on their faces.

These Gu Immortals would nod sincerely when they saw acquaintances, when they went past each other, they would greet each other and talk about their missions or ranking on the contribution board.

When these Gu Immortals saw the mermaid Gu Immortals, they showed expressions of understanding.

A few of them took the initiative to greet the mermaids, they were very welcoming.

“Oh, I’ve heard that we are bringing in a group of merman Gu Immortals, are they the ones?”

“Great, with them joining us, we can finally take a breather.”

“There are more and more missions now, I hope this can reduce our workload.”

“Twelfth Hair, you are so lucky to have taken the mission of bringing them in!”

[1] Author is making a joke here. The character’s name means adding water, while water is slang for filler in Chinese, therefore a watery a filler chapter.

Chapter 2243: Gu Yue Fang Xiang

Twelfth Hair laughed heartily as he said some pleasantries.

Looking back at the mermaid immortals, he saw that they were in a daze, some of the Gu Immortals even had tears in their eyes.

Twelfth Hair was startled, he quickly said: “If I have done anything wrong...”

Before he finished, Lian Ke Xin interrupted him: “Twelfth Hair, don’t worry. It is just that we saw everyone being harmonious and tolerant in this sovereign immortal aperture, each individual is given a chance with equal opportunities, they are close and tightly knit together, regardless of whether they are an inkman, rockman, snowman, or even human.”

“To speak the truth, I have never seen anything like this. I did not even dare to imagine that such a place would exist in this world we live in!”

Twelfth Hair was silent.

He was originally a member of Lang Ya Sect, even though Lang Ya blessed land was well hidden, he was aware of the situation in the five regions and two heavens, the variant humans had low statuses, they were suppressed by the humans and were all living difficult lives.

Looking at it from the perspective of the Eastern Sea Merman Imperial Court, they had been surrounded by human forces and definitely faced much greater pressure than Lang Ya Sect’s hairy men.

Even though the sight in Star Collection City was simple and normal, it created a huge impact on the mermaid immortals.

For an instant, all of the mermaid immortals had a similar thought.

No matter how chaotic or dangerous the sovereign immortal aperture’s environment became, they had to continue living here!

“Maybe this is our true homeland!” Yu Zi muttered.

“This is a wonderful place to live in.” Lian Ke Xin sighed deeply.

“I finally understand the true meaning of Great Love. Master is truly worthy of being Great Love Immortal Venerable, he is unlike the detestable Longevity Heaven or Heavenly Court. Be it Star Constellation Immortal Venerable or Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, they cannot compare to our master!” A mermaid immortal spoke about Fang Yuan in an extremely reverent tone.

Twelfth Hair gave a thumbs up as he said proudly: “Even among all the venerables, master has the biggest heart! It was only natural that Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable thought highly of him and gave all of his inheritance to master. Nobody else is qualified to receive this. We can only obtain true happiness by following master’s footsteps, since you recognize this now, then work hard to defend our home from now on, this is the way to maintain our blissful life.”

The mermaid immortals nodded their heads, some were so moved they started crying.

After calming down, Tang Qiong asked: “I wonder what the profound use of this sub-hall is?”

Twelfth Hair gasped, he showed a complex expression.

There was pride and admiration in his eyes, one could even see excitement and thrill, but he also had some lingering fear.

Even Twelfth Hair’s hair could not conceal his expression.

This made the mermaid immortals even more curious.

Next, the female immortals heard the explanation: “This was once a formation called the liver life formation. But recently, master modified it into an Immortal Gu House.”

“It has an excellent effect, it is very useful!” Saying so, Twelfth Hair gave a thumbs up again.

He said to the mermaid immortals with a tone that contained deep meaning:” You will definitely make good use of it in the future!”

After hearing Twelfth Hair’s in-depth description, the Liver Life Immortal Gu House left a deep impression on the mermaid immortals.

There was nothing else to introduce in Star Collection City, Twelfth Hair brought these mermaid immortals out of the mini nine heavens.

The group came to Mini Eastern Sea and looked at the sea area below.

Tides were rising, a sea breeze was blowing.

Twelfth Hair explained: “This is the location that master has chosen for your merman race to live and grow from now on.”

The mermaid Gu Immortals quickly used their investigative methods to inspect this sea area’s environment.

The unexpected good news was that this sea area has a vast quantity of ordinary Gu materials, but they were scattered chaotically with no order at all. Furthermore, many of the Gu materials conflicted with each other, they were in the process of breaking down.

This situation was caused by the sovereign immortal aperture’s dao marks.

The sovereign immortal aperture had many dao marks, that naturally led to the creation of many Gu materials. Because of non-conflicting dao marks, strange situations occurred often and the Gu materials were distributed chaotically and ended up in an unstable state.

“This is the map of the five regions and nine heavens, it is a version from three days ago, I will gift this to you.” Twelfth Hair pointed as an information path mortal Gu flew out.

“Version from three days ago?” Yu Zi was very alert.

“Indeed.” Twelfth Hair nodded and explained: “Because strange situations are occurring all the time, terrain will also change along with them. And because master is constantly adding in resource points and annexing blessed lands and grotto-heavens, the map of the five regions and nine heavens has been changing all the time, it needs to be updated constantly.”

Yu Zi looked into the Gu and shouted in shock: “So big?!”

Her shouting attracted the attention of the mermaid immortals, they had rarely seen Yu Zi, a leading elder, act in such a manner.

Twelfth Hair said with a trace of pride in his tone, he laughed: “The sovereign immortal aperture was originally over 335,000km2 in size. Now, after master’s annexing of apertures and undergoing tribulations, the size has expanded by a hundred times, we are over 33,500,000km2 in size now!”

When the other female immortals heard this news, they became dumbstruck and went into a daze.

Twelfth Hair smiled again: “Don’t worry, this place will continue to get bigger. If one day, the sovereign immortal aperture surpasses the five regions and two heavens in size, we will not be surprised!”

“I have already marked your territory on this map.”

“My mission has been completed, but if you have any needs, feel free to contact me using this information path mortal Gu.”

“I am currently living on Yellow Hair Continent, I am in charge of leading the yellow hair hairy men, you and I can be considered neighbors.”

Lian Ke Xin and Yu Zi quickly expressed their gratitude, they took out their own information path mortal Gu that were used for communication and exchanged them with Twelfth Hair.

After Twelfth Hair said his goodbyes to the mermaid immortals, he vanished into the sky.

After Lian Ke Xin and Yu Zi discussed among themselves, the six mermaid immortals started to get busy.

They sent people to scout and probe the surroundings, including the sky and sea, to collate the resources. On the other hand, the Gu Immortals also created a super sized defensive Gu formation.

After the two tasks were completed, the mermaid immortals opened their immortal aperture’s entrances.

Groups of mermen went into this sea area along with their families.

Under the instructions of the female merman Gu Immortals, these eight hundred thousand mermen started to build houses, create underwater villages, towns, and even cities at the center.

The mermaid immortals created six cities, each one had a Gu Immortal to guard it.

The cities were surrounded by towns which had branched out villages.

Because they made ample preparation, the merfolk did not lack living resources.

Chaos was, of course, unavoidable, they had just arrived here after all.

But with the guidance and control of the mermaid immortals, no losses appeared.

They worked hard for nine days and nights, after the merfolk mortals settled down, Yu Zi and Lian Ke Xin gathered the immortals for a meeting.

“There are many ordinary Gu materials but each one has low quantity, they change a lot as well. In my opinion, we should organize groups of merman Gu Masters to collect these Gu materials at set intervals of time.”

“The environment is quite safe here, there are few desolate beasts and almost no ancient desolate beasts.”

“There are also no common food like kelp, fish, or shrimp, we need to raise them from scratch. We also need to create a stable ecology.”

“There are few immortal materials here. According to the map, the closest immortal material resource point is the seven treasures sea spring, it produces seven treasures water.”

“Don’t target resource points, this is the sovereign immortal aperture, all resource points belong to master. If we want to get resources, we have to complete missions and exchange for them using contribution points.”

Speaking of missions, these mermaid immortals had been researching hard on the missions.

“Twelfth Hair is right, I think that we need to focus on completing missions to prove our worth. That way, the other Gu Immortals will acknowledge us.”

“I checked clearly, the most suitable missions for us are the ones to build water path resource points. Master has grand and magnificent ambitions, he is establishing water veins now. The first water vein has already been completed, he is making the second one now, this is our chance.”

“You are right, but we cannot give up on other missions. Especially the ones that involve other Gu Immortals, I think we should take some of them and use the missions to get acquainted with and befriend the other Gu Immortals. Before coming here, we prepared a lot of gifts, they are still with us now.”

After the mermaid immortals talked about this, the decision was that Yu Zi would stay in this sea area and be in charge of creating the ecology, this would create a stable source of food for the mermen.

The four female immortals led by Lian Ke Xin went around the place to collect information while also establishing relationships with other factions.

Lian Ke Xin spent an entire day to arrive at Yellow Hair Continent.

Twelfth Hair received her information path mortal Gu’s notification already, he went to the sky to welcome her.

As the saying goes, better a close neighbor than a distant brother, the two parties were inclined to establish a healthy relationship.

Lian Ke Xin brought a gift with her again, these days, while researching the contribution board, she noticed that in the sovereign immortal aperture, the hairy men were undoubtedly the number one force!

Twelfth Hair also prepared a present, it was very valuable too.

After talking for a while, Twelfth Hair heard of the mermaid immortals’ actions and smiled at Lian Ke Xin: “You’ve done the right thing.”

“In the five regions and two heavens, Gu Immortals will visit each other and hold banquets, in the worst case, they will at least prepare tea. But in the sovereign immortal aperture, this never happens! How can we have the time to entertain anyone in these useless banquets?”

“It is very wise of you to use these missions to meet with other people. If you follow the customs of the five regions and two heavens, you will not be well received by everyone.”

After hearing these words, Lian Ke Xin felt glad internally, she understood the style of the sovereign immortal aperture’s Gu Immortals soon after.

Twelfth Hair said directly: “We both took a mission to nurture Gu Immortal seeds, let’s go. Time is pressing, let’s go to the most important one.”

Lian Ke Xin went with Twelfth Hair and they flew while concealing their traces, entering a forest in the mountain.

A hairy man Gu Master was getting chased, he was covered in wounds and ran in the forest hurriedly.

Sounds could be heard from behind him, slowly creeping closer.

Lian Ke Xin inspected and found that this hairy man Gu Master was actually a mixed blood of hairy man and human.

“His name is Gu Yue Fang Xiang.” Twelfth Hair introduced at this time.

Lian Ke Xin’s pupils contracted immediately, her entire body shuddered.

Twelfth Hair quickly raised his hand: “Don’t let your thoughts run wild! He is not master’s bloodline, he is the son of Gu Yue Fang Zheng. Hehe, master is truly farsighted, his vision is far beyond our understanding, he has been secretly nurturing this kid, creating opportunities and setbacks for him. He is currently the most qualified Gu Immortal seed among our hairy man Gu Masters!”

Chapter 2244: Sudden Love

“Huff, huff, huff...” Gu Yue Fang Xiang breathed roughly, he hid behind the roots of an ancient tree.

The huge ancient tree had giant roots protruding out of the ground, they were interwoven and created a secluded area.

Gu Yue Fang Xiang managed to temporarily get away from the pursuit, he gained some time to rest and recover.

He was still bleeding profusely from his mouth and nose, he hurriedly wiped away the traces on his lips as he started to inspect his own physical condition.

Gu Yue Fang Xiang’s expression turned dim, he found more than ten injuries on his body, he had three bone fractures and the most severe injuries were in his organs, he needed healing urgently.

But he was neither worried nor flustered.

This was not the first time he had gotten injuries of such severity.

Gu Yue Fang Xiang tore his upper shirt that was extremely tattered, it was easily removed, his chest that was covered in black hair was exposed.

There was a deep wound across his chest, broken white bones could be seen from within.

Gu Yue Fang Xiang gritted his teeth, activating his Gu worm.

The healing Gu worm resembled a centipede, it dived into his body through the wound, quickly stopping the internal bleeding.

After a while, the centipede was covered in blood and came out of Fang Xiang’s body, lying on his chest wound.

Its hundred pairs of legs stabbed into the skin of his wound, the intense pain made Gu Yue Fang Xiang suck in a sharp breath.

Next, the centipede slowly exerted force as its hundred pairs of legs dragged the skin and flesh, emitting a soft sound and forcing the wound to mend together.

But this handling of the injury only suppressed it, it could not solve the root cause, Gu Yue Fang Xiang knew that but there was no time for him to heal himself.

“I see blood traces!”

“Hurry, hurry.”

“Be careful, that kid is quite dangerous.”

“What’s there to fear, even if he has rank five cultivation level, after getting hit by our leader’s crippled refinement killer move, most of his Gu worms were destroyed.”

“Hehe, precisely because of such thinking, more than ten experts died at his hands already.”

“This mixed blood Gu Yue Fang Xiang is truly a monster!”

All these discussions made Gu Yue Fang Xiang’s expression change.

“Damn it! They arrived so quickly, I had just handled my wounds...” Gu Yue Fang Xiang clenched his teeth, he inspected the remaining few Gu worms in his aperture.

At this point, most of the Gu worms had been destroyed already.

The remaining ones were mostly injured, if he tried to activate them, they would be destroyed in the process.

These were all Gu worms that Gu Yue Fang Xiang had accumulated after much effort, but now, he had no choice but to sacrifice them!

“Oh sleep lurk Gu, I can only depend on you now. You must persevere!” Gu Yue Fang Xiang prayed as he activated the Gu worm to conceal himself.

This rank four Gu worm had outstanding concealment effects on par with rank five. Gu Yue Fang Xiang had used it many times in his life to escape from fierce threats.

But this Gu had a weakness, once activated, the Gu Master would fall into deep sleep. The deeper their sleep, the better the concealment effect.

Gu Yue Fang Xiang lost his sensation of the outside world as a result.

What he did not know was that after he fell asleep for some time, this sleep lurk Gu broke apart into pieces.

But the pursuers were still chasing him.

Seeing this, the lurking Twelfth Hair waved his hand, the immortal killer move was instantly used on Gu Yue Fang Xiang.

A yellow hair hairy man Gu Master that was chasing him combed the surroundings carefully while checking the tree roots that Gu Yue Fang Xiang was hiding in.

Even though he was right in front of Gu Yue Fang Xiang, he could not see the latter.

Eventually, he concluded that Gu Yue Fang Xiang had escaped from this mountain, so he went deeper into the mountain to pursue him.

After Gu Yue Fang Xiang woke up, he found that he was safe and let out a sigh of relief.

Looking in his aperture, he found that the sleep lurk Gu had already shattered into pieces, he felt glad and also lingering fear: “It seems that sleep lurk Gu lasted until the crucial moment, so I managed to get away from the pursuers. They have already gone to the next mountain, now is the time for me to escape.”

Gu Yue Fang Xiang was very happy, because his injuries had already stabilized, he quickly got up and left.

He hid in the deep bushes of the forest as he moved, carefully trying not to leave any traces behind as he escaped.

After half a day, the sky suddenly turned dim, a strange fog appeared in the mountain’s forest.

Gu Yue Fang Xiang arrived in a deep pool on the mountain, he inspected the surroundings and felt very satisfied, he decided to stay here for some time and recuperate.

“There is a good source of water here, wild beasts will definitely come here to drink water, be it water or beast flesh, they are both needed.”

“If I am lucky, I can even hunt and obtain some Gu materials to refine Gu worms, that will refill my stock of Gu worms!”

Gu Yue Fang Xiang was very experienced in living alone within the mountains and forests.

He was a mixed blood of human and hairy man, in the Black Hair Continent that was ruled by hairy men, he was greatly ostracized.

Even his birth mother, Steel Thread City Lord, did not like him.

In Gu Yue Fang Xiang’s childhood and adolescence, his greatest wish was to use all his effort to gain the acknowledgement of his mother.

However, because he was a mixed blood, his aptitude in Gu refinement was far inferior to hairy men. And the worst thing was that hairy men took pride in Gu refinement.

But the problem was that Gu Yue Fang Xiang also had his secret encounters, because of all sorts of situations, he coincidentally obtained some special cultivation methods.

He was hardworking and shocked people with his performance, gradually, his mother, Steel Thread City Lord, changed her opinion of him. She started to accept him from the depths of her heart.

But good times did not last long, Steel Thread City was attacked once and the entire city’s people were nearly wiped out, Steel Thread City Lord did her best and escaped with Gu Yue Fang Xiang in the end.

Before her death, Steel Thread City Lord told Gu Yue Fang Xiang of his identity: “Oh son, mother has let you down. Didn’t you always want to know about your father?”

“His name is Gu Yue Fang Zheng, he was once a human slave that I owned. But after he escaped, he became a renowned demonic path Gu Master expert.”

“You have a human name, it is called Gu Yue Fang Xiang. Go and find your father, tell him your name and everything that has happened in your life.”

“We have strong enemies that want to kill us, if you want to take revenge for me, you need to find your father first.”

Like that, the youngster Gu Yue Fang Xiang stepped on the journey to find his father.

He secretly went from Black Hair Continent to White Hair Continent, before moving to Yellow Hair Continent.

The journey was filled with lots of difficulties and danger, he faced constant challenges and trouble.

Even though Gu Yue Fang Zheng was no longer in the aperture, the stories of his experiences across the three continents were left behind as legendary tales.

Gu Yue Fang Xiang’s cultivation level slowly rose as his social experiences became richer, countless battles and escapes shaped his optimistic and determined nature, he believed that one day, he would definitely find his father!

Near the deep pool, Gu Yue Fang Xiang took a good rest for the night.

At the break of dawn, mountain mist became extremely dense, Gu Yue Fang Xiang showed a suspicious look as he went to the periphery of the deep pool.

He found that this deep pool was very strange.

The mist in the mountain originated from this pool.

Gu Yue Fang Xiang stayed here for half a day and a full night, but he did not find any traces of beasts that came here to drink water.

All sorts of phenomena gave him a familiar sensation. Whenever he had a fortuitous encounter, something like this would occur.

Gu Yue Fang Xiang had a rich adventurous spirit, after probing for some time, he went into the pool.

But out of his expectations, the pool was not ice-cold, the deeper he went, the warmer it got.

Gu Yue Fang Xiang got all the way to the depths of the pool, the water was as comfortable as hot springs.

“This is?” He found a piece of white jade in the deep pool.

The jade was nearly transparent, from the outside, he could easily see that there was a beauty sealed inside the jade.

“This is a mermaid?” Gu Yue Fang Xiang looked at the beauty’s face and his pupils expanded, he felt deeply moved: “So beautiful!!”

He had never seen such a beautiful woman.

Such beauty made his heart jump, he felt a sense of adoration emerging from his heart.

The mermaid that was ‘sealed’ in the white jade was Lian Ke Xin.

She transmitted her voice to Fang Xiang: “Interesting mixed blood kid, you are the one who woke me up?”

Gu Yue Fang Xiang wanted to scream as he opened his mouth, because he forgot that this was deep within the pool, water quickly gushed into his mouth.

He quickly shut his mouth, he showed a pathetic look.

Lian Ke Xin laughed out loud, Gu Yue Fang Xiang felt his entire body going numb from infatuation, he thought: “This mysterious mermaid has such a beautiful voice as well!”

Lian Ke Xin explained: “I am mermaid immortal Lian Ke Xin, after I calmed a disaster in the world, I got injured by accident and became sealed in this white jade. Young man, it is fate that we met, please give me a hand to break free from here.”

Gu Yue Fang Xiang was extremely shocked but he did not have a Gu worm that could transmit his voice, he cupped his fists and bowed deeply, he tried to use sign language in the water to express his words.

Lian Ke Xin smiled: “Don’t worry, this white jade cannot trap me, it is just that I need some time to break free. If you can refine the rank four earth refinement Gu and refine this white jade from the outside, it will save me a lot of effort.”

Gu Yue Fang Xiang nodded in succession.

Lian Ke Xin then gave him pointers and the Gu recipe of earth refinement Gu, she also instructed him to find the suitable Gu materials in the vicinity.

Gu Yue Fang Xiang went out of the pool and immediately got to work.

After spending three days, he finally refined the rank four earth refinement Gu on his first try.

“I was really lucky!” Gu Yue Fang Xiang felt glad internally, according to his regular performance, rank four Gu worms were not easy to refine, he was just a mixed blood after all.

“It seems that even heaven is helping me to save this fairy.” Gu Yue Fang Xiang sighed to himself.

Twelfth Hair, who was hiding himself to the side, shook his head, while unable to contain his laughter.

It was with his secret help that Gu Yue Fang Xiang could succeed in one try.

After obtaining earth refinement Gu, Gu Yue Fang Xiang did not rest, he went into the deep pool with a tired body and started to refine the white jade.

Lian Ke Xin successfully ‘escaped’, she smiled at Gu Yue Fang Xiang and showed a gaze of appreciation.

Gu Yue Fang Xiang’s face turned red, he quickly lowered his head.

In order to express her gratitude, Lian Ke Xin waved her hand and healed all of Gu Yue Fang Xiang’s injuries. Next, she gave him close to ten mortal Gu as his reward and even one inheritance.

Lian Ke Xin was about to leave, Gu Yue Fang Xiang asked in panic: “Fairy, fairy, will I be able to meet you again?”

Lian Ke Xin smiled: “Do you know the difference between immortal and mortal?”

Gu Yue Fang Xiang shook intensely, his face turned ashen and pale.

But Lian Ke Xin added: “The inheritance I gave you is an immortal cultivation method. If you can become an immortal, you will surely meet me again.”

“Ah!” Gu Yue Fang Xiang cried out, lost for words, he did not expect that this fortuitous encounter would be so valuable.

After a moment, he watched in a daze by the pool as Lian Ke Xin flew up into the sky, vanishing into the clouds.

“Lian Ke Xin, Fairy Ke Xin...” Gu Yue Fang Xiang muttered, his hand over his heart.

Lian Ke Xin’s appearance was etched into his memories.

He knew that from now on, other than finding his father, he had a new goal to achieve in life —

That was to become a Gu Immortal and meet with Fairy Lian Ke Xin again!

Chapter 2245: Reprimanding Heavenly Court

“How is it?” Twelfth Hair asked with a smile.

Within the clouds, he met with mermaid immortal Lian Ke Xin secretly.

Lian Ke Xin replied: “He is a Gu Immortal seed indeed, there is a high chance of becoming an immortal.”

Twelfth Hair shook his head: “He obtained an immortal cultivation method and strong motivation from this, but they are not enough. We need to continue raising his foundation, after all, the balancing of three qi can only be done by himself.”

As for the other calamities and tribulations, they were not a problem! The immortals could secretly help him from the side.

“Then what do you intend?” Lian Ke Xin showed a look of hesitation.

Twelfth Hair explained: “I will give him around eight days to familiarize himself with those mortal Gu. Afterwards, I will arrange for those pursuers to find him and act as his sparring targets.”

“His mother, Steel Thread City Lord, is not dead, she is only in a comatose state of near death, only a Gu Immortal’s method can save her.”

“I will let him understand this and affirm his determination to go through and pass the tribulation!”

Lian Ke Xin heard this and became solemn for a while, she soon praised: “Friend, you have broad visions, I cannot compare to you. After we complete this mission, I hope you can decide the distribution of contribution points.”

“Fairy, you are too modest.” Twelfth Hair squinted his eyes and waved his hand: “I will report your effort as well. Besides, Star Collection City decides the contribution points, how can I interfere with it?”

Lian Ke Xin had originally taken this mission to get closer to Twelfth Hair. But once she found out about Gu Yue Fang Xiang’s special identity, she immediately understood that Gu Yue Fang Xiang would become very useful in the future, he was an important pawn to Fang Yuan!

Thus, this mermaid immortal came up with a plot, she went in and used herself as bait to interact with Gu Yue Fang Xiang.

In order to perform well, this mermaid immortal was putting in her full effort.

Twelfth Hair was afraid that her performance would affect his own gains, thus, he explained another plan to Lian Ke Xin.

Lian Ke Xin was very sharp, she quickly explained that she was not going to fight with him over contribution points, this made Twelfth Hair feel very satisfied about their cooperation.

The atmosphere between the two became harmonious again.

After a short conversation, suddenly, far away in the south, a huge pillar of light soared to the sky as an eerie Gu refinement aura spread around the vicinity.

Lian Ke Xin sensed it and her expression changed: “Someone has just succeeded in refining rank seven Immortal Gu?”

She then turned to look at Twelfth Hair as she praised: “Your race is truly talented, just this aura alone is making me feel admiration and aspiration. I wonder if a meeting can be arranged for us?”

Twelfth Hair showed a difficult expression, he subconsciously suppressed his volume as he shook his head: “I can introduce you to any other hairy man Gu Immortal, but this person is very special. He is actually Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s clone, he has been affected by master’s method, he is imprisoned for life and cannot stop refining Gu.”

Lian Ke Xin was very shocked when she heard this, inspiration flashed in her mind, she asked involuntarily: “Don’t tell me this imprisoned Gu Immortal is Sixth Hair?”

Twelfth Hair nodded: “Very astute, fairy, you guessed it right on your first try. The valley that Sixth Hair lives in is also specially arranged by master, it is a forbidden area in the sovereign immortal aperture, we call it the Spectral Valley Forbidden Ground.”

Currently, within the Spectral Valley Forbidden Ground.

Sixth Hair was thin as a stick, his cheeks were caved in and his eye bags were deep.

A rank seven Immortal Gu had just been refined.

This Gu worm looked like an ant, the front half was shiny while the lower half was dim, its front limbs were short and weak while its back legs were long and powerful.

It was the enslavement path Immortal Gu — master-servant Gu.

“Finally, I finally refined it...”

“I failed thirty-three times, got heavily injured twenty-seven times, and nearly died nineteen times, but I still refined it in the end!”

“With this Immortal Gu, I can definitely help sect leader Fang Yuan.”

“I need to rely on sect leader to save the main body.”

“Wait, am I forgetting something... never mind, I need to continue refining Gu.”

“The more Immortal Gu I refine, the stronger Shadow Sect will get, and the higher the hope of saving the main body!”

Sixth Hair’s state of mind was not right, after mumbling for some time, he started to prepare and refine other Immortal Gu.

A moment later.

Within treasure yellow heaven, Fang Yuan’s will and He Feng Yang’s will completed a transaction under everyone’s watchful gazes.

Fang Yuan obtained an earth path resource point of Central Continent called nine central stone forest, while He Feng Yang obtained master-servant Gu.

“They really did a transaction, this is unbelievable, He Feng Yang is actually so daring!”

“He is not doing this out of desperation, it is obvious that Immortal Crane Sect has instructed him to do this.”

“Immortal Crane Sect? No, if they publicly transacted with Heaven Refining Demon Venerable, even Immortal Crane Sect cannot bear the pressure from everyone. This transaction is definitely approved by Heavenly Court, otherwise, how can the ten great ancient sects even dare to do this?”

“Didn’t Heavenly Court denounce Fang Yuan as a Demon Venerable? They will cooperate with him?”

“So what? Rank seven Immortal Gu are hard to refine, Heavenly Court is extremely rich, they have countless resource points like nine central stone forest, this cost for an Immortal Gu is too worthwhile, even I would do it!”

“Fang Yuan is truly Heaven Refining Demon Venerable, he can refine rank seven Immortal Gu with such ease! It is simply as easy as drinking water.”

“What do you think his success rate of refining rank eight Immortal Gu is? It won’t be so easy, right? I think he has fifty, no, thirty percent chance of success.”

“What about rank nine Immortal Gu?”

“Hehe, you must be joking! Even a refinement path venerable will face great difficulties when trying to refine a rank nine Gu. Look at historical records, there had been many attempts to refine rank nine Immortal Gu, but how many truly succeeded? Even Star Constellation Immortal Venerable took a hundred years to refine a wild rank nine wisdom Gu.”

“That’s right, Heavenly Court spent over a million years to repair the rank nine fate Gu. And in the end? It was all for nothing. And they were just trying to repair a rank nine Immortal Gu, refining one from scratch is too hard!”

“Who knows, this Gu Yue Fang Yuan is the first refinement path venerable in history, we can only look up to him, we cannot fathom his true abilities.”

At once, the Gu Immortals of the five regions and two heavens discussed among themselves.

They started to talk about Fang Yuan’s refinement path abilities, they were curious about the extent of power that a refinement path venerable had.

Most of them felt that it would be very difficult for Fang Yuan to refine a rank nine Immortal Gu. After all, many historical records supported this idea.

The remaining Gu Immortals felt that they were too weak to see through and understand Fang Yuan’s true limits.

Soon, the Gu Immortals’ topic shifted to Heavenly Court gradually under some people’s meticulous arrangement.

Heavenly Court approved of He Feng Yang’s actions while Star Constellation Immortal Venerable held an ambiguous attitude towards Fang Yuan, many of the immortals looked at this in disdain, they expressed their tone of mockery towards Heavenly Court, but they understood why this was happening.

After all, Fang Yuan’s business could not be stopped, there were a lot of profits to gain from it as well!

From this topic, the Gu Immortals shifted towards the issue of Heavenly Court’s stoppage of handing out immortal essence stones.

Thus, begrudged discussions and requests to Heavenly Court to distribute immortal essence stones became louder and more common, the mockery, jealousy, and hatred towards Heavenly Court became increasingly aggravated.

Heavenly Court had always been the number one human force in the world, they stood proudly at the top of the Gu Immortal world of the five regions and two heavens.

This time, they stopped distributing immortal essence stones. It went against their usual behavior of being the leader of the Gu Immortal world.

The lack of immortal essence stones caused a lot of trouble to the bulk of the Gu Immortals.

Within treasure yellow heaven, nine out of ten transactions were done through bartering, the remaining one involved the purchasing of immortal essence stones by various super forces at high prices.

Western Desert.

Fang Di Chang also activated his Gu worm to connect to treasure yellow heaven.

“This wave of discontent towards Heavenly Court is very strange, it seems Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Heaven Refining Demon Venerable are the ones manipulating it from the background.” Fang Di Chang’s eyes flickered with uncertainty as he sensed the peculiarity.

And this was the truth behind the matter, Fang Yuan and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not let go of this opportunity.

Heavenly Court’s reputation fell time and again under such discontented discussions.

Fang Di Chang’s divine sense came to Fang Yuan’s will and spoke in a humble and subservient manner: “Western Desert’s Fang Di Chang greets Lord Alliance Leader, alliance leader is truly a master of the pen and the sword, your divine radiance lights up the world, I hope Lord Alliance Leader will live a life of eternal bliss, I hope your lifespan can rival heaven itself...”

Before he finished, Fang Yuan’s will waved his hands impatiently, interrupting Fang Di Chang: “Cut the crap, transact now.”

Fang Di Chang quickly acknowledged.

Thus, another transaction after the one with He Feng Yang was successfully completed.

Fang Yuan refined a rank seven Immortal Gu and gave it to Fang clan. They paid him one earth vein resource point and several million hairy man slaves.

Fang clan originally wanted to keep a low profile and develop in secret. But after Fang Yuan’s Great Love declaration, he exposed his relationship with Fang clan and stunned them completely.

Wan clan gathered the Western Desert’s righteous path forces to attack Fang clan but failed, it caused Fang clan to understand their circumstances, they stopped dreaming of a different outcome.

Thus, under Fang Di Chang’s suggestion, Western Desert’s Fang clan declared that they were joining the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance.

“At this point, Fang clan can only cooperate with Fang Yuan and use this chance to strengthen ourselves!” Fang Di Chang sighed internally.

This was a dangerous status to have, but at the same time, they gained immense benefits.

Immortal Gu were too hard to refine!

“With this Immortal Gu replenished, my battle strength can rival ordinary rank seven Gu Immortals now.” Fang Di Chang fell into deep contemplation.

He had already gone through the immortal ascension, he was a rank six Gu Immortal now.

The balancing of three qi was the hardest hurdle but Fang Di Chang had ample experience. It could not be that he would fail in his second attempt after succeeding the first.

The other problem with immortal ascension were tribulations.

But with the help of Fang clan’s Gu Immortals, most tribulations were of no threat.

Unless they were dream path or painting path.

What made Fang Di Chang feel regret was that his immortal ascension did not have any natural inspiration opportunity.

When a Gu Master ascended, they would have a prime opportunity for natural inspiration to occur. They would be able to ask the world some questions and gain immense benefits.

But this time, Fang Di Chang did not get this opportunity.

This was not because he was undergoing immortal ascension for the second time, instead, the issue was with heaven’s will itself.

With the fusion of two heavens, heaven’s will had also gotten into chaos and turbulence, it did not have the ability to grant natural inspiration at this time.

“After recuperating for a few days, we will attack Wan clan!” This time, Fang Di Chang’s eyes were sharp like an eagle’s.

Chapter 2246: Not Much Immortal Essence Left

Northern Plains.

Golden light floated in the sky like thin threads, gathering and forming a huge golden aurora that permeated into the ground and spread out widely, the commotion was huge and the aura was vast.

This was Giant Sun Immortal Venerable refining Northern Plains’ natural luck path dao marks.

But at this time, the golden light that filled the area dimmed.

A moment later, this core area of Northern Plains returned to its original state.

In the air, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable opened his eyes slowly, he had a handsome face and his mouth, nose, eyes and brows were all thick and straight, but currently, his expression was cold and had a faint trace of helplessness.

The three venerables tried to kill Spectral Soul Demon Venerable but failed because of Fang Yuan’s disturbance, afterwards, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable returned to Northern Plains and refined luck path dao marks there instead.

After a period of time, the results were abundant.

Currently, he had already completed a stage of his plans, all the luck path dao marks of Northern Plains’ core area were refined by him, his luck path dao marks covered the wisdom path area that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had refined earlier, allowing him to cancel out some of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s advantage in this place.

However, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable could do nothing against the wisdom path dao marks that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had already refined. But in the future, if they fought here, although Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would get a dao mark amplification, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable would also receive the same bonus, he would not lose his territorial advantage.

“But I don’t have much immortal essence left.” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable sighed to himself.

The refinement of natural dao marks expended a lot of rank nine immortal essence.

Initially, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was only refining the luck path dao marks of the vicinity around him. It was like he was building a ball-shaped spider web, from an initial dot, it grew into a small ball, and finally a large ball.

The larger the ball expanded, the more dao marks he would encounter. To refine these luck path dao marks, he would expend an increasingly terrifying amount of immortal essence.

Currently, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable only had around a hundred yellow apricot immortal essence beads left. This forced him to stop here, his immortal essence reserves were reaching a critical level, he had to leave some for emergencies.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s rank nine immortal aperture could produce yellow apricot immortal essence, this was his only source of immortal essence production.

Longevity Heaven could not produce any.

Even though Longevity Heaven did not annex any nine heavens fragments and was not corroded by heaven’s will, after Giant Sun Immortal Venerable died in his era, it stopped producing immortal essence.

Right now, even though Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had revived, the venerable aperture that he had was the current one, it had not passed one chaotic disaster yet.

Furthermore, this second aperture had also just started developing, it was not flourishing and did not produce a large amount of immortal essence.

That was unless Giant Sun Immortal Venerable annexed Longevity Heaven, but if he did that, he would gain a huge number of luck path dao marks, it would destroy his plan of cultivating blood path.

“I need to raise blood path to a certain level first before I can regain my previous life’s foundation. This development will be costly, but I must endure it. Blood path will be of utmost importance when I face the other venerables in the future.”

“Thankfully, even though I am low on immortal essence, the other two are in an even worse state.” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable smiled to himself.

All along, he had been thinking that immortal essence was his advantage.

Even though he could not refine more luck path dao marks, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not slack off, he waited for his immortal essence to replenish while comprehending blood path.

Blood Sea Ancestor was actually Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s clone.

Blood Sea Ancestor created blood path and left behind countless blood path inheritances after he died. Most were mortal level and contained mortal killer moves and mortal Gu, but he had nine true inheritances of Gu Immortal level, that was the peak of blood path when he died.

These nine were blood skull Gu, blood handprint Gu, blood qi Gu, blood sweat Gu, menses blood Gu, blood shadow Gu, blood battle Gu, blood deity Gu, as well as the method to raise and enslave the ancient desolate beast violent blood dragon bat.

It was a pity that Blood Sea Ancestor was targeted by Heavenly Court in his life, even after his death, many inheritances were ruined by them.

Thankfully, Blood Sea left behind countless mortal inheritances, most of the nine true inheritances also displayed their worth.

The one who obtained the most true inheritances was Southern Border’s Gu Immortal Shang Yan Fei.

In his younger days, he found blood handprint Immortal Gu in Southern Border’s blood tide pit, he later obtained blood shadow Gu’s true inheritance.

Northern Plains’ menses blood Immortal Gu was obtained by Dong Fang Chang Fan.

Western Desert’s blood qi Immortal Gu true inheritance was obtained by Demon Immortal Qi Jue.

As for the true inheritance regarding the ancient desolate beast violent blood dragon bat, it was obtained by Shadow Sect’s Song Zi Xing.

Central Continent’s blood deity Immortal Gu true inheritance was fought over by the ten great ancient sects, they destroyed over half of it and the incomplete Blood Deity Immortal Gu recipe ended up in the hands of Myriad Dragon Dock.

As for the remaining three true inheritances, because of the changing terrain, a volcano erupted and destroyed blood skull Immortal Gu’s true inheritance. Blood sweat Gu was taken mysteriously and had never been shown in public, it was possible that the person who took it met with an accident. Blood battle Gu’s true inheritance was by chance destroyed by an immemorial desolate beast.

After Giant Sun Immortal Venerable revived, he took all of the blood path research results that the Northern Plains Huang Jin tribes had, as well as Longevity Heaven’s research gains.

Next, he instructed Earth Extremity Gan Ni to refine Immortal Gu, the result was that they obtained several blood path Immortal Gu.

Among them, there was blood battle Immortal Gu.

As for the other seven Immortal Gu, other than Blood Deity, the rest had been tested, it was confirmed that all of them were already existing in the world.

Without an alternative, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had to temporarily turn imitation Gu into blood relation Gu and barely created a blood path formation that helped him to revive during the battle in Crazed Demon Cave.

“I have already digested the Primordial Domain regarding blood path, my current blood path attainment level has also reached supreme grandmaster! But...”

There were too few blood path Immortal Gu!

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had first absorbed the Primordial Domain in Crazed Demon Cave to become a supreme grandmaster in luck path, afterwards, he focused on blood path.

He obtained a lot of the Primordial Domain but did not have time to digest them earlier, now, he had already used up all of the Primordial Domain regarding blood path.

In terms of attainment level, he was the number one person in the world regarding blood path, but currently, he was in an awkward state of lacking relevant Immortal Gu.

He needed a large quantity of crucial blood path Immortal Gu!

Among them, the ones that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable wanted the most were Blood Asset, Blood Skull, Bloodline, Blood Relation, and others.

But in fact, these Immortal Gu were already owned.

Gan Ni had been refining all sorts of blood path Immortal Gu for Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, blood rope Immortal Gu was one of the products.

But these Immortal Gu were too low ranked, they did not suit Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

These blood path Immortal Gu needed to be rank eight at least!

This job was too difficult for Gan Ni to complete.

Gan Ni cultivated earth path and refinement path, she was not a pure refinement path Gu Immortal. Even if she was, the success rate of refining rank eight Immortal Gu was just too low.

“If Long Hair Ancestor were still around, it would be much simpler.” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable started to miss Long Hair Ancestor.

Back then, he had asked Long Hair Ancestor to refine all those luck Immortal Gu, he managed to create Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

“Fang Yuan took the initiative to refine so many blood path Immortal Gu, regardless of this situation, or whether I need to advance my other blood path Immortal Gu, I will need to transact with him!” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable found that he could not avoid Fang Yuan.

Recently, He Feng Yang publicly transacted with Fang Yuan, this showed Giant Sun Immortal Venerable that Heavenly Court had an ambiguous attitude towards him.

Since Heavenly Court was attempting this, if Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not follow, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Fang Yuan would leave him in the dust.

“I’ll let Heavenly Lord Bai Zu handle this and buy blood path Immortal Gu from Fang Yuan! Hmph, isn’t he quite close to Fang Yuan...” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable made a decision.

Next, he started to deduce more blood path Immortal Gu recipes and killer moves.

Blood path supreme grandmaster attainment level was his greatest assurance.

Of course, there was another aspect, he was using his methods to look for the blood path research results of the various super forces, and also the blood path inheritances left behind by other geniuses.

After all, deducing Immortal Gu recipes and killer moves took time and effort, if he could use established inheritances as reference, he would save a lot of time and energy.

Heavenly Court.

Two days ago, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had already stopped refining Heavenly Court’s wisdom path dao marks.

It was not that she was unwilling to, but her situation was the same as Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, their immortal essence reserves were reaching critical levels, they had no choice but to stop.

But Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s situation was different from Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

In her previous life, her venerable aperture was contributed to Heavenly Court, and because Heavenly Court had devoured many immemorial nine heavens fragments, it was corroded by heaven’s will and her own wisdom path dao marks were turned back into natural dao marks.

Thus, she could not retrieve her previous venerable aperture like Giant Sun Immortal Venerable to raise her own dao marks to a colossal scale.

But she had her own advantage.

Heavenly Court contained a huge number of wisdom path dao marks, far beyond what she had in her previous life.

Because Heavenly Court had existed for three million years, during which countless rank eight Gu Immortals had appeared, their immortal apertures were also fused into Heavenly Court.

If she fully refined all the wisdom path dao marks in Heavenly Court, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would receive amplification that was far beyond Giant Sun Immortal Venerable inside Longevity Heaven!

These last two days, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had been deducing killer moves, she wanted to use star eyes Immortal Gu and others to modify her own combat system.

Similar to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, she had absorbed a lot of the Primordial Domain, her star path became supreme grandmaster again, and together with her wisdom path cultivation, she was much more adept than Giant Sun Immortal Venerable in modifying killer moves!

When refining natural dao marks, the immortal essence expenditure was huge. but when deducing killer moves, for the case of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, the immortal essence expenditure was of an acceptable level.

Relying on her current venerable aperture, the production of immortal essence was greater than the amount she expended.

“But the most important thing is to refine all of Heavenly Court’s wisdom path dao marks.”

If she completed that, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would be able to use a killer move to conceal Heavenly Court’s information, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable would not be able to use Longevity Heaven’s luck path dao marks to forcefully inspect it.

Things were difficult to do openly, but easy to do secretly. Star Constellation Immortal Venerable knew this clearly.

“After I block Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s investigative method, I will break the truthful floating ice and retrieve derivation Gu, it will be helpful in our human path development!”

“In terms of immortal essence, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable should have an advantage, in terms of Gu refinement, Fang Yuan has the advantage. But I have rank nine derivation Immortal Gu, if I can use it well, I can surpass the two venerables.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable calculated internally.

In the contest of three venerables, although they were not physically fighting, their contest had taken a different form.

Refining dao marks, immortal essence reserves, rank nine Immortal Gu, all these various aspects were crucial points that the venerables competed in.

Undeniably, whoever had the advantage in these aspects would have a higher chance of winning in the end!

Chapter 2247: Fang Yuan’s Second Rank Nine Immortal Gu

Eastern Sea.

“This is about enough, I should stop now.” Fang Yuan willed as he stopped refining dao marks.

The sovereign immortal aperture had a hundred beads of yellow apricot immortal essence stored.

But Fang Yuan did not stop refining natural dao marks because of issues with his immortal essence reserves.

The truth was, he refined Eastern Sea’s refinement path dao marks openly, while secretly unsealing the truthful floating ice in his aperture!

Most of his yellow apricot immortal essence beads were used to unseal the truthful floating ice, only a small portion were used to refine Eastern Sea’s refinement path dao marks.

Because of his action, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable stayed in their territories, they did not come to attack Fang Yuan.

“Oh? Giant Sun Immortal Venerable stopped refining natural dao marks.” Fang Yuan’s eyes shone with luster.

This information could not be hidden, because the three venerables paid a lot of attention to each other, Fang Yuan soon caught wind of this.

“Giant Sun Immortal Venerable should not have much immortal essence left, although Star Constellation Immortal Venerable is holed up inside Heavenly Court, her situation should be similar.”

Fang Yuan let out a sigh of relief.

With the two of them having low immortal essence, the chance of them attacking Fang Yuan was very low, their threat towards him also fell by many times.

“Thankfully, I took a risk earlier and refined rank nine Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus, otherwise, I’d be in a tough predicament now.”

In the contest of three venerables, if one side lagged behind, they would not be able to catch up easily.

After all, the three venerables were all elites of elites.

“Currently, in terms of immortal essence reserves, I am already on par with the others. But truthfully, I have a lot more advantage than the two venerables.” Fang Yuan evaluated.

Firstly, Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus was simply too incredible and useful!

Next, Fang Yuan’s sovereign immortal aperture had time path methods in effect, the rate of time was faster than the two venerables. In contrast, because of conflicting dao marks, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not have any time path methods that could be effective on their immortal apertures.

And finally, Fang Yuan’s sovereign immortal aperture had far deeper foundation than the two venerables who had just started developing theirs, the yellow apricot immortal essence he produced exceeded theirs.

With all three elements, Fang Yuan’s yellow apricot immortal essence production far surpassed the two venerables.

Currently, while Fang Yuan refined the natural dao marks, he showed signs of weakness, he constantly had to stop and wait.

Because of obscured heavenly secret, the two venerables did not know that Fang Yuan possessed rank nine Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus.

And because they knew about the sovereign immortal aperture’s details, they knew the trait of non-conflicting dao marks, they did not think that Fang Yuan would take a risk to accelerate the time flow.

As for the immortal aperture origin core’s production of immortal essence, the two venerables knew that the sovereign immortal aperture had just undergone a chaos tribulation and also got hit by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s fortune and disaster coexists killer move, thus, they underestimated the sovereign immortal aperture’s current foundation.

Especially during this period of time, Fang Yuan refined Gu in treasure yellow heaven and was willing to pay Immortal Gu to purchase all sorts of resource points and establish earth vein and water veins, he did not conceal anything.

In the eyes of the two venerables, such an action of urgently developing his immortal aperture meant that the sovereign immortal aperture had suffered immense losses in Crazed Demon Cave.

Fang Yuan guessed the two venerables’ thoughts: “In their eyes, I need to work on raising my immortal essence production, while refining rank nine Immortal Gu is too dangerous, accelerating time flow will also cause tribulations to occur more quickly and expose my weakness. Thus, I can only build more resource points to raise my immortal aperture origin core so that I can produce more yellow apricot immortal essence.”

“But if I make a small blunder, the two venerables will immediately be suspicious of me. Especially Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, as the number one person in wisdom path throughout history, it will be extremely difficult to deceive her!”

Fang Yuan was currently treading on thin ice, he knew that maintaining the status-quo was the best form of victory.

He could not afford to make any small mistakes!

If a single small mistake appears, the two venerables would analyze it carefully before quickly taking attempts to probe the truth.

If the truth was exposed, what would happen?

Fang Yuan would definitely be attacked by both venerables together!

Fang Yuan did not know how long he could hide this, after all, he was facing the two of the greatest geniuses throughout human history.

It was possible that he would be exposed at the next moment.

If such a situation happened, Fang Yuan would not be surprised.

No longer distracted by refining the refinement path dao marks, Fang Yuan started to unseal the truthful floating ice with his full strength.

Intuition told him that a huge gain was about to appear.

And sure enough, several days later, his heaven path attainment level rose to quasi-grandmaster.

Even though it did not reach grandmaster, Fang Yuan had a deep foundation, he developed a strong sense of confidence —

“If I deduce with all my effort now, I can definitely create a heaven path killer move that can allow me to take the Primordial Domain!”

Fang Yuan’s portion of the Primordial Domain had always been kept in treasure yellow heaven.

Goods in treasure yellow heaven could not be used on the spot.

Thus, Fang Yuan could not sell his own clone and absorb the Primordial Domain there, there was no chance of this happening.

Fang Yuan had to retrieve the portion of the Primordial Domain and absorb them to raise his attainment levels!

“Unsealing the truthful floating ice mainly increases heaven path dao marks, followed by heaven path attainment level, and finally, the attainment level of other paths. This last effect is barely evident, it is only an additional effect of the truthful floating ice and is extremely insignificant.”

“Only by using the Primordial Domain can I raise the attainment levels of all my paths to a huge degree!”

“But, right now, is there a need to do it?”

After careful consideration, Fang Yuan shook his head.

Deducing the heaven path killer move was not hard for Fang Yuan, his worry were the two venerables.

Once he took out the Primordial Domain, he would have exposed his heaven path method.

The two venerables would first be alerted, Fang Yuan had the sovereign immortal body, with so many portions of the Primordial Domain, if he digested them, his attainment levels would rise and cause him to become much more threatening.

Afterwards, the two venerables would be suspicious, why would Fang Yuan possess such a heaven path method?

He did not use it in the past, now that he had the heaven path method, it meant that his heaven path cultivation had improved greatly.

That would make them think of the truthful floating ice.

After all, Fang Yuan obtained the most pieces of truthful floating ice among the three venerables!

If Fang Yuan improved in heaven path because he unsealed the truthful floating ice, then where did he get the immortal essence beads needed to do so?

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Limitless Demon Venerable had cooperated for a million years to maintain the Crazed Demon formation. She even assimilated with the Dao and created the killer move human executing heaven’s work, she definitely knew that unsealing the truthful floating ice required immortal essence.

Once she found out, she would inform Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, and the two would work together and attack Fang Yuan to suppress him.

Like what Fang Yuan considered earlier, a small mistake would cause the two venerables to attack him immediately.

It was too likely!

“I can secretly deduce the heaven path killer move but the collection of the Primordial Domain will need to wait.”

Even though the Primordial Domain was very useful to Fang Yuan, it was not the key now. Because it would cause both venerables to attack and cause Fang Yuan to lose his current advantage, the loss was not worth the gain.

“No, the heaven path killer move can wait. After all, once I gain this method, my luck will rise sharply.”

“Also, I have rank nine Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus now, it has already increased the burden on obscured heavenly secret, its expenditure is rising rapidly.”

“What I need to do is to refine a second rank nine Immortal Gu!”

This thought had been lingering in Fang Yuan’s mind for a long time.

As for what Immortal Gu he should refine, Fang Yuan already had an answer.

That was Immortal Gu — Advance Refinement!

Not Spring Autumn Cicada, Dog Shit Luck, Attitude, or Dream Token, but advance refinement Gu.

Once advance refinement Gu becomes rank nine, it would be extremely useful for Fang Yuan to advance the rest of his rank eight Immortal Gu.

For example, when Fang Yuan refined Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus, if he had rank nine advance refinement Gu, the difficulty would be halved at least!

Fang Yuan had two advantages when refining rank nine advance refinement Gu.

The first advantage was that Fang Yuan had rank eight advance refinement Gu already, this Gu came from Lang Ya Sect, it was originally the core of the Long Hair refinement path formation, it was currently the core of Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool.

Secondly, advance refinement Gu was a refinement path Immortal Gu. Even though some rule path immortal materials were needed in the process, it was much purer than Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus, refinement path immortal materials were the bulk of its components.

Fang Yuan was a refinement path venerable, he could perfectly process refinement path immortal materials, this meant that the success rate would be much higher as well.

Right when Fang Yuan was secretly thinking of refining rank nine advance refinement Gu.

Western Desert.

At the core area of wind falcon desert.

Bam!

With a loud sound, a vast amount of sand flew into the sky.

An Immortal Gu House charged out from underground, it was Fang clan’s rank seven Immortal Gu House, Chicken Dog Coop.

This Chicken Dog Coop Immortal Gu House looked like two buildings side by side, the left building was yellow and had a round plaque that had ‘chicken’ written on it, the right building was red and had the word ‘dog’ on its plaque.

As its entrance opened, chicken and dog ancient desolate beasts flew out, there were tens of them.

Chicken Dog Coop burst out with profound light, shaking heaven and earth.

The empty desert suddenly had an oasis that appeared out of nowhere.

This oasis had countless pine trees that were tall and sharp, each one was at least three hundred feet tall, and they were widely spaced apart. The trees spread their branches and leaves out, the leaves gathered into balls with an extremely flat surface that resembled a grassland.

On top of the pine leaf grassland, there were huge nests.

Within the nests, there were long-distanced wind falcons, there were all sorts of wind falcons ranging from ordinary beasts, beast kings, desolate beasts, and even ancient desolate beasts.

“This tall pine oasis is incredible, as expected of Wan clan’s resource point that is ranked second in Western Desert.” Fang Di Chang critiqued from within Chicken Dog Coop.

This was Wan clan’s territory, the rank seven Gu Immortal expert of Wan clan that guarded this place was Wan Xiao.

He did not show up, instead, he controlled the immortal formation and defended against the attacks of the ancient desolate beasts, he scolded angrily: “Fang clan, what are you trying to do? As a Western Desert righteous path super force, you are actually attacking another righteous path super force without reason?!”

Within Chicken Dog Coop, Fang Di Chang smiled coldly and replied: “Earlier, Wan clan gathered the Western Desert super forces to attack my Fang clan together, we will settle the score now! Do you really think my Fang clan is a weak target to bully?”

Chapter 2248: Winding Light Platform

At the center of the formation. Wan Xiao’s expression was solemn, he felt a huge rock pressing down on his mind.

Fang clan’s attack was too sudden, he was completely unguarded!

The truth was, it was not that Wan clan had not made preparations.

Even since they failed in rallying Western Desert righteous path super forces, Wan clan had prepared for Fang clan’s retaliation; they sent more manpower to their large peripheral resource points, while also strengthening the defensive formations there.

They even paid a huge price to request Xiao clan to set up a transportation formation, in order to send reinforcements in time.

But who could have thought that the moment Fang clan made a move, they actually bypassed the peripheral resource points, and directly invaded deep into Wan clan’s territory, attacking Wan clan’s second largest resource point!

“Fang clan planned a long time for this, but how in the world did they come here?” Wan Xiao was puzzled.

Wan clan was already aware of Fang clan’s three Immortal Gu Houses – Chicken Dog Coop, Inquiry Dock, and Fallen Flower Hall. None of them could accomplish this.

“Oh no!”

Right at this time, Wan Xiao shockingly sensed that the formation was shaking and the ground was quaking, as if an earth trench was about to form. A large number of pine trees of the tall pine oasis fell.

“This defensive formation’s base is buried thousands of feet deep under the ground. Fang clan actually found it so precisely, they are destroying it!”

Wan Xiao quickly inspected and saw an Immortal Gu House wreaking havoc underground, destroying the formation’s base.

Immortal formations usually had a formation base, it was like the foundation of a building but much more important. Formation bases were incredibly important to the immortal formations, they were the foundation of the foundation.

If the formation base was destroyed, the formation would become extremely unstable, like a building with ruined foundation. With just a slight disturbance in the base, the formation would reveal a huge flaw and even be destroyed.

Therefore, when Gu Immortals set up immortal formations, they would hide the formation base. Some formation bases were hidden underground, some were hidden in the air, and some were kept in the center of the formation.

This defensive formation in tall pine oasis had existed for a long time, and because of the environmental restrictions, the Gu Immortals who set the formation back then felt that only by burying the formation base deep underground could the formation take care of all aspects. It could defend and also nurture resources.

“But the formation base has been discovered and is being attacked! Fang clan is too insidious, they actually had an earth path Immortal Gu House as well!” Wan Xiao gritted his teeth.

What made him feel an even greater chill was that Fang clan’s methods were powerful and well prepared.

“Whose plan was it? Isn’t Fang Di Chang trapped inside Divine Emperor City? Could it be that youngster Fang Yun? What should I do?” Wan Xiao was sweating all over.

He had confidence earlier as tall pine oasis’ defensive formation was very strong. He had confidence to rely on the formation to hold on until Wan clan’s reinforcements arrived.

Fang clan had Immortal Gu Houses, Wan clan naturally had them as well!

When Wan clan’s Immortal Gu Houses arrived and coordinated with the defensive formation, it would not be difficult to force back Fang clan.

Once Fang clan were forced back, it would be Wan clan’s victory.

Because Fang clan’s action already crossed the limits of the Western Desert righteous path, such a defeat would definitely lower their reputation.

Wan clan could take the chance to counterattack, rallying the other forces with a righteous reason. At that time, the reaction of Western Desert’s super forces would be different from before.

“But can I hold on until then?” Wan Xiao was solemn.

Wan clan headquarters.

“What? Fang clan attacked our tall pine oasis!” After receiving Wan Xiao’s letter, the expression of Wan clan’s first supreme elder changed sharply.

Wan Xiao had given a detailed description in the letter. The situation was serious and extremely urgent.

Tall pine oasis was Wan clan’s second largest resource point, it was a renowned super resource point in Western Desert and even in the whole five regions, it could not be taken. Once it was destroyed or taken over, the losses would be enormous.

“Fang clan... is really vicious. It is now a critical moment for my Wan clan!”

Wan clan’s first supreme elder only had rank seven cultivation and did not have outstanding battle strength, but he possessed an intuitive view of the big picture.

He was deeply aware: Once tall pine oasis fell into the enemy’s hands, not only would they lose all the resources inside, Wan clan’s reputation and prestige would also suffer a huge impact.

Previously, Wan clan’s rally did not succeed. Now, if the resource point were to be destroyed by Fang clan, in the eyes of everyone, Wan clan would become the weakest force in Western Desert’s righteous path. They would be an object of ridicule and the representation of the weakest target!

Once this thought emerged, Wan clan would head down the road of decline. Because in the current situation, with the chaotic war imminent, people’s hearts were uneasy. If the chaotic war erupted, everyone would feel that Wan clan could be taken advantage of.

This was a frightening situation for Wan clan.

Hence, when Wan clan’s first supreme elder received Wan Xiao’s request for reinforcements, he immediately acted. He personally moved with Winding Light Platform.

Only a rank six Gu Immortal and a rank seven Immortal Gu House were left to guard the headquarters.

On his way, Wan clan’s first supreme elder messaged all the Wan clan Gu Immortals.

The Wan clan immortals were shocked and furious.

“The peripheral territories are peaceful and have no disturbance.” After receiving the replies, the brows of Wan clan’s first supreme elder furrowed tightly.

After some rapid thinking, he clenched his teeth and sent a command.

Shortly after, Wan Hao Guang received this command.

“Zhui Qing, defend this place. If Fang clan attacks, you must retreat immediately. I need to hurry to wind falcon desert to reinforce Wan Xiao.”

Wan Hao Guang immediately moved out.

The relationship between him and Wan Xiao’s relationship. Back then, three Wan clan immortals fought Fang Yuan, and Wan Xiao risked his life to save Wan Hao Guang. Now, Wan Hao Guang could similarly go to such an extent.

But Wan Zhui Qing grabbed Wan Hao Guang’s hand: “Lord, it is too dangerous for you to go right now! We don’t have clear information on what Fang clan’s real arrangements are. If their plan of besieging the enemy stronghold is meant to strike at the reinforcements, wouldn’t you be jumping right into a trap?”

“I have a suggestion. Currently, Fang clan has entered deep into our Wan clan’s territory, if we just defend, we will only receive a beating and fall into Fang clan’s scheme. We may as well launch an attack and invade Fang clan’s resource points, we should use offense against offense!”

Wan Hao Guang’s eyes shone as he sized up Wan Zhui Qing and patted his shoulder: “Good lad, you have improved!”

“But, do you think first supreme elder did not think of this?” Wan Hao Guang shook his head.

“First supreme elder asked experts like us to go and reinforce them because he does not have the confidence to force back Fang clan’s forces. Fang clan’s first supreme elder Fang Gong is a rank eight expert, while we have not seen him since the start of the battle. He may very likely be inside Chicken Dog Coop.”

“According to your plan, even if we invade Fang clan’s resource points, once we lose tall pine oasis, our Wan clan will still suffer a huge loss. All those peripheral resource points of Fang clan combined cannot compare to our tall pine oasis.”

Wan Zhui Qing turned pale as he deeply realized the cruelty of reality.

Even if they were not clear of Fang clan’s true arrangements, Wan Hao Guang had to go reinforce them, even if he had to risk his life. Simply because they could not afford to lose tall pine oasis.

Boom!

The formation base was destroyed, a huge flaw formed in the immortal formation from which Chicken Dog Coop charged in.

Wan Xiao was furious but could only maintain the damaged formation while clenching his teeth.

With their home being invaded, wind falcons were provoked. They screeched as they attacked Chicken Dog Coop, going against the chickens and dogs sent by Fang clan.

A fierce fight between the beasts erupted as blood splashed everywhere.

Chickens cawed, dogs barked, and falcons screeched. They formed a medley that resounded in the battlefield.

An immemorial wind falcon clawed open the roof of Chicken Dog Coop.

The Fang clan Gu Immortals inside were already prepared, they repaired it in orderly and calm fashion.

Fang Di Chang laughed loudly: “What an impressive immemorial desolate beast, get in here!”

At the next moment, Chicken Dog Coop let out a beam of light. The beam enveloped the immemorial wind falcon and dragged it inside.

The immemorial wind falcon struggled with all its strength, but its body kept on shrinking and its resistance grew weaker and weaker, until it was finally absorbed by Chicken Dog Coop.

“What? This Immortal Gu House can suppress the immemorial wind falcon?” Wan Xiao’s heart shook.

Chicken Dog Coop was an enslavement path Immortal Gu House that could only enslave chickens and dogs, but who could have expected that it gained a new ability now.

“Enough is enough! Fang clan, you will pay for this one day! I, Wan Xiao, swear upon it.” Wan Xiao roared in his head as he stared at the wind falcons that were being suppressed by Chicken Dog Coop.

Fortunately, this situation did not continue for long, Wan clan’s first supreme elder appeared in the horizon with Wan clan’s Immortal Gu House.

Wan Xiao immediately relaxed.

“Winding Light Platform.” Fang Di Chang muttered as he saw this.

This Winding Light Platform was a rank seven light path Immortal Gu House. It was greyish white with eight sides and eight corners. On the tall platform, Wan clan’s first supreme elder was standing straight, his face furious as he fixed his gaze on Chicken Dog Coop.

Both sides were still a few kilometers apart when Winding Light Platform suddenly shot out four beams of light.

The beams actually bent in the air, they nimbly attacked Chicken Dog Coop from different directions.

Under Fang Di Chang’s control, Chicken Dog Coop activated defensive killer moves and blocked all four beams.

In this short while, Winding Light Platform had arrived before Chicken Dog Coop.

Boom.

With a loud explosive sound, Wan clan’s first supreme elder actually made Winding Light Platform collide with Chicken Dog Coop.

The two Immortal Gu Houses collided before being mutually repelled, a large number of mortal Gu broke into pieces and scattered in the air.

“Hehehe, Wan clan’s first supreme elder, you have such a fiery temper.” Fang Di Chang’s voice resounded in the battlefield.

Wan clan’s first supreme elder and Wan Xiao’s expressions changed: “Fang Di Chang? Weren’t you trapped in Emperor City, no, inside Divine Emperor City?!”

Fang Di Chang’s eyelids twitched as his voice turned heavy: “That is not the important point. Wan clan, I am representing Fang clan to teach you a lesson. Don’t think that any random force can find trouble with my Fang clan.”

“You speak with no shame!” Wan clan’s first supreme elder shouted furiously. Immediately after, Winding Light Platform activated its killer move again.

Tens of beams of light swept the battlefield, Chicken Dog Coop was forced back time and again, its ancient desolate beasts suffered serious casualties. Even the earth path Immortal Gu House that was deep underground also got struck by the light, it was almost destroyed.

“Fang clan moved underground and invaded deep into our territory, it is very likely because of the ability of this earth path Immortal Gu House. But this Immortal Gu House seems fragile, or at least, its defensive aspect is not good enough.” Wan clan’s first supreme elder immediately cheered up.

Chapter 2249: Huge Commotion

Wan clan’s first supreme elder traveled in Winding Light Platform and arrived just in time. After fighting one round with Chicken Dog Coop, he immediately discovered the weakness of Fang clan’s earth path Immortal Gu House.

When he discovered this, Wan clan’s first supreme elder did not hesitate to activate Winding Light Platform to shoot out beams of light at the underground earth path Immortal Gu House.

The earth path Immortal Gu House quickly drilled deeper, evading with extreme nimbleness.

Although its defense was nothing to boast about, its speed was astonishing, it dodged all the beams.

Some beams brushed past it, making for an extremely dangerous situation.

Wan clan’s first supreme elder smiled: “Let me show you my Wan clan Immortal Gu House’s ability!”

Saying so, he activated Winding Light Platform’s signature method.

Immediately, those straight pure-white beams of light underground started to bend and change their direction, attacking the earth path Immortal Gu House again.

A large number of beams formed a web that shrouded the earth path Immortal Gu House from all sides.

The earth path Immortal Gu House could only struggle fiercely, and after ten or so breaths of time, it charged out of the ground.

“I was waiting for you.” The eyes of Wan clan’s first supreme elder shone sharply, “I shall destroy this Immortal Gu House as the payment for invading my Wan clan!”

“Stop dreaming.” Fang Di Chang called out as he controlled Chicken Dog Coop to collide with Winding Light Platform.

Wan clan’s first supreme elder gave a shout, Winding Light Platform shot out beams once again. The beams of light coiled around Winding Light Platform, connecting with each other as they formed a powerful defensive ring.

Chicken Dog Coop collided onto the surface, but its strength was redirected by the winding beams, causing it to brush past Winding Light Platform.

Immediately after, Winding Light Platform shot a ray of yellow light.

The yellow light covered Fang clan’s earth path Immortal Gu House, holding it down on the spot.

Wan clan’s first supreme elder poured in his immortal essence in a frenzy, the yellow light started to coil like a fried dough twist[1].

Under the constriction of the yellow beam of light, Fang clan’s earth path Immortal Gu House started cracking, a large number of mortal Gu were crushed to pieces.

This move was Winding Light Platform’s strongest method. In just a short ten breaths of time, Fang clan’s earth path Immortal Gu House would be completely destroyed, even the Gu Immortals inside could not escape alive!

Wan Zhui Qing flew rapidly in the sky.

His expression was extremely cold, but his heart was like a bright burning flame.

This was the fire of vengeance!

Wan Zhui Qing’s father was Wan Liang Han.

The latter was a rank seven wisdom path Gu Immortal. He had fought Fang Yuan with Wan Hao Guang and Wan Xiao, resulting in his death in the battle.

Back then, Fang Yuan hid in Fang clan, so in Wan Zhui Qing’s heart, it was the same as Fang clan killing his father.

The hatred of his father’s murder was irreconcilable!

Since the moment he learned of father’s death, Wan Zhui Qing’s life experienced a complete change.

Previously, he was a second generation immortal, with his father’s support, he could be arrogant and complacent.

After the fall of his father who sheltered him from the cruelty of the outside world, Wan Zhui Qing matured quickly amidst the grief and fear.

He realized that his comfortable life was the result of many people giving face to his father. He realized how fortunate he had been, and also realized his only hope now was to work hard.

So, when Wan clan’s rally did not bear fruit and they deployed immortals to defend their peripheral territories, although Wan Zhui Qing was only at rank six, he disregarded the risk and requested to be sent to a peripheral territory to defend the resource point.

He knew that he had to display his value to the clan. If the value was not high, then he had to show his loyalty!

He did not have any fortuitous encounters, so he could only rely on the clan.

And the clan was not his father.

Every time Wan Zhui Qing remembered how blessed he had lived when his father was alive, his hatred towards Fang clan deepened.

“Wan Hao Guang made me guard the resource point, but what can I, a mere rank six Gu Immortal, do, even with the support of the immortal formation? Wan Hao Guang is the main reliance to stall the enemies until reinforcements arrive. If Fang clan’s true motive is to attack the peripheral resource points, I will definitely not be able to defend mine.”

“Since that is the case, I may as well risk it and attack Fang clan’s resource points. I will do what Wan Hao Guang cannot do!”

Wan Zhui Qing decided to risk it.

If he stayed to defend the resource point, and Fang clan attacked strongly, he would at most be able to hold on for a while before he would need to retreat through the teleportation formation.

Returning to the clan with such a result of losing the clan’s resource point would be a small stain on his records at the very least.

But if he attacked Fang clan’s resource point and made some gains, it would no doubt be a huge merit. Especially under the situation when tall pine oasis was attacked and the casualties were high.

In this situation, as long as Wan Zhui Qing succeeded, it would be like helping Wan clan restore their prestige.

“At such a time, one merit or contribution will be counted as ten! The clan will also look at me differently.”

“With the clan’s rewards and increased support, I can progress rapidly, otherwise, with my current growth speed, it will take forever before I can exact revenge for my father!”

After Wan Liang Han died, his Gu worms were not left behind for Wan Zhui Qing.

It was not easy for Wan Zhui Qing to cultivate, and he could only fight for opportunities by himself.

“I am here. The most peripheral resource point of Fang clan!” Wan Zhui Qing slowed down, he restrained his aura and approached quietly.

“Fang clan, regarding the hatred of killing my father, I am going to take a bit of revenge now!”

However, after a while, Wan Zhui Qing was stupefied.

He was standing dazedly on the spot, facing the desolate desert.

“Wasn’t this the location of flying sand tunnel? Wait a second, there are clear signs of relocation. Fang clan moved this resource point away?”

Wan Zhui Qing was puzzled.

Was it necessary to do that?

Just to prevent an improbable counterattack of Wan clan, they relocated the resource point?

The loss in doing that was not small.

When resource points were relocated, their productivity would fall. Because the resource point was already in sync with the surrounding environment.

Relocating a resource point was like moving trees, the roots would leave the land and lose the nutrients, even if they were transplanted to a better land, they would need to adapt for some time.

But how many areas were truly suitable for the resource point?

Even if it was an area with denser earth path dao marks, the difference in the arrangement of the dao marks could result in the destruction of the resource point.

Super forces rarely relocated their resource points.

As far as enemies were concerned, relocating a resource point was like the front-line fortress being removed, it reduced the obstructions, and they could easily invade deeper.

“No, something is wrong!”

“Super forces don’t easily relocate their resource points, but it is different now.”

“Heaven Refining Demon Venerable has been madly developing his sovereign immortal aperture, the Gu refinement price list in treasure yellow heaven mostly asks for earth path resource points too.”

“Fang clan could have secretly transacted with Fang Yuan using these resource points as the payment.”

“Then, how many Immortal Gu did they exchange for?”

A shocking thought flashed by Wan Zhui Qing’s mind, turning his face pale as paper.

“Fang clan has secretly traded with Fang Yuan, their strength has increased greatly. Our information on Fang clan is way off, oh no, tall pine oasis is in danger!”

When he realized this, Wan Zhui Qing immediately sent a message to Wan clan’s first supreme elder through treasure yellow heaven.

But at this time, Wan clan’s first supreme elder was controlling Winding Light Platform and making the final attacks on Fang clan’s earth path Immortal Gu House, how could he spare any time to look at Wan Zhui Qing’s message?

“Break!” Wan clan’s first supreme elder shouted.

“Hmph, wishful thinking.” Right at this time, a figure suddenly appeared above Wan clan’s first supreme elder.

Rank eight aura surged like a tide, it was Fang clan’s first supreme elder, rank eight Fang Gong!

Wan clan’s first supreme elder, however, did not even take a glance at Fang Gong. His sight was fixed on the earth path Immortal Gu House, he wanted to destroy this Immortal Gu House to make Fang clan suffer a heavy loss!

As for his safety, Wan clan’s first supreme elder was confident in the protection of Winding Light Platform.

However, all this was within Fang clan’s plan.

Immortal killer move — Roof Tile Breaker!

Fang Gong activated a killer move and slammed down with his palms.

Ripples spread around Winding Light Platform as it blocked Fang Gong’s attack.

Bam bam bam...

Fang Gong slammed down without stopping. Palm shadows flew in the air as attacks rained down on Winding Light Platform.

Rank seven Winding Light Platform possessed rank eight battle strength, blocking all of Fang Gong’s attacks.

But the expression of Wan clan’s first supreme elder changed abruptly.

He made a horrifying discovery: Every attack of Fang Gong’s possessed a strange power, although it could not destroy Winding Light Platform’s defensive methods, the power infiltrated the inside and caused severe damage to Winding Light Platform’s Gu worms!

Almost in an instant, Winding Light Platform was damaged to a great extent, the yellow beams of light that had been restricting Fang clan’s earth path Immortal Gu House lost their source of power and dispersed completely.

Wan clan’s first supreme elder almost spat blood from anger after seeing this.

“Fang clan, you have gone too far!” Wan clan’s first supreme elder immediately controlled Winding Light Platform to retreat.

He realized Fang clan was targeting him, more accurately, they were targeting Wan clan’s Immortal Gu House.

Compared to tall pine oasis, Winding Light Platform was Fang clan’s true objective.

Wan clan’s first supreme elder used all his strength to retreat.

But since Fang clan saw their real objective, why would they let it go so easily?

Under a normal situation, other Gu Immortals might not be able to block an Immortal Gu House’s charge and could only evade. But Fang Gong was an exception.

Fang Gong held down Winding Light Platform while Chicken Dog Coop also attacked.

After enduring for a while, Winding Light Platform crumbled apart loudly. Wan clan’s first supreme elder’s mind was filled with anger as he attacked Fang Gong.

Fang Gong’s expression was indifferent: “Wan clan’s first supreme elder, remember this moment. Our Fang clan is not to be trifled with, this Winding Light Platform is the price for going against us.”

Fang Gong punched lightly towards Wan clan’s first supreme elder while maintaining his momentum.

Wan clan’s first supreme elder only had rank seven cultivation, he simply could not catch Fang Gong’s attention.

But at the next moment, Wan clan’s first supreme elder’s expression suddenly stiffened. His killer move’s activation failed, causing him to get hit by an intense backlash, he was also struck by Fang Gong’s punch, he immediately turned into meat pulp, losing his life!

Everyone was stumped, including Fang Gong and Fang Di Chang.

“First supreme elder!!” Wan Xiao cried mournfully, he rode a wind falcon and took the chance to escape tall pine oasis.

His movement shook the Fang clan’s immortals as they regained their senses.

“What should we do now?” Fang Gong transmitted his voice to Fang Di Chang with an awkward expression.

Fang Di Chang’s expression was dark: “How could you kill Wan clan’s first supreme elder?”

This was different from their plan.

Fang clan’s true target was Wan clan’s Immortal Gu House. Wan clan had two Immortal Gu Houses, both were rank seven and could fight rank eight, they were the foundation which Wan clan relied on to be a super force. Their significance was far higher than that of tall pine oasis.

Getting rid of Winding Light Platform would be the greatest victory for Fang clan.

Fang clan’s prestige would rise sharply, no super force would dare to rashly unite against them again.

On the contrary, Wan clan would lose one of their rank seven Immortal Gu Houses, from then on, they could only hole up in their territory, unable to cause any more trouble.

But it was different now!

Wan clan’s first supreme elder was dead, this was a huge issue.

Wan clan would definitely retaliate with all their strength. They could use this reason to gather Western Desert’s righteous path forces and form a punitive expedition against Fang clan.

Because Fang clan had gone way beyond the limits.

Not only did they battle without prior notice, they even killed the other clan’s first supreme elder. It was like a neighbor suddenly crashing into someone’s home and killing its owner.

This action of Fang clan was completely a demonic path action. Righteous path forces would be frightened, afraid that they would be the next Wan clan.

Thereupon, Western Desert’s super forces would definitely unite.

“I already held back in that punch, but Wan clan’s first supreme elder was in an agitated state. He seemed to have triggered his killer move’s backlash, and by some freak coincidence, lost his life.” Fang Gong said with a sigh.

Although they won, Fang Gong was not happy.

Even the other Fang clan Gu Immortals felt a heavy mood, because all of them knew this matter was huge now.

Only one person was different.

Tang Fang Ming was hiding deep underground, excited and fearful.

“Amazing, this dream path killer move is truly amazing. Wan clan’s first supreme elder lost his life because of this, but Fang clan is completely unaware.”

“I have accomplished Lord Fang Yuan’s mission!”

[1] A type of food, Google for image.

Chapter 2250: Fang Yuan’s Scheme

Countless thoughts surged in Fang Di Chang’s mind like tall towers before quickly collapsing. The rising and collapsing of the thoughts for thousands of times caused Fang Di Chang to sweat profusely and his face to flush red.

Evidently, his wisdom path deductions reached his limits.

“This is bad, extremely bad!” Fang Di Chang mumbled with an ugly expression. All the results of the deductions let him see the miserable future of Fang clan.

Previously, Wan clan’s rallying failed, thus, Fang clan avoided a calamity, in truth, this was mainly because of the uncertain relationship of Fang clan and Fang Yuan.

Adding on that the five regional walls were gone and with the fusion of the two heavens, Gu Immortals were worried for their own safety and maintained caution.

However, Fang Di Chang was very clear of the true nature of Great Love Immortal Venerable.

If Fang clan were to be besieged by Western Desert’s super forces, Fang Yuan would never stand up for them.

Fang Yuan only prioritized real benefits!

Unless Fang clan paid a high price that moved Fang Yuan’s heart, he would never help Fang clan.

Like this time, Fang clan first had the intention of attacking Wan clan, before they secretly transacted with Fang Yuan.

Fang clan paid a lot of resource points to advance the rank of the core Immortal Gu of roof tile breaker killer move and exchanged for many Immortal Gu to construct that earth path Immortal Gu House.

If Fang Yuan did not help, Fang clan and Fang Yuan’s true relationship would be exposed, then Fang clan would face destruction.

Could Fang clan pay the price for Fang Yuan’s help?

Fang Di Chang had no confidence in this.

What made him more worried was that even if Fang clan could pay a high price to request for Fang Yuan’s assistance, what if the other super forces tried to imitate them, could Fang clan match their price?

“No matter what Fang clan chooses, Fang Yuan will be the biggest winner!” Fang Di Chang gritted his teeth as he thought.

Fang Yuan destroyed his body and captured his soul, Fang Di Chang could not forget this hatred.

“What should we do? This first supreme elder is really the shame of Wan clan, he actually fought so carelessly. Maybe, we can revive him?” Fang Gong suggested with a frown.

Fang Di Chang shook his head.

He had already thought of this, but they could not do it.

Not to mention that Fang clan did not have a method to revive Gu Immortals, they might need to request help from others to revive Wan clan’s first supreme elder.

Even if they succeeded in reviving Wan clan’s first supreme elder, would this grudge be gone?

It was similar to how Fang Di Chang was killed by Fang Yuan and his soul captured, but was released later on. Was the hatred between him and Fang Yuan gone?

How could that be possible!

This grudge deepened, on the contrary.

It could be said that the enmity between Fang clan and Wan clan was already impossible to resolve, Wan clan was definitely going to retaliate with their full strength.

Under this situation, were Fang clan to revive Wan clan’s first supreme elder, it would be like reviving their enemy who would give them more trouble in the future.

It was too stupid.

Naturally, Gu Immortals had endless methods. There were many ways to resolve the hatred.

For instance, the publicly known Spring Autumn Cicada. As long as the rebirth succeeded, everything could start anew.

There were also wisdom path methods to change the feelings of Wan clan’s immortals.

But these methods would need to be of an extremely high rank to be effective on all the Wan clan immortals, and Fang clan did not have them.

“Huff!” Fang Di Chang sighed, sharp light flashed past his eyes as he said heavily, “We can only continue to go forward now. We will go attack Wan clan’s headquarters and deal a huge blow to them!”

Fang Gong narrowed his eyes, while the other Fang clan Gu Immortals felt a chill in their hearts.

This matter had already become big, Fang clan would no doubt face huge trouble.

Since that was the case, there was no need to hesitate, they might as well disregard the consequences and weaken Wan clan as much as possible.

“Alright!” Fang Gong made the decision.

Fang clan immediately collected Chicken Dog Coop and got inside the earth path Immortal Gu House, moving towards Wan clan’s headquarters through the underground.

However, when they reached Wan clan’s headquarters, there was no one there.

Wan clan’s Gu Immortals had evacuated long ago, their remaining Immortal Gu House Myriad Age Building, as well as all the resources in the headquarters and treasuries were also completely gone.

Fang clan’s immortals were livid.

This was the worst situation for Fang clan!

After a while of silence, Fang Di Chang suggested: “First supreme elder, at this point, I can only ask you to move with Chicken Dog Coop and clean out Wan clan’s resource points. I will lead the others to go back to our headquarters and prepare for war!”

Fang Gong nodded: “I guess we have no choice.”

Fang Di Chang’s expression was extremely solemn: “For Fang clan to get past this trial, we must rely on Fang Yuan. The more resource points you can loot, the more Immortal Gu we can exchange from Fang Yuan and have greater hope.”

“I understand!” Fang Gong chose two people to go with him inside Chicken Dog Coop, they disappeared in the horizon.

Fang Di Chang led the remaining Fang clan immortals back to Fang clan’s headquarters in the earth path Immortal Gu House.

A storm was coming, everyone in Fang clan was tense, they were like tigers who sensed threats to their lives, hairs stood on ends and their eyes opened wide, as they prepared to oppose the retaliation of a group of savage beasts!

Eastern Sea.

A sea breeze was blowing, and birds were chirping.

Fang Yuan was calmly undergoing a Gu refinement attempt.

Inside sovereign immortal aperture, the refinement of rank nine Advance Refinement had reached the mid-late stage.

It was too easy!

This was Fang Yuan’s biggest impression, even though this was the refinement of a rank nine Immortal Gu.

It was completely different from the previous time.

This time, Fang Yuan was not under the external pressure brought by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, and Spectral Soul Demon Venerable. He also did not need to guard the heavenly spirit.

Another crucial point was Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus was a wood path Immortal Gu, but advance refinement Gu was a refinement path Immortal Gu. The latter came under Fang Yuan’s specialty.

It was much easier for him to process refinement path immortal materials than to handle wood path immortal materials.

Fang Yuan was even dealing with other matters while refining the rank nine Immortal Gu.

Fang clan’s message arrived quickly, and it contained a list.

The contents of the list were over ten resource points! It did not lack large resource points, and there was even a super resource point.

Over these days, Fang Gong displayed the strength of a rank eight Gu Immortal.

Fang Di Chang managed the overall situation, and even dispatched Inquiry Dock. Fang clan combed through Wan clan’s territories, occupying many of the resource points.

“Looks like Fang clan gained a lot. Sure enough, every person has potential. How can it appear if they are not pressured?”

Fang Yuan smiled lightly.

After Fang clan entered the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance, they made secret transactions.

By seeing the several Immortal Gu that Fang clan exchanged for, Fang Yuan could deduce Fang clan’s plan.

It was also reasonable for Fang clan to retaliate against Wan clan for self preservation.

Since Tang clan’s name was intentionally concealed by Fang Yuan, it was rather special for Fang Yuan to only be connected to Fang clan among all the Western Desert super forces.

Previously, Wan clan gathered Western Desert’s righteous path forces to attack Fang clan, this had already deeply provoked Fang clan.

Wan clan’s rally failed, Fang clan let out a breath of relief before deciding to take the chance to attack Wan clan. This was a sensible move of using offense as defense!

Fang Yuan immediately developed a plan when he noticed this. He manipulated the scene from behind, helping Fang clan with the Immortal Gu and raising their strength, while also sending a command to Tang clan, imparting a dream path killer move to Tang Fang Ming and also lending a dream path Immortal Gu.

Currently, Fang clan had already stepped into Fang Yuan’s trap, becoming the source of disturbance in Western Desert.

For self-preservation, they must cooperate with Fang Yuan even more deeply, seizing resource points for Fang Yuan.

On the other hand, Tang clan schemed against Fang clan, this was the same as Fang Yuan gaining a huge hold over them. Fang Yuan’s influence over Tang clan deepened much more.

In the letter, Fang clan asked for a lot of Immortal Gu, and also requested Fang Yuan to personally go to Western Desert and display the invincibility of Great Love Immortal Venerable if necessary! For this, Fang clan agreed to pay everything.

“They want me to make a move?” Fang Yuan sneered.

How could it be possible?

In the current situation of the contest of three venerables, Fang Yuan had to make the most of every moment. It was impossible for him to make a move for Fang clan.

He was using Fang clan, using them as a chess piece.

A chess piece was a chess piece, it should be sacrificed when necessary.

Unless the value of the chess piece was extremely high and could not be replaced, Fang Yuan would not go defend it personally.

Who among Fang Yuan’s subordinates could not be replaced?

No one!

Fang Yuan could even abandon his own clones without hesitation when necessary. Why would he make a move for Fang clan?

Heavenly Court.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had just started refining Heavenly Court’s wisdom path dao marks when an important message arrived.

“There is a change in Western Desert, Fang clan invaded Wan clan?” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s eyes flickered with starlights.

“There is something fishy about Fang clan being so radical. Did Fang Yuan secretly fuel the situation?” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable quickly thought of this detail, after all, the whole five regions knew about Fang clan openly joining the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance.

“Fang clan’s strength rose sharply, Fang Yuan clearly supported them from behind. Wan clan was caught unprepared, and Wan clan’s first supreme elder died in battle. Looks like Fang Yuan is intentionally causing unrest in Western Desert.”

“Fang clan is actually willing to be ordered like this by Fang Yuan, making a move that puts the clan’s survival in risk. It seems Fang Yuan’s influence over Fang clan is much deeper than I thought!”

“This is not good.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable frowned slightly.

She quickly sensed Fang Yuan’s true motive.

“Fang Yuan does not care about Fang clan, even though he needs the resource points to develop the sovereign immortal aperture, his main target is to set an example of Fang clan to influence the Gu Immortal world of the whole five regions and two heavens!”

Fang Yuan was a refinement path venerable, it was extremely easy for him to refine Immortal Gu.

With his investment, any super force’s strength would soar rapidly. It was the so-called ‘with a sharp weapon in hand, killing intent rises’; Fang Yuan’s simple transaction could break the power balance that had existed for a long time in the five regions’ Gu Immortal world.

At present, Western Desert super forces already understood the benefits of transacting with Fang Yuan.

On one hand, Fang Yuan was openly transacting Immortal Gu in treasure yellow heaven, and the price was affordable to the super forces. On the other hand, he created the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance, allowing any super force to join the alliance. Moreover, once they joined the alliance, they could transact secretly and obtain a lot of benefits.

Fang clan joined the alliance, so they could transact secretly and raise their strength. Now, Wan clan Gu Immortals did not even dare to show up, they could only let Fang clan loot almost all of their resource points.

This trend was truly dangerous!

The gains of Fang clan moved people, while the miserable state of Wan clan deterred them.

What could super forces do in this situation?

The simplest choice was to join the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance!

Chapter 2251: Heavenly Court’s Interference

All along, Fang Yuan’s foreign policy had been extremely flexible.

For instance, the content of the contribution board, mission board, and exchange board were different when comparing the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance and the sovereign immortal aperture.

Similarly, the Eastern Sea Gu Immortals had to accept strict alliance agreements when they joined the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance, but when the Gu Immortals of other four regions joined, their alliance agreements were extremely relaxed with almost no bindings.

Such details were enough for Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to learn of Fang Yuan’s sinister and vicious mind!

She had a clear judgment of Western Desert’s situation.

“Fang clan must be suppressed, they cannot be allowed to rise in power. If need be, they must be eradicated.”

“Otherwise, once other super forces start to imitate them, it will greatly increase Fang Yuan’s influence over the five regions!”

Fang Yuan relied on Immortal Gu transactions and other supporting methods to easily stir the situation of the five regions’ Gu Immortal world.

As the saying went, ‘humans die for wealth and birds die for food’.

If this situation was allowed to develop to become a common sentiment, then Fang Yuan’s influence would cover the five regions in the future. Even if not all the five regions were affected, it would at least influence three regions.

At that time, with just a thought, Fang Yuan could control the Gu Immortal world of Southern Border, Western Desert, and Eastern Sea to besiege Central Continent!

Naturally, no matter how many Gu Immortals the three regions had, they could not hold a candle to Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

A venerable was invincible, especially a venerable who was starting to exhibit the might of a Dao Lord.

But venerables could threaten each other.

If Fang Yuan’s influence made the three regions’ Gu Immortals into cannon fodder, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would have no choice but to make a move to protect Central Continent.

As such, there would be a change in the contest of three venerables.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would be hindered by those cannon fodder, while Fang Yuan could take the chance to surpass her.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was the number one wisdom path Gu Immortal since the ancient times. Fang Yuan’s scheme had just started, and she already saw through it from some small details!

“Currently, in the contest of three venerables, everyone is giving their all to refine natural dao marks. Fang Yuan is lagging behind, so he is using this trick to shorten the gap.”

“Hmph, will it go like you wish?”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable made a decision immediately: “Zhou Xiong Xin, Wan Zi Hong, go on an expedition to Western Desert!”

Western Desert.

Sun clan headquarters.

Sun clan’s first supreme elder was discussing with Wan Hao Guang and Wan Xiao.

“Fang clan attacked my Wan clan abruptly, they are seizing my Wan clan’s resource points in a frenzy, they have already gone mad. This act is completely of the demonic path, everyone in Fang clan has entered the demonic path, Fang clan is the biggest demon’s nest in Western Desert! Your clan is one of the core forces of Western Desert’s righteous path, can you stand by and watch this situation?” Wan Hao Guang said righteously.

Sun clan’s first supreme elder nodded and said: “You are right, my Sun clan will definitely use all our strength to maintain righteousness. But currently, Sun clan is in a bit of trouble...”

Sun clan’s first supreme elder explained Sun clan’s difficulty, he assured them at the end that if Wan clan was able to gather other super forces, Sun clan would definitely join and do their best for Western Desert.

“This old fox!” After leaving Sun clan’s headquarters, Wan Hao Guang said furiously.

Wan Xiao smiled bitterly: “Sun clan is the most timid among Western Desert’s super forces. It is not strange for Sun clan’s first supreme elder to say that. It is already his greatest sincerity to be here expressing his stance. Which clan should we go to next?”

Just as he was speaking, two figures flew over from the horizons, their rank eight aura clear and unconcealed.

“Who is it?”

“Ah, they are Heavenly Court Gu Immortals!”

Wan Xiao and Wan Hao Guang were on guard.

They were not afraid, after all, they had Myriad Age Building.

The two Heavenly Court immortals were Zhou Xiong Xin and Wan Zi Hong.

“Please hold on a moment, friends from Wan clan. We are here to help you.” Zhou Xiong Xin greeted from afar.

Wan Xiao and Wan Hao Guang looked at each other, seeing the joy in the depths of their eyes.

Immediately, the two stopped on the spot, hiding their joy while being on full alert.

The two Heavenly Court immortals stopped one thousand steps away, expressing they bore no ill intentions.

Wan Zi Hong did not speak, letting Zhou Xiong Xin explain their purpose in coming: “Fang clan joined the so-called Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance, and received support from Heaven Refining Demon Venerable. They want to overthrow Western Desert’s righteous path, and turn the whole of Western Desert into a demonic den. Although Heavenly Court is the leader of Central Continent, we cannot bear to watch this happen, so the two of us were sent to help and eliminate this demonic trend, in order to restore light to the world.”

Wan Hao Guang asked: “How will Heavenly Court help? Will Star Constellation Immortal Venerable make a move if necessary?”

These two questions were crucial.

Heavenly Court’s help was not a completely good thing for Wan clan, if it was not handled properly, it would be adding onto Wan clan’s troubles and they would be beyond redemption.

The reason?

Heavenly Court was Central Continent’s force, and this was Western Desert.

Although five regional walls had disappeared, how could the five regional walls that had existed from the beginning of the world disappear so easily from the Gu Immortals’ hearts?

If Heavenly Court were to personally interfere in Wan clan’s fight, Wan clan would be publicly recognized as Heavenly Court’s subordinate force, Central Continent’s bridgehead in Western Desert.

Under such a situation, Western Desert super forces would be vigilant and stay their hand. Wan clan would lose the reason for assembling the Western Desert super forces, and everyone would be on guard against them.

What was an internal battle between Western Desert forces, would become the battle of Fang Yuan and Fang clan against Heavenly Court and Wan clan.

Zhou Xiong Xin smiled: “You can rest assured, we will not personally take part in this campaign against Fang clan.”

Wan Hao Guang and Wan Xiao let out sighs of relief.

Heavenly Court Gu Immortals could not interfere directly.

Zhou Xiong Xin continued: “Wan clan’s and Fang clan’s fight is Western Desert’s internal matter. The reason Heavenly Court is willing to help Wan clan is to deal with Heaven Refining Demon Venerable Fang Yuan. If Fang Yuan makes a move or sends his subordinates to participate in the battle, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable will not stand by and do nothing, our Heavenly Court’s immortals will also make a move to defend righteousness and ensure peace in the world!”

Wan Hao Guang and Wan Xiao could not restrain their joy.

Since the start, what they were most wary of was the relationship between Fang clan and Fang Yuan. If Fang Yuan made a move, which Western Desert super force could block him?

No one!

Heavenly Court’s guarantee immediately removed Wan clan’s greatest apprehension.

When Wan clan rallied Western Desert forces later on, and these forces learned of this situation, they would definitely help Wan clan.

Wan Xiao questioned: “Fang clan joined the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance, and used resource points to exchange for a large number of Immortal Gu, even constructing a new Immortal Gu House. They are crazily relocating our resource points now, their intention is clear as day. So, can Heavenly Court sell us some Immortal Gu?”

Wan Hao Guang also looked at the two Heavenly Court immortals with bright eyes.

Zhou Xiong Xin sneered inwardly: “Wishful thinking! Immortal Gu are unique, there are barely enough Immortal Gu for us to use, how can we sell them?”

On the surface, however, he showed a smile: “We cannot sell Immortal Gu, but we can lend them. On the other hand, we can consider transacting immortal killer moves and Immortal Gu recipes.”

Zhou Xiong Xin then gave a quote which immediately caused Wan Xiao’s and Wan Hao Guang’s expressions to become unsightly.

Heavenly Court’s price was high, Wan clan’s wallet would bleed if they wanted to reach that price.

“Heavenly Court’s righteousness comes at a price.” Zhou Xiong Xin suddenly said with a low voice, “In fact, Heavenly Court will give financial support that will certainly satisfy your clan.”

“Oh? We would like to hear the details.”

Eastern Sea.

Fang Yuan was communicating with Heavenly Lord Bai Zu.

“Bai Zu, you clearly cultivate enslavement path, why are you asking me to refine blood path Gu?” Fang Yuan deliberately asked.

Far away in Northern Plains, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was smiling bitterly.

He mumbled internally: “You think I want to do this?”

But he had no choice.

For the blood path Immortal Gu transaction, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable personally summoned Heavenly Lord Bai Zu to make him a middle man for the transaction.

How could Heavenly Lord Bai Zu refuse?

He was only a meager rank eight Gu Immortal, and his clan was established in Northern Plains. He had no choice but to agree to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s command.

As the saying went, people had to be humble when they were in an inferior position.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu naturally resented Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, at the same time, he also resented Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan’s speech as Great Love shook the whole world. He publicized his connection with the five regions’ Gu Immortals and forces, among them, the transaction with Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was completely made up.

Back then, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu had been so frightened that he even burnt his skewer!

Fang Yuan wanted to use this to incite and probe Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s response. Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s ideal was hereditary monarchy, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was not his bloodline descendant, Bai Zu tribe was also being ostracized and suppressed by Huang Jin tribes.

This was Fang Yuan’s incitement plan, maybe it could make Huang Jin tribes ally and exterminate Bai Zu tribe?

Naturally, the possibility was small, the world did not lack smart people.

But Fang Yuan’s plan was extremely low cost, it took just a few words.

And how would he know if he did not try?

So, a grand rank eight Gu Immortal Heavenly Lord Bai Zu had to live in fear and anxiety, afraid of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable picking on him.

In the end, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable really did pick on him, giving him a mission.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s attitude was clear: Aren’t you, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, close with Fang Yuan? Then, be my middleman and transact blood path Immortal Gu. Use your actions and results to prove your sincerity to me, Longevity Heaven, and the entire righteous path of Northern Plains!

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu felt wronged!

When did he have a close relationship with Fang Yuan?

It was clearly Chu Du who was linked to Fang Yuan. What did it have to do with him, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu? He had even fought Fang Yuan before.

He wanted to prove his innocence, but Giant Sun Immortal Venerable simply did not talk about this, and only wanted him to receive the task.

In fact, from Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s point of view, there were very few people who could take on this task. Longevity Heaven and the Huang Jin tribes’ Gu Immortals were out of the question because they represented Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu and Chu Du were different, however.

“Lord Fang Yuan, you are Great Love Immortal Venerable, why do you need to make fun of a minor character like me.” Heavenly Lord Bai Zu put himself in a low position, “How can a wise hero like you not know of my situation?”

Fang Yuan laughed heartily: “What blood path Immortal Gu do you want?”

Chapter 2252: Rank Nine Advance Refinement Gu!

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had instructed Heavenly Lord Bai Zu: If possible, try your best to obtain all of Fang Yuan’s blood path Immortal Gu!

But Heavenly Lord Bai Zu naturally could not say that right now, so he mentioned ten Immortal Gu.

Fang Yuan sneered when he received the message.

Among these Immortal Gu, there were Bloodline, Blood Asset, Blood Skull, and Blood Qi.

Fang Yuan possessed bloodline Gu.

This Immortal Gu had been Wu clan’s property. Back when Fang Yuan disguised as Wu Yi Hai, Wu clan had even used this bloodline Gu to test Fang Yuan.

Later, Fang Yuan scammed them and became its owner.

It was not difficult for Giant Sun Immortal Venerable to know of this information.

Fang Yuan also had blood asset Immortal Gu.

This was a unique Gu created by Lang Ya land spirit by combining some blood path Gu recipes he bought in treasure yellow heaven.

Fang Yuan smoothly obtained it from Lang Ya Sect.

Currently, blood asset Immortal Gu was already raised from rank six to rank eight. It was one of the core Immortal Gu of Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool, as one of the four elements, it was extremely important.

Blood skull Immortal Gu was also with Fang Yuan!

Fang Yuan originally possessed rank four blood skull mortal Gu, and he had once used it to raise his aptitude.

But the price of using blood skull mortal Gu was very high, the Gu Master had to kill enough blood-related kin to raise their aptitude.

In Qing Mao Mountain, Fang Yuan slaughtered almost the whole of Gu Yue village to raise his aptitude.

At Gu Immortal level, the price of using blood skull Gu to raise aptitude rose explosively. To Gu Immortals who acted alone, blood skull Gu was of little use.

But to a force, blood skull Gu was extremely significant.

Fang Yuan could not obtain benefits from blood skull Gu, but others could.

The memories from the five hundred years of his previous life told him that blood skull Immortal Gu’s true inheritance was destroyed because of the changes in the world.

So, before the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, when he helped many Gu Immortals undergo immortal ascension, he used the natural inspiration to ask for a rather intact blood skull Immortal Gu recipe.

Together with his deductions, he created a blood skull Immortal Gu recipe.

Fang Yuan easily refined blood skull Immortal Gu with this Immortal Gu recipe.

Like he expected, blood skull Immortal Gu’s effect was still to raise aptitude. Because it was an Immortal Gu, it was effective on Gu Immortals. The flaw was still the same requirement of killing blood-related kin. The higher the cultivation level of the Gu Immortal, the larger the number of people they needed to kill, they even had to kill Gu Immortal relatives!

As for blood qi Immortal Gu, it was also in Fang Yuan’s hands.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue obtained blood qi Immortal Gu true inheritance, and had transacted the Immortal Gu recipe with Fang Yuan.

After Demon Immortal Qi Jue died, Fang Yuan refined it.

Currently, it was only at rank six.

Besides this, Fang Yuan also had other blood path Immortal Gu. For instance, blood trace Gu and blood oath Gu.

These two blood path Immortal Gu were created by Eastern Sea’s blood path demonic immortals Ding Yan and Ding Qi. One was used for investigation, and the other could achieve the effect of information path.

Fang Yuan did not obtain these two Immortal Gu recipes from Ding Yan and Ding Qi, but he knew these two Immortal Gu were destroyed.

Using natural inspiration, he asked for complete Immortal Gu recipes, and adding on his own deductions, he refined them.

“I will be honest with you, Bai Zu. I have many blood path Immortal Gu.” Fang Yuan said.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu immediately praised: “Lord Fang Yuan is well-prepared and farsighted. As a refinement path venerable, you are the number one expert in refinement path in history. I am in deep admiration.”

Fang Yuan chuckled: “If you want to trade Immortal Gu, then exchange for it with the Primordial Domain extraction method.”

Before Heavenly Lord Bai Zu looked for Fang Yuan, he was instructed by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable. Back then, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable told him about the Primordial Domain extraction method.

In Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s mind, Fang Yuan desired a method to retrieve the Primordial Domain. This was quite clear, just look at treasure yellow heaven, Fang Yuan’s portion of the Primordial Domain was still stored there.

Fang Yuan had not taken it out even now, it could be judged that he had no way to extract it.

So, this method was the greatest bargaining chip to purchase the blood path Immortal Gu and could be made use of!

“As expected, Fang Yuan immediately mentioned the method to take out Primordial Domain, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable guessed correctly!” Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was excited inwardly, his trepidation also disappeared for the most part.

He intentionally remained silent for a while before responding: “The Primordial Domain extraction method?”

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu pretended to be in a difficult position.

Fang Yuan snorted coldly: “Don’t try any tricks, since you have been sent by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, didn’t he instruct you?”

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu’s mind shook as he quickly corrected his attitude: “Lord Fang Yuan is wise and mighty, please forgive my impudence.”

Fang Yuan gave a light nod: “Then use the Primordial Domain extraction method to purchase one blood path Immortal Gu.”

“Wh... what?” Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was shaken, Fang Yuan was so absurd and greedy that he did not even dare to believe those words.

“Lord Fang Yuan, I think the Primordial Domain extraction method is extremely valuable and can definitely be exchanged for ten blood path Immortal Gu.” Heavenly Lord Bai Zu said quickly.

Fang Yuan sneered: “Hehe, you are actually so absurd and greedy, do you have no shame!”

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu: “...”

Fang Yuan simply did not require any Primordial Domain extraction method, he was just teasing Heavenly Lord Bai Zu while refining advance refinement Gu.

Inside sovereign immortal aperture, tens of long rivers were flying in the sky.

Every river was filled with all kinds of immortal materials.

The river streams converged sometimes, and separated at other times.

To refine rank nine advance refinement Gu, Fang Yuan was mainly using the water refinement technique.

Rank eight water refinement Immortal Gu—one of the core Immortal Gu of Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool—had been activated since the start of the refinement.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu came to his senses and started to raise the price: “Lord Fang Yuan, you are clear of my sincerity. You also know that the Primordial Domain extraction method is extremely rare. This Primordial Domain extraction method is valuable to you, and it is what you need the most currently. Just ten blood path Immortal Gu are not of any significance to you. You are a refinement path venerable, isn’t it a simple matter to refine any Immortal Gu for you?”

Fang Yuan scoffed, his attitude turning cold quickly: “Back then, I transacted Primordial Domain with Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, shouldn’t he have handed the Primordial Domain extraction method as well? Now, I can’t even take it out, I have yet to settle the accounts with him, but he is actually shameless enough to sell this thing? Could it be that I, a grand refinement path venerable, cannot deduce a rank nine refinement path killer move to handle the Primordial Domain as an immortal material and extract it?”

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu quickly said: “Lord Fang Yuan, please quell your anger.”

“Shut up.” Fang Yuan continued, “Go tell Giant Sun this, I rushed to refine blood path Immortal Gu to intentionally make things difficult for him. He wants to dual cultivate blood path? Hehe, I will continue to refine even more blood path Immortal Gu ahead of him! Unless he hands over the Primordial Domain extraction method to me and shows me his sincerity.”

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu did not dare to talk anymore. He heaved a sigh and contacted Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

After Giant Sun Immortal Venerable learned of the event, he immediately scolded: “That kid Fang Yuan is really arrogant, actually daring to threaten me. Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, you are also trash, showing such a cowering attitude! Don’t you know that you are negotiating with Fang Yuan as my representative?”

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu could only say: “Lord Giant Sun, it is my mistake! I am not of Huang Jin bloodline and my ability is meager...”

“Alright.” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable interrupted him, “It is because you are not of Huang Jin bloodline and have meager ability that I am giving these opportunities to you to temper yourself and increase your ability.”

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu: “...”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable continued: “Continue to negotiate with Fang Yuan, the Primordial Domain extraction method... I won’t hand it over for free. Tell Fang Yuan that in the contest of three venerables, his progress is the slowest and he has the least immortal essence. Tell him to assess the situation, cooperating with me will give him great benefits and fill up the gap. A wise person should be aware of their situation.”

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu asked: “If so, Lord Giant Sun, how many blood path Immortal Gu should I exchange the Primordial Domain extraction method for?”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was silent for a bit.

Hearing Heavenly Lord Bai Zu’s words, Fang Yuan’s plan was to use his refinement path venerable foundation to deduce a rank nine killer move to extract Primordial Domain.

Although this method was time consuming, it was a feasible method indeed.

Thereupon, the Primordial Domain extraction method could not be priced too high.

But regarding the price, in Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s opinion, the higher the better.

In the end, he chided Heavenly Lord Bai Zu: “It will depend on your effort to see how many blood path Immortal Gu you can exchange for, and that will show your sincerity to Longevity Heaven. Go, I am watching your performance.”

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu felt stifled under the enormous pressure. He contacted Fang Yuan once again.

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture, some issues emerged in the handling of refinement path immortal materials.

Fang Yuan was carefully separating the rivers, while removing several of them.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu said with a smile: “Lord Fang Yuan, there is really no way to offer the Primordial Domain extraction method as a gift. But since you feel ten blood path Immortal Gu is too much, how about... eight?”

Fang Yuan did not have the mood to talk with Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, he chided immediately: “Junior Bai Zu, how can I, a grand venerable, haggle with you? You think I am a mortal merchant?”

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu cursed inwardly, while immediately saying: “I won’t dare to!”

Fang Yuan continued: “Let’s put aside the matter of the Primordial Domain extraction method. Since you want to purchase blood path Immortal Gu, offer more of the Primordial Domain.”

“This...”

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu wanted to say something but was interrupted by Fang Yuan: “What are you standing dazedly for? Can you decide it? Why aren’t you returning to ask for instructions?”

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu’s anger was soaring. He, a mighty rank eight Gu Immortal, had been turned into a messenger.

And the communicating parties happened to be venerables, he could not afford to offend them!

He could only swallow this grievance and look for Giant Sun Immortal Venerable again.

“This is indeed Fang Yuan, a guy with infinite greed.” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable laughed.

He had a lot of the Primordial Domain. The Primordial Domain had little value to him, after all, he did not have the sovereign immortal body.

Currently, it was already Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s limit to cultivate luck path and blood path.

But Giant Sun Immortal Venerable could use the Primordial Domain to cultivate his subordinates.

“It is not impossible to transact them with Fang Yuan...” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable pondered for a while before informing Heavenly Lord Bai Zu of this decision.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu contacted Fang Yuan once again.

“Lord Fang Yuan, lord?”

He tried to contact many times, but Fang Yuan simply ignored him.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu: “...”

At this moment, inside the sovereign immortal aperture, tens of rivers had merged, raising countless ripples.

A completely new advance refinement Gu rose from the vast river.

Advance Refinement had reached rank nine!

Chapter 2253: Internal Worry, External Threat

“Rank nine advance refinement Gu...” Fang Yuan inspected carefully and found that the appearance was not much different from its previous rank eight version.

However, it had already undergone a qualitative change!

This was Fang Yuan’s second rank nine Immortal Gu, it would provide a huge help to Fang Yuan.

Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool would also rise to become a rank nine Immortal Gu House because of this.

A rank nine Immortal Gu House!

Such Immortal Gu Houses were few even in the whole history of humanity.

Heavenly Court’s Heaven Overseeing Tower was the most famous Gu House. Unfortunately, with the destruction of rank nine fate Gu, it could not be constructed again.

“Once I finish with the modifications, rank nine advance refinement Gu can be placed in Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool once again, thereby allowing this Immortal Gu House to also experience a qualitative change. If there was a ranking list for Immortal Gu Houses, it would be at first place for sure.”

Fang Yuan evaluated in his mind.

If it was before, Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool might be at the same ranking as Divine Emperor City, but as long as it became a true rank nine, it would suppress Divine Emperor City stably.

After all, Divine Emperor City did not have a rank nine Immortal Gu.

Naturally, Fang Yuan needed to modify the previous Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool, to make it suitable for rank nine advance refinement Immortal Gu.

Fang Yuan was a refinement path venerable, a supreme grandmaster in refinement path, it was not hard for him to modify this.

Fang Yuan placed advance refinement Immortal Gu aside and inspected himself.

Just like he expected, because of the second rank nine Immortal Gu, the fishing net-like heaven path dao marks left on him by the killer move obscured heavenly secret were being expended at almost double the speed of before!

This showed that rank nine advance refinement Gu would provide an enormous help to Fang Yuan.

It had a huge significance as it could influence many subsequent matters.

It would be much easier for Fang Yuan to raise the rank of other rank eight Immortal Gu from now on.

“Fortunately, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable have expended a lot of immortal essence, they also need to use their remaining immortal essence to refine natural dao marks. They will not inspect frequently like before, this will greatly reduce the pressure on obscured heavenly secret.”

Fang Yuan was aware that obscured heavenly secret was already reaching its limits at this stage.

If Fang Yuan wanted to refine a third rank nine Immortal Gu, obscured heavenly secret might help him conceal it during the early stage, but it would not be able to keep on concealing it at the mid-late stage. The effect of the killer move would dissipate completely.

“So, should I refine or not? If I am to refine the third rank nine Immortal Gu, which should I refine?”

Fang Yuan calmed down and analyzed the situation.

He was now facing problems both internally and externally!

The internal problem was the instability of the sovereign immortal aperture.

Because of non-conflicting dao marks, abnormal situations kept on occurring, causing the whole immortal aperture’s ecology to be unstable.

Because of the severe loss of subordinates in the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, there were few Gu Immortals in the sovereign immortal aperture, and they were barely able to stabilize the situation.

Secondly were calamities and tribulations.

Even venerables needed to undergo tribulation.

Among the three venerables, it was extremely difficult for Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to change the time flow of their immortal aperture using time path methods because of conflicting dao marks.

Fang Yuan, however, sped his time flow twice when raising the rank of Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus.

For this, his time path clone, He Chun Qiu’s time path foundation was almost entirely used up.

For some time, Fang Yuan would not be able to change the sovereign immortal aperture’s rate of time. If he did it again, it would lead to a series of changes, abnormal situations would erupt frequently and form into a terrifying tribulation that would cover the whole of the sovereign immortal aperture.

This was because a time path killer move that could transform the whole sovereign immortal aperture had to be of an extremely high rank. To be effective, many time path dao marks had to be engraved or modified.

The sudden change in these time path dao marks would create a chain reaction in the sovereign immortal aperture, leading to unpredictable changes and ultimately causing severe losses.

If a loss occurred, it would have an enormous impact on him.

Previously, Fang Yuan used Landscape as Before along with the year essence pools as recovery methods, but they could not be used now.

Because the water of the River of Time in the year essence pools had poured in just recently. The essence of this method were still the time path dao marks.

The abnormal situations that erupted because of the disorderly time path dao marks would make the usage of any time path dao marks aggravate the situation.

“To reduce the danger of this, I need to construct a time path dao vein at least!”

The third internal problem was the sovereign immortal body’s food.

Fang Yuan’s sovereign immortal body was created from sovereign immortal fetus Gu, it needed to feed on similarly ranked immortal apertures every set interval of time.

Fang Yuan’s cultivation was rank nine now, so he needed to devour rank nine immortal apertures!

Looking at it from this point, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable were Fang Yuan’s food.

But the difficulty in this was enormous.

Naturally, Fang Yuan was prepared.

He schemed against the revived Paradise Earth in Crazed Demon Cave. Before Paradise Earth died, he was only a slight distance away from rank nine, his corpse still had a rank eight immortal aperture.

This rank eight immortal aperture was at quasi-rank nine level. Moreover, because Paradise Earth cultivated heaven path, this immortal aperture displayed a unique style, it could actually form into an independent entity that was extremely stable.

Normally speaking, when a Gu Immortal died, their immortal aperture would be unstable and fall on the world, opening their immortal aperture entrance to absorb a large amount of heaven and earth qi, to form either a blessed land or a grotto-heaven.

But Paradise Earth’s quasi-rank nine heaven path immortal aperture was special, it was stable.

“If it becomes hopeless in the future, I will split my soul to use Paradise Earth’s body to create a heaven path clone. Then, let this clone undergo tribulation to become a heaven path venerable, then devour its rank nine immortal aperture!”

Paradise Earth’s corpse was Fang Yuan’s future food.

Naturally, doing this was quite wasteful.

If possible, Fang Yuan would prefer having a heaven path venerable clone to assist him!

The three main internal problems were: sovereign immortal aperture, calamities and tribulations, and food. Besides these, Fang Yuan also had external problems.

The external problems were the venerables.

Fang Yuan had quietly refined two rank nine Immortal Gu, this was his greatest advantage now. But other venerables also had their advantages.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had refined the most dao marks among the three venerables!

In his territory, he could fight against two others and even gain an upper hand.

The amplification from the outside world’s dao marks was too huge.

And although Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was below Giant Sun Immortal Venerable in this aspect, the scale of her refined wisdom path dao marks clearly surpassed Fang Yuan’s.

Moreover, Fang Yuan could guess Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was modifying her killer moves.

Fang Yuan had almost no foundation in this aspect.

He had two newly refined rank nine Immortal Gu, but he had no complementary killer moves to use with them.

Fang Yuan’s own skill in deducing killer moves was far below Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s.

Were the three venerables to fight now, Fang Yuan’s two rank nine Immortal Gu could not provide direct help.

There was another point of the two venerables that Fang Yuan envied.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had Longevity Heaven, while Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had Heavenly Court.

The two venerables had their own headquarters, as long as they hid inside, they would receive a huge amplification and show the might of a Dao Lord!

Even if the other two venerables allied sincerely, they would be without options.

This gave them each an impenetrable fortress!

Even if the situation were to crumble apart, as long as they had their headquarters, they would have a foothold and hope to counterattack.

Fang Yuan, however, did not have it.

The sovereign immortal aperture was unstable, how could he dare to use it as a battlefield?

He really could not compare to the other two venerables in this aspect. After all, the two venerables had the accumulation of their past lives, while Fang Yuan was not even a rank eight Gu Immortal in the five hundred years of his previous life.

The main reason was because in Fang Yuan’s previous five hundred years, fate Gu still existed. Heaven’s will made arrangements for him, and venerables had their own arrangements, Fang Yuan had no ability to go against them.

So, once Fang Yuan lost, he would not have a place to take shelter.

Fang Yuan thought for a long while, but could not come to a decision.

There was a tough decision in front of him.

He could choose to refine or not, both would have a great impact on his following actions.

For instance, if he refined a rank nine Immortal Gu that could be used directly in a fight, Fang Yuan might make a move to suppress the other venerables, consume their immortal essence and enlarge his immortal essence advantage.

If he did not refine it, obscured heavenly secret could still hold on for some time. Using this chance, Fang Yuan could secretly accumulate even more advantages.

It depended on Fang Yuan’s choice.

“I don’t have enough information...”

Fang Yuan heaved a deep sigh.

Unlike the concluded battle in Crazed Demon Cave, venerables had the time to develop now. Their trump cards and methods had already changed.

With the situation being unclear, it was not easy to make a decision!

Another advantage of choosing a direct confrontation was that information could be forcefully obtained.

But Fang Yuan felt the plan of suppressing two venerables at the same time was somewhat unreliable. They had their own territories, and if the two venerables were forced to join hands, could Fang Yuan handle it?

As the contest of three venerables prolonged, the importance of information became even more prominent.

Fang Yuan, however, was not specialized in this aspect.

Information path was most specialized in gathering information, and Fang Yuan never had a notable accomplishment in information path.

This did not mean he did not have any progress in information path.

Although Li Xiao Bai had been entrusted with the hope of information path back then, he was just an idle chess piece now. Fang Yuan’s current foundation was still effective in gathering information on ordinary Gu Immortals or super forces.

But his attainment in information path had never caught up with his development.

Now that he was dealing with two venerables, this aspect appeared quite weak.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable inspected him, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable deduced him, but Fang Yuan had no way to make any counterattacks.

Just as Fang Yuan was pondering deeply, the situation in Western Desert was changing rapidly.

Wan Xiao, Wan Zi Hong, Sun Wang, as well as Wan Zi Hong, Zhou Xiong Xin and the rest arrived in Xiao clan’s headquarters blessed land.

“I already know of your purpose in coming. Fang clan has gone mad and fallen into the demonic path, they are the shame of Western Desert’s righteous path. My Xiao clan is willing to help Wan clan to recover your lost territory!” Xiao Ye Hu expressed the stance of Xiao clan clearly.

Wan clan’s group formed an alliance with Xiao clan smoothly.

After a round of discussion, Wan clan was willing to cede resource points like visualization oasis, perfume flying island, and black-yellow earth pool. Xiao clan would dispatch Xiao Ye Hu and several other Xiao clan experts.

At the same time, Heavenly Court supported them with immortal essence stones. Moreover, Heavenly Court guaranteed that if Heaven Refining Demon Venerable made a move, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would definitely appear to obstruct him and protect Western Desert’s righteous path forces.

With Zhou Xiong Xin’s and Wan Zi Hong’s active participation, a righteous path alliance against Fang clan was forming rapidly!

Chapter 2254: I Want To Sleep

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

Mini Western Desert.

Mermaid immortal Yu Zi’s expression was pale, she panted while looking at the flying sand tunnel in front of her.

“It is finally set up.” Yu Zi mumbled.

Rockman Gu Immortal Shi San Bai thanked her: “Yu Zi, you specialize in water path, setting up this kind of earth path resource point is truly hard on you. I could not have accomplished this by myself.”

Rockmen were most specialized in earth path.

This was their racial talent.

Originally, Shi San Bai and Shi Gua Bi had agreed to finish the mission of setting up the earth path resource points.

But not long ago, Fang Yuan suddenly sent a command and dispatched several rockman Gu Immortals out of the sovereign immortal aperture.

Shi San Bai had no other options but to wait for others to team up with him.

In the end, he teamed up with Yu Zi.

Although Yu Zi specialized in water path, she was a rank seven Gu Immortal after all.

With Shi San Bai as the leader and Yu Zi as the support, the two cooperated and spent close to ten days to set up this resource point, finishing the mission.

Seeing Shi San Bai expressing his gratitude, Yu Zi gave a humble reply with a polite attitude.

She had her own plans, in fact.

“Resource points like flying sand tunnel can be used as earth vein nodes.”

“Lord Fang Yuan’s clone will personally come to set up an immortal formation in this resource point to change it into one of the earth vein nodes.”

“This is the chance for me to meet Lord Fang Yuan!”

When Yu Zi saw Fang Yuan’s main body, her determination had been shaken. But she had gotten over it during this period of time.

She did not have any extravagant hope of building a relationship with Fang Yuan’s main body, so her attention was placed on Fang Yuan’s clones.

As long as she could connect to Fang Yuan, becoming one of his fiancées, the merman race’s status would immediately be stable and unshakable.

Moreover, with this relationship, the merman race would obtain powerful protection for their development.

It was because she had this plot, Yu Zi took on this mission and came to cooperate with Shi San Bai.

A figure suddenly appeared in the horizon.

“Lord Wu Shuai is here!” Shi San Bai showed a respectful expression.

“He is here, Wu Shuai is Fang Yuan’s dragonman clone.” Yu Zi’s heartbeat accelerated as she encouraged herself inwardly.

It was up to her to fight for the merman race’s future.

Yu Zi quickly checked her appearance, this time, she was wearing a rare and precious pearl necklace that constantly let out the light scent of sea wind. Her elaborate robe showed off her alluring figure, and the bright fish scales gave off a feeling of being unblemished.

Yu Zi nodded in satisfaction inwardly and encouraged herself. She looked around and had a light smile on her face as she tried her best to show a captivating expression.

Shi San Bai was dumbstruck, immediately understanding the mermaid immortal’s plan.

When Wu Shuai arrived above flying sand tunnel, Yu Zi said softly: “Greetings to Lord Wu Shuai!”

This voice made Shi San Bai feel a chill. He also quickly paid his greetings.

Wu Shuai glanced at them and nodded lightly before activating an investigative killer move to carefully inspect the flying sand tunnel.

After three rounds of inspection, Wu Shuai said contentedly: “Not bad, you have done a good job in setting up this flying sand tunnel.”

After saying so, Wu Shuai started controlling Immortal Gu, mortal Gu, and many immortal materials as he began to set up an immortal formation.

Yu Zi carefully sized Wu Shuai up. He was muscular and handsome, he had a tall nose bridge and firm lips. He looked like a peerless hero.

His pupils were the color of amber, he had a pair of golden spiral horns, especially his pure-gold dragon scales that shone dazzlingly, they suited the merfolk sense of aesthetic beauty.

“Lord Fang Yuan really has peerless beauty!” Yu Zi admired inwardly.

The beauty of Fang Yuan’s main body was a kind of a shock to her, she had a feeling that she could only worship and look up to it, making her feel inferior. While Wu Shuai’s heroic appearance moved her heart.

After several hours, Wu Shuai finished setting up the immortal formation.

“Lord Wu Shuai really has amazing methods, you can set up the immortal formation with such little effort.” Yu Zi immediately praised.

Wu Shuai smiled: “I can’t draw a conclusion yet, I need to see the actual effect. Move back and take care of your safety.”

The first activation of a newly constructed formation was rather dangerous. If the killer move were to fail, it would lead to a backlash. The immortal formation would break apart, and not only would it inflict a backlash on the Gu Immortal, it would also cause a violent change in the surroundings.

After all the formation was closely connected to its surroundings.

Especially a large formation over a resource point like this, once it broke apart, the violent change due to the massively concentrated dao marks in the resource point would cause even higher damage. It was even more so in an environment like that of the sovereign immortal aperture.

This was derived from experience.

There were already several failures in the arrangement of immortal formations, which caused dao marks to turn chaotic and the surroundings to change intensely. The loss of the resource points was a small matter, they even resulted in terrifying abnormal situations!

Wu Shuai activated the formation carefully.

He cultivated enslavement path after all. The reason he could set up the formation was because he shared attainment levels with the main body.

So, if there was a mistake in the formation, it would be hard for Wu Shuai to deal with it with his methods as he was not a formation path Gu Immortal.

The immortal formation began to activate. Nothing unexpected happened for the moment.

Wu Shuai’s eyes were bright as torches without any signs of relaxing.

After a few breaths of time, Yu Zi finally could not endure it, she bravely approached Wu Shuai and said with a revering expression: “Lord Wu Shuai, this immortal formation seems to have no issue.”

Wu Shuai did not look at her, he sniffed the air and frowned slightly: “What is this smell?”

Yu Zi was joyous and was just about to say shyly that this was the fragrance of her pearls.

But right at this moment, there was an explosion!

A large amount of stench qi gushed out of the flying sand tunnel.

Around ten li of the surroundings immediately became filled with a foul smell. Yu Zi’s expression was pale, she nearly vomited.

The fragrance of her pearls was completely drowned, moreover, the pure-white pearl necklace was dyed black.

Wu Shuai laughed loudly: “You don’t need to worry, this is earth stench qi. The method of relocating this flying sand tunnel was not good enough, so these accumulated stench qi collected inside the tunnel. But it is alright now, this formation has discharged them, there are no hidden threats left.”

“Congratulations, Lord Wu Shuai!” Shi San Bai quickly cheered.

Yu Zi also praised while enduring the stench: “This is all due to Lord Wu Shuai’s extraordinary methods.”

She approached him courageously once again, trying her hardest to attract Wu Shuai’s gaze.

But right at this time, sandy rocks shot out of the flying sand tunnel.

These sandy rocks were filled with moisture, thus the stench they emitted was even worse than the earth stench qi.

Lumps of sandy rocks flew to the air before falling down to the surrounding area with splattering sounds.

Just like...

Just like taking a dump.

Yu Zi looked at the sandy rocks that filled the sky, she felt despair.

In this situation, no matter how beautiful she was, Wu Shuai would not be moved.

After the sandy rocks fell for a while, it became normal again.

A large amount of fine, dry sand grains shot out of the flying sand tunnel. The sand grains flew up to one hundred or so feet high before sprinkling down on the ground like a drizzle.

This was flying sand, it had a soft texture, it was an immortal material.

Although it was only a rank six immortal material, the grains were in high quantities.

Under the effect of the formation, the flying sand tunnel had become one of the earth vein nodes.

Wu Shuai nodded contentedly and said in a joyous tone: “Now, the second ring of the earth vein is finished. Although we were also at second ring before the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, the nodes in that second ring were far fewer than the present scale.”

“I am sure this world will keep getting better!” Yu Zi added in agreement.

Wu Shuai glanced at her, then glanced at Shi San Bai before flying away.

Yu Zi and Shi San Bai quickly bade him farewell.

Only when Wu Shuai had disappeared in the horizons, did Yu Zi take back her gaze and sighed deeply, unable to hide her deep disappointment.

Shi San Bai laughed inwardly, he knew the mermaid’s plan but did not look down on her.

Mermen had already lived in the sovereign immortal aperture for some time now, this period of time was neither long nor short. The mermaid immortals were meticulous in their tasks, and almost all the Gu Immortals knew of them.

In Shi San Bai’s opinion, the weak relying on the strong to survive was a wise plan.

He did not feel any hostility, after all, rockmen were all male, they were simply not in the competition.

So, Shi San Bai feigned ignorance: “I am going to continue setting up another earth path resource point. Fairy Yu Zi, are you willing to continue teaming up with me?”

Shi San Bai naturally hoped to have an earth path Gu Immortal as an ally, but the manpower in the sovereign immortal aperture was truly in shortage right now.

Yu Zi had already worked with him, they had a certain level of tacit cooperation.

Yu Zi asked for the details, before refusing Shi San Bai politely while showing a difficult expression.

The next earth path resource point could not be treated as an earth vein node, that meant Yu Zi could not see Fang Yuan’s clone, so she did not have any incentive to do it.

Shi San Bai understood, suggesting: “From what I see, you should take a rest.”

Yu Zi felt somewhat strange, a thought emerging in her mind: “The Gu Immortals in the sovereign immortal aperture actually rest?”

Yu Zi had lived here for some time, she had already recognized what workaholics the Gu Immortals here were, they did not know what rest was.

This was the first time she heard the word ‘rest’ from a Gu Immortal here.

Shi San Bai laughed: “This is my own experience. The mission board will never be empty, in fact, there are endless missions, but we are short on manpower. Most of the time, we might not be proficient in the mission, but we have no choice but to force ourselves to finish them.”

“It is like how you cultivate water path and had to use much more effort to set up the earth path resource point. You aren’t even able to display twenty percent of your strength, which will feel stifling. So, I suggest you take on some missions that allow you to display all your strength. That way, you can ease your mind.”

Yu Zi nodded and expressed her thanks.

But she was coughing out blood in her mind: “Sure enough, the so-called ‘rest’ was still to do missions! These Gu Immortals seem to not know what true rest is!”

“Sleep, I have not had any sleep for over ten days. I have only slept five times since I came here, and each sleep was less than four hours! I really want to sleep, sleep until I wake up naturally!”

“Why are so many earth path resource points pouring in recently? I am already disgusted from arranging these resource points to the point of vomiting.”

“I really hope some water path resource points come next...”

When she thought of this, Yu Zi almost wanted to slap herself from anger!

“What are you thinking?”

“You still want more resource points?”

“I hope there are no resource points ever!”

“I hope there are fewer missions!”

“I hope other Gu Immortals finish them instead!”

“Let me sleep, I just want to have a proper sleep.”

Chapter 2255: Painful Sale

Western Desert, Fang clan’s blessed land headquarters.

Fang clan’s immortals were all present, their expressions were ashen.

The atmosphere in the discussion hall was so heavy that it was suffocating.

“According to the information we obtained just earlier, Wan clan paid a visit to Qin clan, and Qin clan has already sent Qin Lang to take part in the battle.”

Qin Lang was a famous expert in Western Desert Gu Immortal world, he had rank seven cultivation and cultivated space path. His signature method was vortex sweep, once the move was used, it could clear out an area of ten thousand li.

“That means, the alliance that Wan clan gathered in the expedition against our Fang clan already includes Xiao clan, Qin clan, Sun clan, Shi clan, Gong clan, and Tang clan.”

“Sun clan’s representative is Sun Wang, he does not have high battle strength but is extremely proficient in investigative killer moves.”

“Gong clan sent Gong Jiao Che, you all know of his battle accomplishments.”

“Shi clan Gu Immortal Shi Kang is a recently famous expert, his defensive aspect is very powerful.”

“Tang clan Gu Immortal Tang Lan Ke is a time path Gu Immortal. She has all along been in charge of Tang clan’s tributary of the River of Time. Although she is not famous, since she was assigned such an important task by Tang clan, her strength is definitely out of the ordinary.”

“The strongest support is still Xiao clan. Xiao clan sent Xiao Ye Hu!”

“That’s right, this person had a fortuitous encounter when he was young, he obtained a Gu Immortal true inheritance and received a damaged Immortal Gu House. Xiao Ye Hu relied on this to cultivate until he became a Gu Immortal, he got Xiao clan’s help to repair the Immortal Gu House and changed his name to Xiao Ye Hu afterwards.”

“According to rumors, his dark path Immortal Gu House Chamber Pot[1] is extremely strange and vicious! Although it is pocket-sized, it can forcefully absorb Gu Immortals. If the Gu Immortal cannot escape and gets trapped in this pot for a night, they will become a pile of piss and stool.”

The Fang clan immortals felt a huge pressure weighing on them as they continued to discuss.

Western Desert’s super forces had fourteen clans: Lin clan, Xiao clan, Tian clan, Fang clan, Dong clan, Wan clan, Sun clan, Mo clan, Tang clan, Qin clan, Shi clan, Gong clan, Zuo Qiu clan, and Tuoba clan.

If the mysterious and secluded Yi clan was also counted, it would be fifteen clans.

Fang clan was only one of them.

There was no precise rankings of the strength of the super clans.

Western Desert was not like Southern Border, Southern Border’s Wu clan was the number one in strength which had been tested over a long period of time and was publicly approved by Gu Immortals.

A super force’s strength came from many aspects; for instance, Gu Immortals, resources, Immortal Gu Houses, and so on.

And these aspects also had strengths and weaknesses too.

In an actual situation, super forces competed, allied, or antagonized each other through many ways. Thus, it was rather difficult to rank the super forces.

Naturally, there was a vague consensus.

For instance, in the Western Desert Gu Immortal world, Xiao clan and Tian clan were normally thought of highly by Gu Immortals, because during the past peaceful era, these two had the largest businesses. They had many Gu Immortals and even had rank eight Gu Immortals leading them.

Fang clan’s strength was actually quite good.

Fang clan had rank eight Gu Immortal Fang Gong, possessed three Immortal Gu Houses, and now had added an earth path Immortal Gu House.

If they had Divine Bean Palace, Fang clan could have immediately become the dominant force in Western Desert’s Gu Immortal world.

Unfortunately, they did not succeed.

Now, Fang clan was facing the alliance of other super forces!

These super clans only needed to send one or two Gu Immortals, and it would be enough to make Fang clan have a tough time.

If just one-third of the super forces mobilized Immortal Gu Houses, it would be enough to surpass the scale of Fang clan’s Immortal Gu Houses.

Right now, Wan clan only had to contact the remaining super forces.

The Fang clan Gu Immortals already felt heavy weights pressing on their hearts, it felt like they were sitting on pins and needles.

As the immortals discussed, Fang Leng said: “Everyone, please don’t forget that there is still the most terrifying enemy that we need to face — Heavenly Court! Although the information says that Heavenly Court’s Gu Immortals clearly won’t interfere in Western Desert’s internal affairs, it is because of their guarantee that we are unable to use Great Love Immortal Venerable’s authority, so these Western Desert super clans are free of their final apprehension.”

“What worries me the most is that Heavenly Court sent two rank eight Gu Immortals. Among them, Wan Zi Hong was a famous demonic path expert in Western Desert’s history.”

The moment Wan Zi Hong was mentioned, some Fang clan Gu Immortals understood Fang Leng’s meaning: “Could it be that this Wan Zi Hong is related to Wan clan?”

“Wan Zi Hong is a demonic immortal, there is no evidence of her being blood-related to Wan clan. But even if there is no evidence, it can be forged. If Wan Zi Hong is believed to be a member of Wan clan, Heavenly Court will have justification to interfere in Western Desert’s internal affairs. Despite this possibility being unlikely, we have to be prepared for it.”

Fang Leng’s words made many nod their heads.

Fang Gong was satisfied inwardly.

He raised Fang Leng as his successor, and he saw him mature day by day. Especially during this recent period of time, his growth was obvious.

At this time, Fang Yun said: “From what I see, our clan must seek Great Love Immortal Venerable’s help. As long as this lord helps, no matter how many Western Desert super clans come, they are of no worry. And only Great Love Immortal Venerable can contend against Heavenly Court’s Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.”

Fang Yun was Fang Di Chang’s successor, and unlike Fang Leng who simply expressed the issue, he directly spoke of his solution.

During the period that Fang Di Chang was captured, Fang Yun became the leader of Fang clan’s wisdom path faction.

He gained many experiences through this, and his influence in Fang clan had also increased by a lot.

As for why he did not mention Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, it was because Fang clan had no connection to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

In fact, even if they could contact him, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable would be suspicious. After all, the connection between Fang clan and Fang Yuan was quite deep.

“Great Love Immortal Venerable already sent several rockman Gu Immortals, but they are only responsible for taking the resource points. We already sent a request to him, but Great Love Immortal Venerable... doesn’t seem to want to interfere.” Fang Leng said with a frown.

Fang clan had openly transacted some resources with Fang Yuan through treasure yellow heaven.

The other batch of resource points were secretly transacted with Fang Yuan. They naturally could not be passed through treasure yellow heaven, the biggest flaw of treasure yellow heaven was the openness, every transaction would be revealed.

Resource points were all counted and recorded, only by transacting them secretly could the information be concealed.

“The chance of getting Great Love Immortal Venerable to make a move is too low, and our clan cannot afford the cost as well.” At this time, Fang Di Chang finally spoke.

He had been maintaining silence before.

Besides him, Fang Gong and Fang Hua Sheng also did the same.

These three were the true leaders of Fang clan, they would not easily express their thoughts. Moreover, they were also giving Fang Leng and Fang Yun a chance to temper themselves.

Super forces were different from solitary Gu Immortals, they usually prioritized the cultivation of later generations.

The moment Fang Di Chang spoke, others kept quiet.

They were quietly watching Fang Di Chang with clear trust in their gazes.

Fang Di Chang suddenly chuckled before continuing: “No need to be worried, I have already deduced that the possibility of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable making a move is extremely unlikely.”

“In the confrontation between venerables, they will try to avoid a direct confrontation with each other, and will not move personally as a consequence of our affairs. Don’t think too highly of yourselves. In the eyes of venerables, we are lowly like ants.”

Fang clan immortals listened quietly, nodding their heads with strange expressions.

This might be the first time they were feeling joy at themselves being weak and ignored.

Fang Di Chang followed by saying: “But we still need to transact with Fang Yuan, we must rely on Fang Yuan, we must exchange for even more support from him!”

Fang Gong heard the meaning behind the words and frowned: “Ever since we occupied Wan clan’s territories, we have already traded many of Wan clan’s resource points with Fang Yuan, and exchanged for Immortal Gu and other resources. The rockman Gu Immortals sent by Fang Yuan are still busy moving away the resource points.”

Fang Di Chang shook his head: “But it is still not enough, we need even more Immortal Gu Houses! Once the war starts, we only have one rank eight, that is you. And the Wan clan alliance army will probably have several, even if they haven’t appeared now, once the battle turns for the worse, they will come to reinforce.”

“So, we need Immortal Gu Houses! Only then can our rank sixes and rank sevens be of use. Only then can they preserve their lives in the battle. They can advance and retreat to a certain extent with the Immortal Gu Houses.”

The Fang clan immortals were silent.

Fang Di Chang heaved a sigh: “We all know that the current situation is extremely grim. Our Fang clan is facing all of Western Desert’s righteous path!”

“We cannot directly raise our cultivation, our immortal essence stone reserves are also not sufficient, but Heavenly Court can keep on sending them immortal essence stones.”

“We must inflict an enormous loss to this wave of the alliance army. Otherwise, even if we hold on through this danger, there will be a second and third alliance army.”

“How many waves can our Fang clan hold off? In fact, we will use up all our strength just to block this first wave.”

“This is a correct judgment.” Fang Hua Sheng praised.

Fang Di Chang then mentioned transacting three big resource points, like black-yellow earth pool.

Fang clan’s immortals were shaken.

“Black-yellow earth pool is a super resource point.”

“It is no small matter!”

“It is Wan clan’s number one resource point, it contains their pride. Are we going to sell it this easily?”

“There will be considerable long-term benefits!”

Fang Di Chang did not speak, only looking at Fang Gong.

Fang Gong thought for a while before saying directly: “I agree, let’s handle it this way!”

Fang Di Chang smiled. At the crucial moment, Fang Gong did not disappoint him.

He continued: “Other resource points can be discussed, but we must openly transact this black-yellow earth pool with Fang Yuan!”

“Oh? Good plan!” Fang Yun immediately reacted, his eyes shining brightly.

When they learned of Fang clan’s decision, Shi Gua Bi and the rest were shaken.

“Fang clan has such a deep understanding of the situation!”

“More importantly, we have no way to relocate this kind of super resource point.”

Shi Gua Bi and the other rockman Gu Immortals felt somewhat awkward.

They only had rank seven cultivation, and this super resource point was at rank eight level.

“Please don’t worry, Alliance Leader Great Love already expected this.” Lu Wei Yin suddenly appeared and resolved the rockman Gu Immortals’ awkwardness.

Lu Wei Yin had joined the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance, he naturally came because he received Fang Yuan’s order.

His defense was extraordinary among pseudo venerables, he could match the two Heavenly Court immortals. Moreover, he cultivated earth path, so it was of no issue for him to relocate black-yellow earth pool.

Such a move of killing two birds with one stone made Lu Wei Yin the most suitable person to be sent to Western Desert!

[1] Pronounced as Ye Hu in Chinese.

Chapter 2256: Yu Zi’s Hair

Bai Ning Bing’s divine sense roamed in treasure yellow heaven.

She looked at the distant Primordial Domain and also Fang Yuan’s will above the Primordial Domain, feeling hesitant.

“Should I also transact with Fang Yuan?”

Over this period of time, Bai Ning Bing had been cultivating in the depths of the Earth Trench, exploring it while facing the risk of death.

Immemorial desolate beasts often ran wild in the depths of the earth, but there were all kinds of fortune hidden in the danger.

Bai Ning Bing had collected many immortal materials in this period of time, and also found many natural resource points, most of which were of earth path.

“It really is too difficult to refine Immortal Gu. If I can borrow Fang Yuan’s strength, it will definitely be a huge help.”

Bai Ning Bing was feeling the urge to make such a move.

According to her understanding of Fang Yuan, he would most likely agree to transact with her.

But Bai Ning Bing had her own misgivings.

On one hand, she had no way to directly take away these earth path resources and put them in treasure yellow heaven.

Bai Ning Bing cultivated ice and snow path, and also had aptitude in enslavement path because of her dragonman identity. She had no suitable Immortal Gu to dig out those earth path resource points.

On the other hand, Bai Ning Bing was worried that exposing the secret of rich resources in the underground would attract Fang Yuan’s greed.

Fang Yuan might not make a move personally, but sending a few of his subordinates would be enough to give trouble to Bai Ning Bing.

After all, Shen Shang and Lu Wei Yin had also joined Fang Yuan.

Right as Bai Ning Bing was hesitating, an earth path resource point entered treasure yellow heaven.

Following that, a treasure light shot out from this earth path resource point, forming an enormous pillar of light that seemed to touch the sky.

“Huh? This is... a super resource point?” Even Bai Ning Bing, who had gone through a lot, felt shaken.

At this moment, all the Gu Immortal wills and divine senses in treasure yellow heaven were fluctuating intensely!

“Oh goodness, am I seeing this wrongly?”

“A super resource point, an earth path super resource point!”

“This kind of resource point is a must-have for any super force, but it is actually being sold?!”

“Simply unimaginable!”

“Which wastrel will do such a thing?”

“How will they live from now on?”

“No matter which wastrel it is, the question is, who is this resource point being sold to?”

“Who else can it be? It is undoubtedly Great Love Immortal Venerable!”

Sure enough, like many immortals expected, this earth path super resource point was taken by Fang Yuan’s will.

Soon, the resource point was taken from treasure yellow heaven and moved into the sovereign immortal aperture.

An open transaction was finished.

Treasure yellow heaven was still in commotion.

“Western Desert’s Fang clan transacted with Fang Yuan.”

“Fang clan sold this earth path super resource point.”

“It has been checked! This super resource point is black-yellow earth pool, it originally did not belong to Fang clan, this is Wan clan’s number one resource point.”

“So it was Wan clan’s property. I understand now, Wan clan is paying a visit to every Western Desert righteous path super force to organize an anti-Fang alliance. Fang clan is really vicious for selling this resource point.”

The five regions’ Gu Immortals were all discussing this matter.

Wan clan also soon learned of this.

“How can this be?!” Wan Zhui Qing’s eyes reddened with hatred as he spoke through clenched teeth.

“Fang clan is too hateful, too despicable!” Wan Xiao’s face was ashen.

This was a classic situation of a person not feeling any heartache for selling something that was not theirs.

Fang clan did not use their own super resource points, but sold Wan clan’s super resource point instead.

They even chose to transact it openly!

This plan was really vicious.

Wan Hao Guang also felt an extreme headache. Because this black-yellow earth pool was meant to be the payment to Xiao clan.

Xiao clan sent several Gu Immortal experts to take part in the anti-Fang alliance, and they would form a close alliance with Wan clan later on to reclaim the territories.

But now, black-yellow earth pool was gone, Fang clan sold it to Fang Yuan.

Who was Fang Yuan?

Great Love Immortal Venerable! Heaven Refining Demon Venerable!

Would Wan clan dare to ask for black-yellow earth pool from Fang Yuan?

Would Xiao clan dare?

They would not dare to do it even if they were given ten thousand guts.

Sure enough, not long later, Xiao Ye Hu paid a visit.

“Wan clan, the situation has changed. We need to have another talk.” Xiao Ye Hu said heavily.

Wan Hao Guang and the others’ expressions did not look good.

When they finished their discussion with Xiao Ye Hu, the expressions of Wan clan’s immortals became even more unsightly.

“These greedy jackals!” Wan Hao Guang clenched his fists tightly.

Wan clan’s and Xiao clan’s transaction contents were modified several times. Black-yellow earth pool was removed, and Wan clan had to add in several giant resource points.

After Xiao clan’s benefits were preserved, Xiao Ye Hu left contentedly.

Wan clan’s immortals felt anger and hatred, but were helpless.

What choice did they have?

“To make these righteous path forces participate in the anti-Fang alliance, our Wan clan must pay a corresponding price.”

“Xiao clan is the super force putting in the most effort, so we need to pay them even more.”

“They are simply kicking a person when they are down!”

“Sigh, among the entire righteous path forces, only Tang clan has the most righteous demeanor.”

“Yes, I did not notice it before. But in this moment of crisis, we can see the true character of others. Tang clan asked for the lowest price.”

“Although Tang clan is not strong, once we retrieve our territory, we should have more dealings with Tang clan.”

“That is reasonable.”

“Tang clan is a true model of the righteous path!”

Just as Wan clan was discussing the matter, the rank seven time path Gu Immortal Tang Lan Ke, who was sent by Tang clan, secretly contacted Fang Yuan.

“Reporting to lord, Xiao Ye Hu just paid a visit to Wan clan. They had a secret discussion for a long time before he left. Looking at his expression, he seemed to be satisfied.”

Fang Yuan nodded. With just a slight deduction, he knew the truth: “Looks like Wan clan ceded black-yellow earth pool to exchange for more support from Xiao clan. The plan with Fang clan has already produced results, continue to stay hidden and probe for information.”

“Yes, lord!”

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

Because the time flow was much faster here, more than a day had already passed.

An abnormal situation was occurring around an earth vein node.

Dense yellow fog shrouded this earth vein node. Dart-like stones constantly flew out of the yellow fog and attacked the earth vein node.

Yu Zi accepted the task to defend the node, she was facing countless flying stones alone.

Water vapor surrounded her body as her hands moved rapidly, raising giant waves that drowned the stones.

After Yu Zi bade farewell to Shi San Bai, she accepted his suggestion and specially chose a task where she could vent her stress.

Thus, she accepted this task.

At the start, she was like an all-powerful being, her moves were majestic and grand. She released all her stress and felt refreshed.

But this abnormal situation continued until now, Yu Zi was not able to suppress it completely.

Yu Zi was feeling restless and stifled at this moment.

“How can I be so unlucky?”

“I chose a random task but it is actually so difficult!”

“The amount of immortal essence I have expended over these days already amounts to a huge loss. Do I still have to take out some contribution points to ask for help?”

Just as Yu Zi was hesitating, the yellow fog expanded suddenly, and the amount of flying stones doubled.

Yu Zi was caught unprepared and was unable to block them, she could only watch as many of the flying stones shot at the earth vein node.

“Damn it!” Yu Zi cursed in shock and anger.

She took on this task to protect the earth vein node. But if the earth vein node was destroyed, her contribution points would be deducted!

At the crucial moment, a figure suddenly appeared.

He lightly waved his hand, illusory pink light specks scattered and flew into the yellow fog.

“This is a dream path killer move?!” Yu Zi was stunned and joyous.

The dream path killer move was clearly effective, the yellow fog quickly shrunk. The danger was eliminated instantly.

“Yu Zi greets Lord Meng Qiu Zhen!” Yu Zi quickly bowed in greeting.

She was extremely excited.

Truly, fortune and misfortune existed together, she was actually able to see another main clone of Lord Fang Yuan because of this event. She was truly too fortunate.

“Are you alright?” Meng Qiu Zhen asked warmly.

Yu Zi raised her head and saw Meng Qiu Zhen. He had a head full of long pink hair that looked dreamy and illusory. His shining gaze was extremely captivating, his smooth facial contours showed a smile at this moment, making Yu Zi feel warm and heartened.

“So beautiful...” Yu Zi was stupefied as she thought to herself.

Although Meng Qiu Zhen was only at rank six, being shown concern by him made Yu Zi feel a sense of security.

She then thought of her plan and immediately appeared more meek, covering her face as she wept softly: “Many thanks for Lord Meng Qiu Zhen’s concern, I used all my strength to protect the earth vein node. But I had no way to protect the formation surrounding the earth vein node.”

Meng Qiu Zhen nodded: “I remember this formation, I personally set it up. According to the condition at that time, the formation base was buried underground. The formation’s structure was somewhat neglected, so a formation barrier was also constructed.”

“Yes.” Yu Zi said in agreement, “The formation barrier is too easily broken, I repaired it many times but it always broke immediately after!”

Meng Qiu Zhen took a deep look at Yu Zi. Suddenly, he took her in his arms and started touching her.

He rubbed here and touched there.

Yu Zi was dazed, her whole body was stiff like a statue.

How could this happen all of a sudden?

The difference in personality among Lord Fang Yuan’s clones was too big!

If I had known this, I should have just gone to find Lord Meng Qiu Zhen, right?

“Meng Qiu Zhen is such a good name[1], he is truly a dream come true!” Intense happiness filled Yu Zi’s body, her stiff body quickly relaxed as she shrunk into Meng Qiu Zhen’s embrace, and looked up at Meng Qiu Zhen’s face while blushing.

But at the next moment, Meng Qiu Zhen said calmly: “There is an issue with your body, you have been contaminated.”

“Wha... what?” Yu Zi was stunned.

Meng Qiu Zhen continued: “Your contamination is quite serious, the abnormal situation is the source of the contamination. In fact, it already had no strength to exist, but after contaminating you, you became the potential source and have been nurturing it. The more you resist, the stronger the abnormal situation will become.”

“Is, is this true?!” Yu Zi’s eyes widened with an incredulous expression.

“You don’t believe me?” Meng Qiu Zhen laughed and patted her shoulder.

“Look, you have hair now.” Meng Qiu Zhen said, “I have triggered the abnormal dao marks on your body.”

Yu Zi almost fainted when she looked.

She saw hair on her chest, nose, armpit and other private areas.

In just a few breaths of time, this hair had already grown longer than an adult’s palm.

Meng Qiu Zhen patted again: “Look, you have grown mold.”

Yu Zi’s hair was previously standing straight, but now, it drooped down as greenish-white mold grew on it. An intense rotten stench assailed her nose.

Tears flowed out of Yu Zi’s eyes.

This was a huge deal to her.

The merfolk aesthetic sense had nothing to do with hair. Merfolk liked scales, luster, and contours forming a streamlined body shape.

Being hairy or furry was ugly!

“What should I do? Please save me, Lord Meng Qiu Zhen!” Yu Zi pleaded, this emotion of desperation came straight from her heart.

Meng Qiu Zhen smiled: “If you want me to help you, you have to spend contribution points.”

“I am willing to pay anything and everything.” Yu Zi quickly said.

Meng Qiu Zhen shook his head slightly: “But your contribution points are still not enough.”

Yu Zi was getting dizzy from anxiety as she quickly explained the reason: “That is because I exchanged for Immortal Gu before!”

“Hmm, let’s do it like this then.” Meng Qiu Zhen first activated a dream path method.

Pink light covered Yu Zi, suppressing all the hair on her body and restoring her to her original state.

Meng Qiu Zhen said: “I have temporarily restrained your abnormal dao marks, go to Star Collection City when you have gathered enough contribution points, you will be treated there. Go.”

Meng Qiu Zhen then left Yu Zi and began to repair the formation around the earth vein node.

Yu Zi gritted her teeth and bowed to bid her farewell.

While flying, she activated a Gu worm to inspect the mission board.

“Why are there so many resource point arrangement missions again?” Yu Zi paled, a vague feeling of disgust emerging in her heart.

But she had no other options, to heal herself, she could only grit her teeth and choose a mission.

“Arrange for the settlement of the black-yellow earth pool! This mission has the highest reward!”

[1] Remember it comes from Dream Reality Seeker.

Chapter 2257: Salt Water Liver

With a pale expression and heavy eye bags, Yu Zi entered Star Collection City in a daze.

After working hard for over ten days without resting, she finally finished arranging black-yellow earth pool with the help of two other Gu Immortals.

“Isn’t this Fairy Yu Zi? I heard you were in charge of arranging the black-yellow earth pool?”

A Gu Immortal greeted Yu Zi.

Yu Zi quickly raised her spirit and responded.

“Your luck is really good, this mission rewards a lot of contribution points. I was held up with another task at that time, otherwise, I would have also taken this mission.” Another Gu Immortal said to Yu Zi.

Yu Zi smiled, nodding towards the Gu Immortal.

The two immortals quickly parted after that.

This was the style of the Gu Immortals of the sovereign immortal aperture, they were always in a hurry, making use of every second.

“Your condition does not look good, go to Liver Life Hall immediately.” Lian Ke Xin came across Yu Zi and said with concern.

“You are also here?” Yu Zi felt much more at ease when she saw a Gu Immortal of her kin.

Lian Ke Xin nodded: “I just came out of Liver Life Hall, the sovereign immortal aperture added black-yellow earth pool, there really are a lot of super resource points here.”

Yu Zi said in agreement: “From what I know, there are rolling fall cliff, triple sacred mountain, divine needle valley, frost dragon pond, pin tree snowfield, water spider sea, and heavenly crystal storage pool. Now, there is this black-yellow earth pool, there must definitely be others as well.”

Before Lian Ke Xin and Yu Zi entered the sovereign immortal aperture, they were leaders of the Merman Imperial Court, and were aware of the value of super resource points.

Normally speaking, resource points were divided into several grades.

Tiny resource points, small-sized resource points, and mid-sized resource points produced rank one to rank five cultivation resources.

Large resource points could stably produce rank six resources, and occasionally rank seven resources.

Giant resource points could stably produce rank seven resources.

Super resource points were at rank eight level, and the pinnacle resource points were those secluded domains of heaven and earth.

A super resource point could lead to an all-out contest between super forces, and it could even result in casualties.

The five regions’ super forces were in possession of super resource points; the richer ones had more than ten, while the poorer ones had at least three or four.

Heavenly Court and Longevity Heaven were naturally not counted among these super forces.

Strictly speaking, Heavenly Court and Longevity Heaven should be considered ultimate forces!

Right now, Fang Yuan’s force could also be considered an ultimate force. There were over ten super resource points in the sovereign immortal aperture, it was just that the mermaid immortals had not been here for a long time, so they did not come into contact with the other resources.

“The sovereign immortal aperture’s foundation has increased again, this is a good thing. But I am worried about the abnormal situations happening more often.” Lian Ke Xin was happy but also worried.

Resource points contained dense amount of dao marks, after they were shifted into the sovereign immortal aperture, the immortal aperture’s dao marks would naturally increase.

By now, the mermaid immortals had already realized the source of the abnormal situations.

Lian Ke Xin was worried, Yu Zi was too, she said in a quiet voice: “Master sent several Gu Immortals outside, there is a shortage of manpower in the sovereign immortal aperture again. Over this period of time, missions have been constantly increasing on the mission board, the Gu Immortals’ mission completion speed cannot match the speed of the addition of new missions. Sigh, it will be great if master can bring in more Gu Immortals.”

Lian Ke Xin nodded and said: “I also hope for more companions. But rashly bringing in the five regions’ Gu Immortals is not appropriate. On one hand, we will have to remove the suspicion of insiders and spies, on the other hand, there is racial equality here. If those self-righteous human Gu Immortals come in, they might destroy the harmony here. Master may also have such misgivings.”

The two talked while walking towards Liver Life Hall.

Yu Zi looked at the Liver Life Hall and suddenly understood: “I heard Liver Life Hall was only a liver life formation before. Master worked hard to modify it into an Immortal Gu House, it was really a wise move.”

The immortal formation was closely connected to its surroundings, but Immortal Gu House was an independent body.

Abnormal situations occurred frequently in the sovereign immortal aperture, and the immortal formations of various locations suffered, but Immortal Gu Houses were not disturbed.

Yu Zi sighed: “I am somewhat worried. Don’t you think master’s idea for the development of the aperture is somewhat radical? The current sovereign immortal aperture is walking on a thin rope, we have to use all our effort to maintain this fragile balance. Even so, we are slowly slipping down the abyss of failure.”

Lian Ke Xin squinted her eyes: “Maybe this nature is one of the reasons for master’s legendary rise. The current sovereign immortal aperture is truly like a glutton, it already is full to the point of indigestion, but is still eating regardless. By constructing dao veins everywhere, we are only treating the symptoms but not the root cause. If we don’t solve the fundamental issues, abnormal situations will still continue.”

Yu Zi shook her head slightly: “In this period of time, I saw Lord Wu Shuai and Lord Meng Qiu Zhen. Both are peerlessly beautiful. I don’t believe such incredible existences are not aware of the root issue. We are only minor characters, how can we estimate master’s thoughts?”

“Yes. This root issue is not our concern.” Lian Ke Xin patted Yu Zi’s arm, “Alright, Yu Zi, the Liver Life Hall is in front. I won’t accompany you, I still have a mission to do.”

Yu Zi parted with Lian Ke Xin as well.

She did not tell her abnormal state to Lian Ke Xin.

Yu Zi entered Liver Life Hall with familiarity.

Yu Zi had visited this mysterious Immortal Gu House many times, so she was not a stranger to it.

She thought this use would also go smoothly, but how could she have expected an accident to happen.

Boom.

Liver Life Hall shook as the nearby Gu Immortals were alerted.

“Looking at this, it seems someone’s liver exploded again?”

“Hehe, this is a terrible feeling for them.”

“No matter who it is, they are much luckier than me. The healing hall was constructed not long ago.”

By the time Yu Zi woke up, she found she was no longer in the Liver Life Hall.

She was lying on a large porcelain plate with dazzling white light filling her surroundings.

After she adapted to this light with difficulty, she saw a will floating in the air and watching her.

This will took a form, it was in the appearance of Fang Yuan’s main body.

Yu Zi tried to stand up to greet him, but was stopped by Fang Yuan’s will: “Don’t move carelessly, your liver exploded, your injuries are not light. Also, some dao marks are still hiding in your body. Although they were suppressed temporarily by dream path methods, they are showing signs of erupting again.”

Yu Zi immediately panicked, she did not want to grow moldy hair in front of Fang Yuan’s will.

Naturally, her current situation was extremely pitiful.

After her liver exploded, her stomach burst open, half of her rib bones were sent flying, and all her organs were injured.

Yu Zi looked at Fang Yuan’s will, immediately saying: “Please save me, master. I already have enough contribution points.”

Fang Yuan’s will nodded: “Your contribution points are enough, I have several treatment plans here for you.”

“First is to use a time path killer move to restore you back to your previous state.”

“Second is to transplant an ancient desolate beast’s liver into you, and use a transformation path method to merge the liver with your body.”

“Third is to use a refinement path method, we will get rid of your abnormal dao marks first, then refine a brand new liver.”

“And finally, the fourth option is my personal recommendation. This is an immortal killer move called salt water liver. After you cultivate it, you can create a new liver. This liver not only has water path dao marks, but also food path dao marks; using this liver, you can dual cultivate food path.”

“Compared to an ordinary Gu Immortal’s liver, salt water liver can bear the support of Liver Life Hall much longer and last for many more uses. Moreover, if you fall into a predicament and have no way out, and are in shortage of food, you can eat this liver to satisfy your hunger.”

“The fifth method is...”

Fang Yuan’s will continued to describe over ten treatment plans.

After Yu Zi listened to them attentively, she asked about the price.

She found the most stable and safest method was the first time path plan. But because she cultivated water path, the time path killer move’s effect would not be obvious. She would have to pay a higher price for an obvious effect. Thus, the performance-cost ratio of the first plan was not high.

The most effective treatment was the second plan. If Yu Zi could afford the price, she could use an immemorial desolate beast’s liver to transplant into her body.

The lowest price was the refinement path plan, that was also the third plan.

The highest performance-cost ratio plan was the fourth plan.

“Salt water liver...” Yu Zi considered for a while before nodding, “I choose this.”

While Yu Zi was being treated, looking over in Western Desert.

Xiao Ye Hu gazed at Wan Hao Guang with a frown: “Muddy beach is no more, perfume flying island is also no more! They were openly sold to Heaven Refining Demon Venerable by Fang clan. Our contract needs to be changed.”

Wan Hao Guang showed a painful expression: “Xiao Ye Hu, you have already been here five times to talk over the contract. Is it appropriate to change it at will? We should follow my previous suggestion, we should quickly attack Fang clan and drive them away, won’t it be much easier to change the contract based on the actual state?”

Xiao Ye Hu shook his head, sighing deeply: “Wan Hao Guang, that is very risky. Your clan’s resource points are almost all sold by Fang clan. Even if we succeed in attacking Fang clan, can you bring out enough remuneration? You have contacted all the super forces of Western Desert. Looking at the price you paid to invite these people to join the alliance, are you still able to satisfy my Xiao clan first?”

Wan Hao Guang felt an extreme headache, he was about to appease Xiao Ye Hu when suddenly, heaven and earth shook, thunderous explosions occurred.

Their gathering point was ambushed!

“It is Fang clan!”

“Such guts, we haven’t even gone to attack them, yet they dare to send themselves to death!”

“Fight!”

The anti-Fang alliance army reacted and attacked furiously.

The Wan clan Gu Immortals were extremely angry.

It was this bunch of shameless scoundrels who sold off their resource points.

They had to modify the contracts almost every day, this caused them a great headache.

Fang clan mobilized three Immortal Gu Houses this time!

The Fang clan immortals were also extremely angry.

You guys! You guys!!

You forced our Fang clan to sell all those resource points.

Bam bam bam...

Both sides were so furious that the moment they started the battle, a huge commotion could be heard, rocks cracked and rubble flew.

Chapter 2258: Battle Against Fang Clan

The thunderous explosions rang for a while as the killer moves collided with each other. Even the aftershock was fatal!

Fang clan’s attack was too sudden, surpassing anti-Fang alliance’s expectations. What made the anti-Fang alliance regret was that they were not stationed at a resource point, but in an ordinary desert.

They were about to make a large scale move against Fang clan, but they had to discuss their payment before the battle.

Fang Di Chang’s plan was very effective, they did open transactions with Fang Yuan repeatedly which led to internal instability in the anti-Fang alliance, greatly postponing their official expedition.

And this sudden attack was also Fang Di Chang’s proposition!

“Fang Di Chang!!!” Wan Xiao gritted his teeth.

Not only him, the other immortals of the alliance also experienced Fang Di Chang’s strength.

Inside Chicken Dog Coop, Fang Di Chang’s expression was cold and his gaze was sharp.

The situation of the battlefield was reflected in his mind, he shouted: “Release all the ancient desolate beasts, not to kill, but to scatter the enemies.”

At the next moment, Chicken Dog Coop let out a dazzling light. Dozens of chicken and ancient desolate beast dogs formed into two groups that rushed ahead.

Wan Hao Guang was furious as he understood Fang clan’s plan. He shouted madly: “Don’t scatter, whoever is alone may lose their life!”

Fang clan immortals were curled up in their three Immortal Gu Houses, while the alliance Gu Immortals were flying in the sky.

These Gu Immortals were pale, who could use their bodies to block these ancient desolate beasts?

Even if they used killer moves, they would not able to exterminate them instantly.

Once they started fighting and dodging, their already loose formation would immediately break, and Fang clan would succeed.

Right at this time, an alliance Gu Immortal suddenly laughed as his appearance started changing.

“It is time for me to make a move!” He was dressed in a blue robe, his laughter was unpleasant and noisy which left a deep impression on people.

“You are not Tian Feng Mang, you are Tian Da Ji!” The other alliance Gu Immortals exclaimed in surprise and joy.

Tian Da Ji had rank seven cultivation and cultivated enslavement path.

He was not a lineal descendant of Tian clan, he had been a lowly young boy with no cultivation aptitude whose only fate was to become a farmer.

But one time, as he was taking care of a field, he accidentally dug out a Gu Immortal inheritance.

It was this inheritance that completely changed his life.

He cultivated secretly at first, but was discovered soon after, and had no choice but to offer the Gu Immortal inheritance to Tian clan.

The Gu Immortal in charge of the matter at that time, Tian Gang Hui, was an honest person. He did not covet this inheritance, instead protecting Tian Da Ji from then on.

Tian Da Ji inherited this special inheritance that could only enslave chickens but its effect was outstanding.

At the next moment, Tian Da Ji made a move, activating a killer move that actually caused all the ancient desolate beast chickens released by Fang clan to defect.

These ancient desolate beasts immediately attacked the ancient desolate beast dogs behind them.

In an instant, chickens and dogs fought, causing sand to fill the battlefield.

The anti-Fang alliance’s crisis was immediately resolved. Wan Xiao, Wan Hao Guang, Sun Wang, and the rest made their moves.

Wind path, light path, fire path, and other paths’ killer moves erupted in succession, forming three waves of attacks that charged towards Chicken Dog Coop.

Fang clan had schemes, Wan clan also had prepared some.

Tian Da Ji’s identity was a secret that was exposed only now. This was the result of Wan clan specially discussing it with Tian clan.

Although the alliance was delayed by Fang clan, Wan clan did not waste the time. While the

contract discussions were being talked, Wan clan actively made Gu Immortals train in group combat.

The alliance Gu Immortals did not have much coordination with each other, it was no issue to fight individual fights, but group battle was their greatest weakness.

After all, dao marks of different paths conflicted with each other.

To target this weakness, under Heavenly Court’s unending supply of immortal essence stones, the alliance immortals cultivated painstakingly, forming an initial stage of group combat coordination.

“Fang Hua Sheng.” Fang Di Chang retreated with Chicken Dog Coop while shouting for reinforcement.

Although the ancient desolate beast chickens revolted, Chicken Dog Coop could still control ancient desolate beast dogs. This Immortal Gu House was important, if it was attacked and lost a crucial Immortal Gu, it would be really bad.

If the ancient desolate beast dogs stop listening to commands, they would be defeated quickly.

Fang Hua Sheng was controlling Fallen Flower Hall, he immediately rushed over after getting the message.

Immortal killer move — Mirror Flower!

The surface of Fallen Flower Hall immediately let out a wave of light.

The light was pure white, it first exited violently before being restrained suddenly, turning into a huge flower bud on the roof of the hall.

The flower bud quickly bloomed, the petals were like mirrors, reflecting light.

As it bloomed, the flower petals collided with one another, emitting a crisp sound.

After the flower bud bloomed completely, it was even larger than the roof of Fallen Flower Hall, being extremely beautiful.

The mirror flower formed in a blink of an eye, and let out a strong suction force.

Be it Wan Hao Guang, Wan Xiao, or Sun Wang’s killer moves, most of them was absorbed by the mirror flower.

But there was still a small number of killer moves left that made Fallen Flower Hall shake endlessly, the mirror flower’s petals broke into pieces, and the remaining petals closed again, turning into a flower bud.

“I am returning them to you!” Fang Hua Sheng shouted.

The mirror flower bud bloomed again, releasing the absorbed killer moves back at the enemies.

The flower bud disappeared completely, the released killer moves forced Wan Hao Guang and the rest to retreat again and again. They could only activate their methods to block arduously.

Fang Hua Sheng saw that three immortals were in a miserable state, he knew the battle opportunity had appeared. He was just about to attack them, when suddenly a fire path Immortal Gu House appeared in the enemy formation!

This Immortal Gu House was like a giant wheel, after it took in Dong clan’s two Gu Immortals Dong Zhu and Gong Ming, it started rolling.

Dong clan’s Immortal Gu House Red River Wheel!

Inside Red River Wheel, Dong Ming shouted in hatred: “Fang clan, you previously used the theft path Immortal Gu House to raid my Dong clan’s resource point, destroying my clan’s treasure moon oasis. This debt will be paid today!”

With a crushing momentum, Red River Wheel whipped up an intense flame as it collided with Fallen Flower Hall.

Bam.

Fallen Flower Hall shook intensely as it retreated quickly.

“Where are you going?” The Gu Immortals inside Red River Wheel gave chase.

Not long later, Fallen Flower Hall fell into a disadvantage as flames stuck to it.

Red River Wheel could counter the wood path Immortal Gu House Fallen Flower Hall to a certain extent.

“Since there is fire, this will be easy.” Inside the alliance army formation, Gong Jiao Che smiled as he used a killer move.

Boom.

At the next moment, the flames on Fallen Flower Hall intensified turning into a huge fire!

“Damn it...” Fang Hua Sheng gritted his teeth as he controlled Fallen Flower Hall to defend, but could not turn the situation around in a short period of time.

The other Fang clan Gu Immortals in Fallen Flower Hall were doing their best to save Fallen Flower Hall’s Gu worms.

But Red River Wheel’s fire continued to infiltrate the Immortal Gu House, spreading towards the core Immortal Gu!

Fang Gong wanted to to go reinforce with Inquiry Dock.

But another rank seven Immortal Gu House blocked its path firmly.

It was Wan clan’s time path Immortal Gu House — Myriad Age Building!

Soon after, Chicken Dog Coop also got attacked by many Gu Immortals.

Fang Di Chang heaved a deep sigh, saying inwardly: ‘Wan clan really prepared sufficiently this time.’

Be it the matter of concealing the identity of Tian Da Ji, Red River Wheel that restrained Fallen Flower Hall, or Myriad Age Building that firmly held back Inquiry Dock, it all proved that Wan clan was well prepared.

These three Immortal Gu Houses of Fang clan were not a secret. Since this anti-Fang alliance included over ten super forces, it was not hard to find methods that could restrain Fang clan.

The moment the ancient desolate beast chickens were made to revolt, Fang Di Chang knew the situation was turning bad.

When anti-Fang alliance stabilized themselves and reacted, Fang clan immediately felt suppressed. The advantage of their sudden attack was already gone.

The situation was urgent, but the Fang clan immortals were still not panicked and held ample confidence.

Earth Shuttle — was mobilized!

Fang Chen and Fang An Lei flew out and entered Earth Shuttle.

“It was this Immortal Gu House that destroyed my tall pine oasis’ formation base!” Wan Xiao was furious. He immediately changed his target, hurling the long-prepared berserk wind blades towards Earth Shuttle.

Earth Shuttle did not dodge as it endured these berserk wind blades and charged towards the enemy formation.

Wherever it went, the alliance Gu Immortals evaded in fright. Who would dare to use their body

to collide with a rank seven Immortal Gu House?

Wan Xiao’s pupils shrunk when he saw this.

Every aspect of Earth Shuttle Immortal Gu House was strengthened. Last time, when it attacked tall pine oasis, its defense was very weak. But it was completely different now.

However, dealing with this earth path Immortal Gu House was also within Wan clan’s plans.

Even the matter of it being stronger now did not surpass Wan clan’s expectations.

At the crucial moment, Mo Sha Ta stood up and activated a killer move, blocking Earth Shuttle.

A dense layer of sand accumulated on Earth Shuttle, reducing its speed sharply.

Boom.

Earth Shuttle shook, destroying the sand layer. Without the restraint, it directly charged at Mo Sha Ta.

Mo Sha Ta was pale with fright as he turned around and ran.

The alliance’s formation began to turn chaotic.

Xiao Ye Hu gritted his teeth as he had no choice but to make a move in advance.

He held Chamber Pot which aimed at Earth Shuttle from afar, letting out a pitch-black lump of light.

“Don’t even think of it!” Fang Hua Sheng shouted.

Fallen Flower Hall moved once again.

Immortal killer move — Fleeting Bloom!

The pitch-black light lump was really fast, but it got struck by fleeting bloom, slowing down rapidly.

Earth Shuttle easily evaded it as Xiao Ye Hu glared in anger.

“You still have the time to care about others!” Tuoba Cheng Feng made his move.

He was a famous Gu Immortal in Western Desert’s Gu Immortal world, and was extremely proficient in support methods.

This was a wind path support killer move. After it covered Fallen Flower Hall, the huge fire

burned even hotter and covered over half of Fallen Flower Hall.

Fang Hua Sheng’s expression turned heavy, he had just gotten rid of Earth Shuttle’s obstacle, but it made Fallen Flower Hall’s situation even more dangerous.

“Do I reinforce Fallen Flower Hall?” Fang Di Chang scanned the whole battlefield, soon his eyes shrunk when he saw a figure, “No, I need to rescue Inquiry Dock first!”

Since the battle started, Zuo Qiu San Sha had been staying at the back of the alliance army as he prepared his killer move.

At this time, the killer move’s aura was already close to complete.

Fang clan possessed roof tile breaker killer move that could restrain Immortal Gu Houses. Zuo Qiu also had a similar killer move, it was called state of disunity which was created by Zuo Qiu San Sha!

Chapter 2259: Like a Tiger, Fang Gong

State of disunity killer move was similar to roof tile breaker; they both countered Immortal Gu Houses.

No doubt, this was a killer weapon of the anti-Fang alliance to deal with Fang clan!

Fang clan’s proficiency lied in Immortal Gu Houses.

Zuo Qiu San Sha who possessed state of disunity was the key person to suppress Fang clan.

“We can’t let him activate it!” Fang Di Chang understood Zuo Qiu San Sha’s threat, immediately commanding, “Fang Zhi and Fang Dong Xi, go!”

Two Fang clan rank seven Gu Immortals flew out of Chicken Dog Coop, they quickly took out an

Immortal Gu House.

This Immortal Gu House had two floors, it was a short building.

As the Immortal Gu House was activated, the roof released dense smoke.

Rank seven Immortal Gu House — Smoke Wave Building!

“A completely new Immortal Gu House appeared!”

“Fang clan sold so many resource points, as expected, they gathered enough resources from Heaven Refining Demon Venerable to construct another Immortal Gu House.”

The alliance immortals were shaken.

According the previous discussion, Shi Kang went forward. He anxiously approached Smoke Wave Building and started probing it.

After all, he was most proficient in defense.

Smoke Wave Building was not fast, but the dense smoke on the roof of the building kept on gushing out. Soon, it filled most of the battlefield, attempting to engulf Zuo Qiu San Sha.

The alliance immortals did not understand the power of the smoke, so they retreated carefully.

Immortal killer move — Vortex Sweep!

Qin Lang activated his proudest method; immediately, most of the smoke dissipated, and the

surroundings became clear again.

“Hmph!” Fang Di Chang left a sentence while personally moving out, “Fang Leng, Fang Yun, look after Chicken Dog Coop.”

Fang Di Chang flew out, he took out an Immortal Gu House before he entered it.

“Another rank seven Immortal Gu House!”

The anti-Fang alliance was in an uproar.

Fang clan had three new Immortal Gu Houses, moreover they were all at rank seven!

How many things did Heaven Refining Demon Venerable give Fang clan!

The third Immortal Gu House was Thought Expelling Pavilion. It was a wisdom path Immortal Gu House that complemented Fang Di Chang.

Fang Di Chang activated the Immortal Gu House’s method and targeted Zuo Qiu San Sha.

Zuo Qiu San Sha had already succeeded in approaching closer, but his thoughts suddenly flew out of his mind and circled around his body!

The Gu worms in his immortal aperture immediately fell into chaos, Zuo Qiu San Sha’s killer move failed to activate. With a cough, he spat out blood and suffered heavy injuries from the backlash.

Tuoba Cheng Feng and Gong Jiao Che saw the situation turning for the worse, they quickly gave up on encircling Fallen Flower Hall; the former went to save Zuo Qiu San Sha, and the latter attacked Thought Expelling Pavilion from afar.

Thought Expelling Pavilion endured Gong Jiao Che’s fire path killer move and activated its method again.

Tang Lan Ke gasped as she fell down from the sky.

“I can’t stop it!” Shi Kang was covered in black smoke, he retreated with a shout.

The dense black smoke emitted by Smoke Wave Building made it extremely difficult for him to defend, this was already his limit.

Right at this time, a yellow meteor streaked across the battlefield and collided with Shi Kang.

It was Earth Shuttle!

Shi Kang’s pupils shrunk as the intense threat of death assaulted his body and mind.

Boom.

At the crucial moment, Lin Shu Tong flew over and sacrificed himself to collide into Earth Shuttle

from the side, forcefully changing its route.

Shi Kang almost brushed past Earth Shuttle, surviving luckily.

His battle intent was mostly gone as he retreated rapidly.

“The enemies are in chaos.” Fang Di Chang saw this, and activated Thought Expelling Pavilion, targeting Tian Da Ji.

Tian Da Ji was startled and immediately released ancient desolate chickens from his immortal aperture to protect him.

But who could have imagined that Fang Di Chang was only bluffing, immediately targeting its attack towards Sun Wang.

Sun clan Gu Immortals were most conservative. The moment Thought Expelling Pavilion showed such movement, Sun Wang immediately ran away with an astonishing speed.

Wan clan Gu Immortals looked extremely unsightly.

Fang Di Chang was indeed worthy of being a wisdom path Gu Immortal, he was familiar with people’s nature. He only used Thought Expelling Pavilion a few times and made use of its threat to gain such battle accomplishments!

“First supreme elder, this is the time for our Fang clan to claim victory!” Fang Di Chang’s voice was slightly excited.

Inside Inquiry Dock, Fang Gong was already impatient from waiting.

When he heard Fang Di Chang’s call, he laughed heartily. He gave the control of Inquiry Dock to other Fang clan Gu Immortals and flew out like a meteor.

Fang Gong collided with Myriad Age Building, the whole building almost collapsed.

Immortal killer move — Roof Tile Breaker!

Fang Gong’s palm shadows flew, raising storm-like attacks.

Myriad Age Building’s defensive killer moves also could not block roof tile breaker, it started to crumble rapidly.

“Good!” Xiao Ye Hu’s eyes lit up, he finally saw an enemy Gu Immortal leaving the protection of

their Immortal Gu House, this was the time for Chamber Pot to shine.

But just as he was about to make a move, Earth Shuttle came crashing over.

Xiao Ye Hu cursed, he could only retreat to protect himself.

Myriad Age Building was forced to activate its strongest defensive method which rapidly extracted Fang Gong’s lifespan.

Fang Gong sneered, decisively retreating.

He had achieved his target by forcing out this method of Myriad Age Building.

Once this method of Myriad Age Building activated, it could only stop after at least two hours.

The surrounding alliance Gu Immortals retreated away from Myriad Age Building.

The anti-Fang alliance’s formation was already in complete disorder.

Fang Gong left Myriad Age Building and charged towards Red River Wheel.

“Didn’t you want revenge? Then come at me!” Fang Gong shouted.

Roof tile breaker killer move activated once again, Red River Wheel retreated rapidly while burning flames closed in on Fang Gong.

Fang Gong did not dodge, sticking to Red River Wheel amidst the burning flames.

Dong Ming screamed: “Fang Gong, you’ve gone too far!”

He activated Red River Wheel and collided with Fang Gong.

Fang Gong’s eyes shone, he did not evade, instead charging right towards Red River Wheel.

The two collided as Red River Wheel was thrown backwards, Fang Gong used the chance to give chase.

Dong Ming’s expression was deathly pale: “Is this the strength of a rank eight strength path Gu Immortal?!”

Dong Zhu kept silent as he let out molten flame birds.

Fang Gong kicked and punched, smashing the molten flame birds to a pulp.

In just ten or so breaths of time, Red River Wheel was beaten back again and again, its surface crumbled and looked like it was in a miserable state.

“Fang Gong, don’t be cocky.” With the help of other allies, Xiao Ye Hu finally had a chance to attack.

Wan clan had paid a high price to request his assistance.

Why?

It was to deal with Fang Gong!

Immortal Gu House Chamber Pot was pocket-sized, it could not carry people like normal Immortal Gu Houses, it would also suffer huge damage if it was used to rampage around.

Its specialty was in dealing with Gu Immortals.

Even Fang Gong would be threatened!

“Fang Gong, go die!!” Xiao Ye Hu finally attacked, a pitch-black light lump shot at Fang Gong.

“Fang Gong, you are still not retreating?!” Dong Ming and Dong Zhu shouted together. They were extremely panicked because Red River Wheel was on the verge of destruction.

Fang Gong instead laughed loudly, not even looking at the pitch-black light lump: “This is the battle of Fang clan against the world! How can I, Fang Gong, not stake my life?”

Boom.

Red River Wheel shattered completely!

Dong Ming and Dong Zhu were in absolute horror. They were sent flying in the sky, their surroundings filled with fragments of Red River Wheel and corpses of countless Gu worms.

They looked at Fang Gong, he seemed like a fearless and invincible heavenly deity!

But at the next moment, the pitch-black light lump struck Fang Gong.

“Success!” Xiao Ye Hu shouted in joy.

Wan clan Gu Immortals were exulted.

Whoosh!

Fang Gong moved his arms, directly crushing the pitch-black light lump.

The anti-Fang alliance immortals were shaken and scared, many even subconsciously opened their mouths wide at this inconceivable sight.

“How, how can this be?!” Xiao Ye Hu could not believe it as he stared with wide eyes.

“Your turn next!” Fang Gong looked at Xiao Ye Hu as he said calmly.

At this moment, Xiao Ye Hu’s heart contracted.

He was frightened by Fang Gong’s ferocious momentum, only one thought remained in his mind

— escape!

“Where are you trying to go?!” Fang Gong flew towards Xiao Ye Hu like a meteor, he broke the sonic barrier and left a grand shock wave behind him.

“Save me! My Xiao clan will definitely reward you well!” Xiao Ye Hu ran madly.

Gong Jiao Che, Tang Lan Ke, Qin Lang, Tian Da Ji, and the rest moved to block Fang Gong.

Fang Gong did not dodge but endured all kinds of killer moves forcibly. Like a fierce tiger or a rampaging dragon, he closed in on Xiao Ye Hu.

His aura surged like a rising tiger over ten thousand li!

Xiao Ye Hu could not shake off Fang Gong, he watched in despair as Fang Gong neared him.

“Let this battle be the start of my Fang clan’s rise!” Fang Gong shouted inwardly, his battle intent burned like inferno.

At the edge of the battlefield, high in the sky.

Wan Zi Hong and Zhou Xiong Xin were watching the battle quietly. The former was somewhat restless when she saw this scene.

“Friends from Heavenly Court, it will be best if you watch quietly.” Lu Wei Yin appeared and said

with a smile.

Wan Zi Hong and Zhou Xiong Xin’s expressions changed as they watched with complete vigilance.

At the same time.

Northern Plains.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable activated his luck path investigative method.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did this every once in a while.

He first inspected Heavenly Court.

In his view, Fang Yuan had little immortal essence and would have refined the least number of dao marks. Heavenly Court’s Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was close behind him, she was the main target to be vigilant against.

Heavenly Court’s luck had somewhat increased.

“Looks like Star Constellation Immortal Venerable has already refined most of the Heavenly Court dao marks. It will be increasingly difficult to inspect her later on.”

Afterwards, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable inspected Eastern Sea.

He saw that Fang Yuan’s luck was low, it had slightly strengthened than before, but it was of no significance.

A portion of Fang Yuan and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s luck had split from the main

portion and moved towards Western Desert.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable gazed towards Western Desert and saw a battlefield. The luck of countless people tangled with each other, forming a blood-red color that was mixed with black.

“Looks like Western Desert’s anti-Fang battle has already started.” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable nodded.

Fang clan’s matter had grown quite big, all five regions paid attention to it. Giant Sun Immortal Venerable naturally knew of the details.

He inspected carefully and understood: “Fang clan seems to be holding an advantage, but there is a huge variable. Wan clan is hiding something... I see, so Heavenly Court helped Wan clan like this.”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable laughed coldly as he saw through the secret.

From the start, he did not interfere in Western Desert’s anti-Fang battle.

“Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Heaven Refining Demon Venerable do not cultivate luck path, they don’t know that they are expending their luck in this contest. This is already turning into their weakness!”

“If I am currently in my peak state during my previous life, I can have gain some advantages

with my luck path methods.”

“What a pity, what a pity...”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had to use the remaining immortal essence to refine luck path dao marks.

Besides this, although he had many rank eight luck path Immortal Gu, he did not have a rank nine luck path Immortal Gu.

Chapter 2260: Wan Gu Chou

Rank nine existences, be they Gu Immortals or Immortal Gu, were envied by the heavens, they

could not live forever.

So, in all of humanity’s history, there were only eleven venerables, and they all were restricted

by their lifespan.

There were also very few rank nine Immortal Gu that existed in the world.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable finally took a glance at his luck.

He could not help but frown.

The situation was not good.

It was worse than before.

But from the information he had, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable still could not estimate where

this bad luck came from.

Naturally, he was most suspicious of Heavenly Court.

“What is that old woman, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, playing at?”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was not anxious.

He had methods to change his luck.

But there was still that flaw.

He was tight on immortal essence and they needed to be used to refine dao marks. He did not

have a rank nine luck path Immortal Gu, using rank eight luck path Immortal Gu to change his

rank nine luck was very difficult and would expend a lot more immortal essence.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable soon stopped activating his investigative method.

The longer the contest of three venerables prolonged, the bigger the importance of information.

But Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s inspection duration kept on decreasing.

He needed to consider his immortal essence expenditure, and try to save as much immortal

essence as possible.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable fell into deep thought: ”What is the source of my bad luck?”

“Heavenly Court is the biggest suspect, but I cannot relax my guard against Fang Yuan too! He

has the sovereign immortal body and can cultivate all paths, his potential is absolutely terrifying.

Besides this, he has another advantage. That is refinement path!”

“Refinement path might not be proficient in fighting, but its development potential far surpasses

luck path and blood path. Thus, refinement path has far more potential rank nine Gu than luck

path, blood path, as well as wisdom path and star path.”

Each path had strengths and weaknesses.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable kept luck path a secret and did not spread it, so its development

was limited. Other Gu Immortals would find it difficult to defend against Giant Sun Immortal

Venerable’s luck path methods, but there were few luck path Immortal Gu that could reach rank

nine.

On the contrary, refinement path was probably the most widely developed path. Simply because

refining Gu was an inevitable part of Gu cultivation.

Even Gu cultivators who cultivated other paths would have refined Gu to some extent.

Thus, as refinement path grew, more refinement path Gu cultivators emerged which meant

more refinement path dao marks. Refinement path resources were unceasing, and there were

all kinds of refinement path Immortal Gu. Moreover, refinement path Immortal Gu that could

advance to rank nine became even more numerous.

“Fortunately, Fang Yuan is lacking immortal essence currently, he is still far from refining a rank

nine refinement path Immortal Gu.”

“Maybe, my bad luck is not because of Fang Yuan or Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, but

the other venerables. If other venerables revived, who would be the most problematic for me?”

Fang Yuan had Cooking Luck Pot as well as obscured heavenly secret, although Giant Sun

Immortal Venerable had the ability to inspect him, he did not get proper results.

“If I gain a breakthrough in the blood path Immortal Gu transaction, this luck should change to

good.”

Fang Yuan was not the only one who obstructed Giant Sun Immortal Venerable in terms of

blood path Immortal Gu, Heavenly Court had already been doing so since Blood Sea Ancestor’s

time.

Demon Judgment Board’s core Immortal Gu Blood Relation, and Red Heart Traveler’s heart

blood Immortal Gu were things that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable thirsted for.

Currently, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu was still in a long negotiation with Fang Yuan.

Longevity Heaven was secretly negotiating with Heavenly Court as well for blood path Immortal

Gu, but the progress was almost zero.

Back in Western Desert.

Fang Gong got close to Xiao Ye Hu and punched.

Under his fear, Xiao Ye Hu moved Immortal Gu House Chamber Pot in front to block.

A loud explosion rang as Chamber Pot was destroyed.

The punch continued forward and struck Xiao Ye Hu’s chest.

Xiao Ye Hu flew away like a meteor. His chest had sunk in, large amounts of blood mixed with

internal organs gushed out of his mouth, leaving a trail of blood.

One punch destroyed Chamber Pot and caused Xiao Ye Hu to be on the verge of death.

“Let’s retreat!”

“We can’t fight anymore.”

The anti-Fang alliance army was shaking with fear, their fighting spirit was almost depleted.

Fang Gong’s strength far surpassed their expectations, he was actually not restricted by

Chamber Pot.

This first supreme elder of Fang clan was truly the nemesis of Immortal Gu Houses. Ever since

Fang clan attacked Wan clan’s tall pine oasis until now, he had already destroyed Winding Light

Platform, Red River Wheel, and Xiao clan’s Chamber Pot.

These three Immortal Gu Houses were all at rank seven, they could match rank eight battle

strength!

“There is one more left!” Fang Gong turned around slightly, ignoring the rank seven Gu

Immortals as he glared at Myriad Age Building.

Only Myriad Age Building was left among the anti-Fang alliance army’s Immortal Gu Houses.

Myriad Age Building was a rank seven Immortal Gu House, it could match rank eight. It was the

final pillar of the anti-Fang alliance army, once it fell, Fang clan would obtain complete victory.

This was the most crucial point.

The remaining Gu Immortals might be rank seven elites with their own specialties, but without

Myriad Age Building to stabilize their position, these people would be like a disorderly mob.

“Fang clan has six Immortal Gu Houses, and they are all at rank seven. Our side only has

Myriad Age Building left.”

“Retreat, retreat!”

“Heavenly Court is still not making a move? Sigh, they are really incompetent. Look at how

much Heaven Refining Demon Venerable supported Fang clan, a total of three Immortal Gu

Houses! What did Heavenly Court provide?”

Fang Di Chang displayed a wisdom path Gu Immortal’s strategic ability. At this delicate juncture,

he ordered Fang clan to stop chasing those rank seven Gu Immortals, instead controlling

Immortal Gu Houses to surround Myriad Age Building.

Seeing that Fang clan did not give chase, besides the Wan clan Gu Immortals, everyone else in

the alliance retreated madly.

Wan Xiao and Wan Hao Guang’s expressions were ashen as they retreated into Myriad Age

Building.

Fang clan’s six Immortal Gu Houses encircled Myriad Age Building, Fang clan’s expression was

leisurely as he flew towards Myriad Age Building.

“Surrender, friends of Wan clan. I guarantee in the name of Fang clan that as long as you

surrender and cede a portion of your territories, my Fang clan will not ask for your Immortal Gu,

or kill any of you.” Fang Gong said.

Their conditions were actually so lax.

“We won!!” Fang Leng and Fang Yun were already starting to cheer in joy.

The Fang clan immortals did not object to Fang Gong’s surrender terms.

Fang clan had already discussed this, if this kind of situation happened, they would persuade

Wan clan to surrender.

If Wan clan surrendered, it would be extremely beneficial to Fang clan.

Once Wan clan admitted their defeat, Fang clan could righteously occupy a portion of Wan

clan’s territories.

Wan clan would no longer have a righteous cause to rally the other super forces to organize

another anti-Fang alliance.

Naturally, Wan clan’s headquarters and some important resource points would be given back to

Wan clan.

But for Fang clan, the overall gains were absolutely much larger than losses.

“Lord Lu Wei Yin, looks like Fang clan has won.”

“Naturally. Just look at who is supporting them!”

Two rockman Gu Immortals were standing beside Lu Wei Yin, showing a prideful smile at this

sight.

But Lu Wei Yin was frowning as he sensed something amiss.

“These two Heavenly Court Gu Immortals still have such a relaxed expression, looks like things

are not so simple!”

Heavenly Court’s Zhou Xiong Xin and Wan Zi Hong had an indifferent expression with an

anticipating gaze.

Suddenly, a woman’s voice rang out from Myriad Age Building: ”Fang clan’s descendants are

really amazing, your strategy is also comprehensive, but is my Wan clan so easily bullied?”

Fang clan’s immortals were bewildered.

At this crucial moment, this strange female voice actually spoke as Wan clan’s representative,

who was she?

Did Heavenly Court interfere?

But Fang clan knew the information about Wan Zi Hong, and this was not her voice.

“Fairy, may I ask for your name? This is a fight between Fang clan and Wan clan.” Fang Gong

frowned, asking inquisitively.

“Hahaha!” The mysteriously female immortal laughed loudly. Her voice was hoarse and

unpleasant, but it was filled with complete confidence.

Following the laughter, a vast rank eight aura spread out.

“As wind, dust, and flowers scatter,

People and eras change beyond recognition.

As the frigid bells of time shatter,

None can dispel the sorrow of myriad ages!”

As the recital ended, heaven and earth turned dark.

Cold mournful wind and bleak clouds filled the sky.

Inside several li of radius, all living beings including Gu Immortals of both sides felt an intense

sorrow attacking their minds.

Sorrow, sorrow, and more sorrow!

Dejection, disappointment, depression, worry... all kinds of negative emotions made the people

shed tears, their hearts felt stifled and suffocated.

Fang clan’s six Immortal Gu Houses surrounding Myriad Age Building became unsteady as they

started shaking, almost falling down.

Fang Di Chang, who was inside Thought Expelling Pavilion, was half-kneeling. His expression

was distorted as he resisted Wan clan’s terrifying killer move with all his strength, blood seeping

out of his mouth and nose!

Fang Gong barely managed to resist, retreating in panic as he exclaimed: ”You are Wan Gu

Chou[1. Her name makes up the ’sorrow of myriad ages’ in the poem.]?!”

In just a short few moments, more wrinkles appeared on his face, he was growing old rapidly as

close to one hundred years were extracted from his lifespan!

“Retreat....” Fang Di Chang said with much difficulty.

Fang clan’s six Immortal Gu Houses retreated in panic.

The alliance immortals who had already retreated to the edge of the battlefield were

dumbfounded at this sight.

“Wan Gu Chou?! Isn’t that the strongest peak rank eight female immortal in Wan clan’s history?”

“When she was alive, Wan clan almost dominated the whole Western Desert!”

“She lived for ten thousand years, Myriad Age Building was created by her.”

“She is actually alive?!”

“Right, this is very likely to be Heavenly Court’s move.”

“It must be her! Her move, everlasting sorrow, is famous throughout the history, only she who

cultivates both time path and wisdom path can use it. And she is the only one who can amplify

this move to such a terrifying degree through Myriad Age Building!”

“This move already possesses the flair of pseudo venerable level!!”

The immortals were shaken.

Wan Gu Chou stopped the killer move as she said to the alliance Gu Immortals: ”Are you still

not making a move?”

The immortals understood at once, they charged over with a battle cry.

Fang clan was struck by everlasting sorrow killer move, the sorrowful and depressive feelings

were hard to get rid of, they could not even use twenty percent of their battle strength and had

to retreat in defeat.

Under Myriad Age Building’s lead, the alliance army gave chase.

The immortals first destroyed Smoke Wave Building, then destroyed Thought Expelling Pavilion.

To save Fang Di Chang who was in Thought Expelling Pavilion, Fang Gong and the other

immortals were forced to make a move.

After a deadly battle, Fang Di Chang was rescued, but Fang clan paid a disastrous price for this.

Their most exceptional Immortal Gu House Fallen Flower Hall was destroyed, Fang Dong Xi

and Fang An Lei, these two elite rank sevens, died in the battle.

Finally, Fang clan brought the remaining three damaged Immortal Gu Houses and left the

battlefield.

Chapter 2261: New Anti-Fang Alliance

Wang Xiao Er woke up from his sleep.

“Wasn’t I imprisoned? Where am I now?” Wang Xiao Er was puzzled, he found that he was in a

vast wasteland.

“Quickly, escape!”

“Escape, escape!”

A large wave of humans suddenly surged out.

Crack!

With a loud sound, lightning struck the ground.

Following that, the earth and mountains shook. Explosions occurred loudly as the ground began

to collapse.

In ten or so breaths of time, the surrounding ten li of area had become a giant crater.

The crater enclosed all the people including Wang Xiao Er.

Wang Xiao Er was dazed as he was sandwiched between the crowd.

The surrounding people were in disorder and panic, Wang Xiao Er also had the same feelings.

He did not know what happened.

Before this, he was captured by Fang Dong Xi in Sand Heap blessed land. Fang Dong Xi soul

searched him and obtained information regarding Hu Land.

During the contest over Sand Heap blessed land, Fang Dong Xi lost his soul cores. Fortunately,

Fang Dong Xi captured Wang Xiao Er and obtained the secret information regarding Hu Land.

Fang Dong Xi used this precious information to make up for his mistake. On the other hand, he

also learned of the peculiarity of Wang Xiao Er’s body.

Fang Dong Xi imprisoned Wang Xiao Er in his immortal aperture, and specially constructed an

underground prison. He studied and experimented on Wang Xiao Er’s body many times, but still

did not understand what was going on with Wang Xiao Er’s body.

“All of you, shut up!” A figure suddenly appeared in the sky.

Wang Xiao Er and others looked up.

“Your ancestor Fang Dong Xi has already died in battle, everything is now all my, Xiao Ye Hu’s,

property. You are also my captives! Stay here, I will make sure you live a life worse than death if

you dare to escape!”

Xiao Ye Hu’s expression was cold and malevolent.

The chaotic crowd was shivering like a cicada under his threat.

Fang Dong Xi and Fang An Lei died in battle to protect Fang Di Chang. They were both rank

seven Gu Immortals, their immortal apertures landed on the ground and opened its door to

absorb heaven and earth qi, becoming an unowned blessed land.

Xiao Ye Hu took the chance to enter and plunder his battle spoils.

But the plundered resources did not satisfy Xiao Ye Hu.

His loss was extremely severe, his Immortal Gu House Chamber Pot was destroyed by Fang

Gong. Even emptying Fang Dong Xi’s immortal aperture only made up for a meager amount of

the losses.

“This won’t do, Wan clan must give me an answer!” Xiao Ye Hu’s expression was unsightly.

After he stabilized Dong Xi blessed land’s situation, he quickly left to look for Wan clan.

At this time, the anti-Fang alliance had already succeeded in regaining Wan clan headquarters

blessed land.

The anti-Fang alliance immortals were resting here for the moment.

Xiao Ye Hu came before a hall, he restrained his unsightly expression and said loudly: ”Senior

Wan Gu Chou, junior Xiao Ye Hu is here as Xiao clan’s representative. Please meet me, we

need to discuss some matters.”

Times had changed.

Wan Gu Chou suddenly revived and defeated Fang clan. Her impressive might shook the whole

of Western Desert’s Gu Immortal world.

In front of such an expert, Xiao Ye Hu had to restrain himself.

Soon, Xiao Ye Hu received permission. He entered the hall and saw Wan Gu Chou sitting on

the main seat.

Wan Gu Chou was wearing a white garment, her hair was silvery white, she looked quite old.

Wan Hao Guang was standing to her left, with Wan Xiao on her right.

“Hehehe.” She looked at Xiao Ye Hu and laughed, her laughter was hoarse and terrifying:

“Junior from Xiao clan, you came at the right time. I have something to discuss with you. Take a

seat and wait for a while.”

“Okay.” Xiao Ye Hu did not dare to refute, he chose a seat to sit.

After a short while, other anti-Fang alliance Gu Immortals were also invited into the hall.

Even Heavenly Court’s two Gu Immortals Wan Zi Hong and Zhou Xiong Xin were present.

Wan Gu Chou looked around and said: ”Although Fang clan was defeated, they stole many of

my clan’s resource points. My Wan clan is unable to pay the price agreed upon with your clans.”

“But, this is a huge opportunity for us.”

“Fang clan suffered a heavy loss, their strength has fallen sharply. As long as we give chase,

Fang clan will not be able to defend. They have fallen to the demonic path, we must get rid of

them! At that time, we will all get a share of the battle spoils.”

The immortals felt a chill as they listened.

This Wan Gu Chou was extremely shameless, directly saying she did not have a way to pay

them, forcing the anti-Fang alliance to continue fighting.

Her methods were also vicious, she wanted to follow up the victory by giving chase and

eradicating Fang clan.

But this was indeed a good opportunity.

The immortals were moved.

Fang clan sold a large number of Wan clan’s resource points, but sold very few of their own

resource points. Their foundation was still there.

Now was the perfect time to beat them down.

‘Wan clan is sinister, they deliberately concealed Wan Gu Chou and kept us in dark.’

‘Wan Gu Chou kept on hiding, she only made a move when we crumbled. And with just one

move, she defeated Fang clan, creating the current situation which is the most favorable to Wan

clan!’

‘On the surface, Wan clan transacted the most with Xiao clan; in reality, their biggest

collaborator is Heavenly Court!’

None of the immortals here were stupid, they had already realized the situation.

If Wan Gu Chou had made a move earlier, even if the anti-Fang alliance defeated Fang clan,

most of the battle merits would belong to the alliance Gu Immortals.

But Wan Gu Chou made a move only at the final juncture, immediately revitalizing Wan clan’s

prestige. The alliance immortals did not have the qualification to talk of their merits or

shamelessly ask for payment.

“We need to eradicate evil completely. Fang clan broke the rules, what rights does such a

demonic super clan have to continue existing in Western Desert’s Gu Immortal world?”

“I agree with Senior Wan Gu Chou’s plan.”

“But we should discuss how we distribute the spoils.”

The immortals had participated in the previous large battle, they all suffered losses; some

needed to urgently make up for it, like Xiao Ye Hu. Some thought since they had to undergo

danger, they might as well reap benefits.

Seeing the Gu Immortals expressing their agreement, Wan Gu Chou looked at the two

Heavenly Court Gu Immortals: ”Heavenly Court has been the leader of humanity since ancient

times, the banner of the righteous path. We will need your help in this battle.”

Wan Gu Chou was deeply aware: Compared to Western Desert’s Gu Immortals, Heavenly

Court’s financial support was much more important.

Without Heavenly Court’s support, Wan clan had no way to attack Fang clan.

Wan clan would have to pay a lot to collaborate with Heavenly Court, but the gains were also

equally great.

Wan Gu Chou herself was revived by Heavenly Court.

Right now, a lot of her rank eight time path Immortal Gu were lent by Heavenly Court.

Even her everlasting sorrow killer move was personally modified by Star Constellation Immortal

Venerable!

Zhou Xiong Xin and Wan Zi Hong glanced at each other, all the development so far did not

exceed Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s calculations.

This was also the moment that these two Heavenly Court immortals were waiting for.

At the next moment, Zhou Xiong Xin stood up: ”Friends of Western Desert, it is my Heavenly

Court duty to eliminate the demonic path, we are very happy to support you.”

“Right now, Fang clan’s calamity is before them. Why did they have such guts to attack the

alliance? The true root issue is not Fang clan but Eastern Sea’s Heaven Refining Demon

Venerable!”

“Heavenly Court is willing to continue to support you, but our condition is that you are not

allowed to join the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance!”

The hall fell into silence as Gu Immortals looked at each other.

Wan Gu Chou broke the silence: ”My Wan clan agrees!”

Wan clan had already become Heavenly Court’s supporter through the anti-Fang battle.

Wan Gu Chou spoke: ”Friend Xiao Ye Hu, what do you think?”

Xiao Ye Hu’s expression was quite unsightly. Wan Gu Chou intentionally picked his name and

forced him into a corner. He had no choice but to state his position.

He snorted coldly: ”I, Xiao Ye Hu, am obviously not willing to associate with the demonic path,

but that is just my individual stance. How can I casually represent my Xiao clan in agreeing to

this? I have to ask for guidance from my Xiao clan’s first supreme elder!”

It was a delaying tactic.

But Zhou Xiong Xin had already expected it: ”Then, Xiao Ye Hu, please contact your clan’s

leading Gu Immortals right now. I believe that the difference between righteous and demonic is

deeply rooted in people’s hearts. Xiao clan is one of the role models of Western Desert’s

righteous path, you will not make a mistake in this major matter.”

Wan Gu Chou immediately nodded, echoing Heavenly Court immortals: ”Let’s do it like this,

friends, please ask for guidance from your clan’s leaders, and we will then discuss the matter of

the distribution of spoils.”

She pretended to be tolerant: ”If any clan is not willing, we will not criticize them. In this

anti-Fang battle, you do not have any merits but you worked hard. If you don’t want to continue

in anti-Fang alliance, my Wan clan will bid you farewell and won’t make things difficult for you.”

The immortals cursed inwardly.

They had not gotten any payment, or maybe only a small portion of it.

If they did not agree to Heavenly Court’s condition, Wan Gu Chou was going to drive them away

from the anti-Fang alliance.

Only if they were in anti-Fang alliance could they get their payment as well as the battle spoils in

the upcoming battle against Fang clan.

A while later.

The Gu Immortals finished asking for instructions. No one left.

Under the pressure of righteousness, Western Desert’s super clans could not risk going against

the public opinion and leave the alliance.

Moreover, if they left the alliance at this point, they could not get any benefits.

Fang clan was like a piece of fat meat that lured these colossal vultures.

“Good, friends, you have not let me down!” Wan Gu Chou stood up and said with a smile.

Right now, a new opportunity lied before her.

She was now the alliance leader of the anti-Fang alliance. As long as she led the alliance and

defeated Fang clan, her reputation would rise to the peak of Western Desert’s Gu Immortal

world.

At that time, she would be like Wu Yong, becoming the publicly recognized leader of the

Western Desert Gu Immortal world.

Zhou Xiong Xin and Wan Zi Hong were smiling.

This was all within Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s calculations.

It was very advantageous for Heavenly Court to help Wan Gu Chou become the leader of

Western Desert.

“Fang Yuan is number one in Gu refinement, but how can he be Star Constellation Immortal

Venerable’s match in terms of methods?” Zhou Xiong Xin laughed inwardly.

The very day, Wan Gu Chou announced the establishment of new anti-Fang alliance.

With the revival of this strongest expert of Wan clan, the situation of the whole Western Desert

Gu Immortal world changed suddenly.

Almost all the Gu Immortals of the five regions were paying close attention to it.

“This contest ended in Heavenly Court’s victory.”

“Fang clan is in danger!”

“I did not expect Heavenly Court to be able to revive other Gu Immortals and not just their own

Heavenly Court members.”

“The big picture is still in under the control of the venerables.”

“If Fang Yuan were to make a move, this Wan Gu Chou will only be a minor joke!”

“Hmph, Fang Yuan can make a move, but can’t Star Constellation Immortal Venerable do the

same?”

“Haha, it’s best if the two venerables fight, then Ancestor Giant Sun can reap the benefits of their conflict.”

Chapter 2262: Righteousness with Benefits to Gain

Back in Western Desert.

Myriad ore desert.

Shi Zhong looked at the message from Shi clan with an indifferent expression.

“Fang clan lost. Looks like Shi Kang has another chance now.”

“However, Fang clan only lost two rank seven Gu Immortals and three Immortal Gu Houses,

they still have some battle strength left.”

Shi Zhong was a person who was ostracized by Shi clan, while Shi Kang was a rising star who

was nurtured by the clan.

Shi Zhong flattered Shi Kang on the surface, but was envious and hated him inwardly.

“Regardless of the battle results, it has nothing to do with me.”

“I still need to rely on myself.”

Shi Zhong gritted his teeth as he thought of how his recent attempt at refining wealth Immortal

Gu failed again.

The thought of asking Fang Yuan to help refine Gu flashed in his mind.

Shi Zhong gritted his teeth as he made a decision.

“Looks like I must sell some wealth mortal Gu.” Shi Zhong had not received any support, and

had spent almost all his assets in his attempts to refine wealth Immortal Gu.

He was already dirt-poor right now. He had to sell some stuff to exchange for immortal materials

for another attempt at Gu refinement.

The things he could sell were only wealth mortal Gu.

Although he had failed in his refinement repeatedly, he also had some gains.

He could not refine wealth Immortal Gu, but he had refined wealth mortal Gu.

Connecting to treasure yellow heaven, Shi Zhong hesitated for a long while before choosing to

put a dozen or so wealth mortal Gu in treasure yellow heaven.

Wealth mortal Gu gathered into a lump and formed a pillar of treasure light.

There was an abundant amount of treasure light, but these were clearly mortal Gu. Such an

abnormality attracted the attention of other Gu Immortals.

“What Gu is this, how can it form such a treasure light?” Nu Er Tu asked.

It had been more than a year since he advanced to a rank six Gu Immortal. Although it was due

to the help of Nu Er tribe, he was still a newbie rank six Gu Immortal.

Whenever he had time, he would connect to treasure yellow heaven and explore with his divine

sense to increase his knowledge.

Nu Er Tu was the great-grandson of Gu Immortal Nu Er Chi, he had also participated in the final

Imperial Court contest.

He was proficient in enslaving leopards and had been recognized as one of the five beast kings

by Northern Plains’ Gu Masters, along with Fang Yuan’s disguise of Chang Shan Yin.

“This is wealth Gu.” Shi Zhong replied.

Nu Er Tu was stunned, and asked with even more curiosity: ”Wealth Gu? Isn’t this the legendary

Gu recorded in <<The Legends of Ren Zu>>? But this mortal Gu...”

Shi Zhong snorted coldly: ”I painstakingly researched and created its mortal Gu recipe. These

rank five mortal Gu can turn into any rank five Gu material.”

Nu Er Tu’s mind shook, asking: ”Any rank five Gu material? Can it be used multiple times?”

Shi Zhong’s voice was softer now: ”These are one-time consumable Gu.”

If not for this, he would not have taken them out to sell.

Shi Zhong had been trying to refine immortal level wealth Gu. If he sold many wealth mortal Gu,

there was the risk of someone deducing its Immortal Gu recipe.

At that time, it would be the same as Shi Zhong creating his own rivals.

If he had an alternative, Shi Zhong would not sell these wealth Gu. Moreover, he was only

selling a dozen of these mortal Gu.

Nu Er Tu thought: ”These wealth Gu can only turn into any rank five Gu material, they are not

practical. As a Gu Immortal, which rank five Gu material can’t we get? But this involves the

legendary wealth Gu, it is not a bad idea to buy some for research or give to others.”

Nu Er Tu asked for the price, but soon, his divine sense fluctuated intensely: ”You are asking for

such a high price for a mortal Gu? Are you insane?”

Shi Zhong said: ”At first glance, using a mortal Gu to exchange for immortal materials is indeed

a fantasy. But just think of it, as long as you have these mortal Gu, you have the chance to

deduce its Immortal Gu recipe.”

“Just think about it, how high of a value does wealth Immortal Gu have!”

“I will be honest, these mortal Gu are one of a kind in this world, and it is likely that only these

many are left.”

“I also obtained these from a fortuitous encounter.”

“Unfortunately, I have no proficiency in Gu refinement. If not for me being lacking on funds, I

would not be selling them.”

“How much do you want? If you buy three, I can give you a discount.”

Shi Zhong had a glib tongue, Nu Er Tu fell into hesitation.

Shi Zhong’s words were reasonable.

But was it worth it to use a large amount of immortal materials to exchange for a hope of

deducing an Immortal Gu recipe?

Nu Er Tu was not stupid, his thoughts changed as he said: ”It is not an issue to buy two or three

wealth mortal Gu. But I will like to know something, where did you obtain these?”

Shi Zhong was immediately vigilant: ”Your question is somewhat going overboard. I don’t want

to get into any trouble. Moreover, if I really did what you want and gave you the information, how

can you confirm if it is real?”

“That is true.” Nu Er Tu hesitated once again.

Right at this time, another divine sense said excitedly: ”Wealth Gu are actually here! I will buy

them, I will buy all of the stock that you have.”

Shi Zhong responded: ”Friend, please be calm and listen to my price.”

The mysterious Gu Immortal stopped for a while after hearing the price, before nodding: ”Alright,

I want all of them!”

Shi Zhong was dazed, while Nu Er Tu was vigilant.

Shi Zhong thought, and said: ”It is not that I don’t want to sell them all to you, but you came

slightly late. This friend here came first and our deal is almost done.”

Shi Zhong did not want sell all the wealth Gu to one person. If he did that, there would be too

many clues, and the possibility of deducing an Immortal Gu recipe would be very high.

This mysterious Gu Immortal’s attitude made Shi Zong feel that something was strange.

Just in case, he hoped to sell some to Nu Er Tu.

But Nu Er Tu backed out.

“This mysterious Gu Immortal appeared just as I was hesitating. Is this a scheme to urge me to

buy some wealth Gu?”

Nu Er Tu had heard of such scams.

In the end, he gave up the notion of buying any.

Shi Zhong hesitated for a while, he had no choice but to sell all the wealth Gu to the mysterious

Gu Immortal.

After gathering enough immortal materials, he left treasure yellow heaven to prepare for Gu

refinement once again.

“He really sold them?” Nu Er Tu felt somewhat disappointed.

And that mysterious Gu Immortal left treasure yellow heaven after obtaining wealth Gu.

He was Spirit Butterfly Valley’s Gu Immortal Xiao Bai Hong.

Xiao Bai Hong handed these wealth Gu to rank five Gu Master Xiao Qi Xing who was standing

beside him.

Xiao Qi Xing was Xiao Bai Hong’s great-grandson, one of the ten children of human path who

obtained huge support from Heavenly Court.

Xiao Bai Hong said: ”Qi Xing, are these wealth Gu really helpful to you?”

Xiao Qi Xing said: ”Great grandfather, I cultivate human path and have recently obtained a Gu

Immortal true inheritance by chance. This true inheritance is incomplete, but it has ten or so

Immortal Gu recipes of justice Gu. The most exceptional Immortal Gu recipe among them uses

wealth Immortal Gu as the supplementary material to refine justice Immortal Gu.”

“Right now, although we don’t have wealth Immortal Gu, we can modify that Immortal Gu recipe

based on these mortal Gu.”

“Once we refine justice Immortal Gu, I can use it as my vital Gu and officially become a human

path Gu Immortal!”

All of the ten children of human path were aware of the advantages of this path, thus they all

planned to become human path Gu Immortals.

But to do that, they needed a human path Gu worm as their vital Gu.

Xiao Qi Xing had great ambitions, he wanted to obtain rank six justice Immortal Gu and make it

his vital Gu.

If his immortal ascension went smoothly, under the ideal conditions, his vital Gu would also

advance to become rank seven!

Like that, rank six Xiao Qi Xing would have a rank seven vital Immortal Gu.

“Justice Gu is no doubt a human path Gu worm.”

“Using it together with soldier Gu, sergeant Gu, lieutenant Gu, and so on, I can use the human

path killer move, commander of justice!”

“This move may become my trump card.”

Xiao Qi Xing excitedly explained his cultivation plan.

Xiao Bai Hong laughed loudly, stroking Xiao Qi Xing’s head: ”Good, good, good, since you have

such lofty ambitions, I will use all our resources to lend you a hand!”

Southern Border, Tie clan.

“Good, good, good, righteousness exists in people’s hearts after all!” Tie Qu Zhong laughed

heartily.

“Lord Qu Zhong, what could make you so happy?” A female voice resounded.

Tie Qu Zhong looked to the side and saw a heroic looking rank five female Gu Master, he

smiled: ”Ah, Tie Ruo Nan. Look, this is the latest battle report about Western Desert’s Fang

clan.”

Tie Qu Zhong handed an information path mortal Gu to Tie Ruo Nan.

Tie Ruo Nan looked into the Gu, her expression was slightly moved: ”So this happened while

we were in closed cultivation inside Demon Suppression Tower.”

Tie Qu Zhong said: ”I already felt that Fang clan was a shoddy force, they got involved with

Fang Yuan, they are the shame of Western Desert’s righteous path, they don’t even have any of

the righteous path’s demeanor. Now, it looks like I was right! Fang clan’s members are

completely insane to associate with a demon like Fang Yuan. Now, they have been defeated,

this miserable defeat will be Fang Yuan’s outcome in the future.”

Tie Ruo Nan nodded: ”Since ancient times, righteousness has always triumphed over evil. The

demonic path can be rampant for a while, but the strength and hope of the righteous path will

exist in this world forever.”

These two had always hated Fang Yuan.

First, Tie clan’s behavior had always been to destroy the demonic path.

Second, the two hated Fang Yuan personally.

There was no need to speak about Tie Ruo Nan, the hatred had already incurred back in Qing

Mao Mountain when her father died.

Tie Qu Zhong had once participated in hunting down Fang Yuan, but was captured by the latter

and his edge Immortal Gu was stolen as well. Although he was released in the end, his immortal

aperture was also taken away by Fang Yuan.

Tie Qu Zhong could only restart his cultivation, he was still a Gu Master now.

Tie Ruo Nan continued to analyze: ”Heavenly Court is worthy of being the role model of the

righteous path, the leader of humanity. They supported Wan clan by reviving Wan Gu Chou,

they would rather support with Immortal Gu, immortal essence stones and so on, than to directly

interfere in Western Desert’s political affairs, this is the noble demeanor of the righteous path.”

“Fang clan’s threat is not the destruction of Wan clan. Wan clan is only one of the many forces,

there are still a large number of super forces even if it is destroyed. Fang clan’s greatest threat

is the fact that they can corrupt people’s hearts, making other Gu Immortals and super forces

join the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance. But now, Heavenly Court has given another

option to everyone.”

“Heavenly Court has immortal essence stones, they can support with Immortal Gu, and even

revive Gu Immortals. Wan clan must have paid a huge price to obtain such support. This is

Heavenly Court’s deep intention.”

“Only righteousness with benefits to gain can be promoted and wildly spread to everyone. Such

righteousness is firm and stable. An overly virtuous type of righteousness is instead dubious

and hypocritical, it cannot be widely spread, and will only make righteousness seem weak.”

Chapter 2263: Selling to the Point of Bankruptcy

Tie Qu Zhong nodded his head repeatedly, he looked at Tie Ruo Nan with an unconcealed gaze

of appreciation.

Previously, when Tie Qu Zhong heard that Tie Mian Shen chose Tie Ruo Nan to inherit the Iron

Mask true inheritance, he had some doubts.

But over this period of interaction, Tie Qu Zhong fully approved of Tie Ruo Nan, he felt that she

was the rising star with most potential in this generation.

“Tie Ruo Nan, it is great that you have such a deep awareness of the situation.”

“Fang Yuan is evil, he seized my immortal aperture and forced me to use second aperture to

cultivate, causing me to be dependent on him. My future is ruined, my prospects are bleak. But

you have bright prospects. Your current accumulation is already enough to undergo immortal

ascension!” Tie Qu Zhong said in a gratified tone.

Tie Ruo Nan did not pretend to be modest: ”Yes. I was in closed cultivation inside Demon

Suppression Tower recently, I have consulted many seniors in the clan regarding their immortal

ascension experience, I am 80-90% confident in passing the immortal ascension!”

“Good. But you need to slow down a little. The two heavens are merging, causing constant

turbulence and heaven’s will to be chaotic, you will suffer losses if you undergo immortal

ascension at this time. The opportunity of natural inspiration comes only once in a lifetime, but it

is very important.” Tie Qu Zhong instructed.

“Oh? I would like to hear the details.”

Tie Qu Zhong explained: ”In the process of natural inspiration, a Gu cultivator can question

heaven’s will and obtain an answer. If the question is too difficult and surpasses the limits of

heaven and earth, you won’t obtain any answer.”

“For instance, if you ask for a method of eternal life during natural inspiration, heaven and earth

has no way to answer you.”

“If the question is too simple, the Gu cultivator can obtain an answer, but they will not be making

the best use of this precious opportunity. That will be extremely unfortunate.”

“The ideal situation is to ask a question of moderate difficulty and obtain a perfect answer. But

this situation is too rare, and we have no way to grasp it.”

“So, the most mature method is to ask a slightly more difficult question. As such, the answer will

be correct but not complete as it will be lacking a small portion.”

“The remaining portion can be completed through deductions using manpower and material

resources in the future.”

“This is the most effective way to use natural inspiration.”

Tie Ruo Nan’s eyes shined as she asked: ”Then how can I judge the difficulty of these

questions?”

“Generally speaking, asking about Immortal Gu recipes of common rank seven Immortal Gu is

the standard for this. Any Gu worms related to <<The Legends of Ren Zu>> are not ordinary

Gu.”

“Besides this, ask about things closely related to you. For instance, you cultivate metal path, ask

questions relating to metal path. But if you ask about earth path or other paths, the effect will be

low. And you need to be very careful if you want to ask about things relating to dream path.”

At the same time.

Southern Border.

Iron Tooth Mountain.

In a nameless cave.

Wu Yong cupped his fists and greeted with a smile: ”I brought some good wine this time.”

In front of Wu Yong was an old Gu Immortal. He was sitting cross-legged on the ground, he

slowly opened his eyes like he had just woken up.

The old man sighed: ”Lord Wu Yong, this is the third time you have paid me a visit. You are a

rank eight Gu cultivator, the alliance leader of Southern Alliance, but have given such special

treatment to a mere rank seven Gu Immortal like me.”

“I understand your intention, but I only want to cultivate in seclusion, I have no wish to

participate in the struggles and conflicts of the world.”

“Your wine is fragrant, but I don’t have the fortune to enjoy it.”

This old man was a secluded cultivator, he cultivated wisdom path and was called Forgotten

Daoist.

Wu clan specialized in wind path, they had no advantages in wisdom path.

Wu Yong had been looking for reliable talents. When he learned that Forgotten Daoist was living

on Iron Tooth Mountain, he personally visited three times to recruit him.

Wu Yong said grimly: ”Friend, you are wrong. Right now, the two heavens are merging, the war

of the five regions is almost before us. Who can possibly stay out of it?”

“Even if you are unwilling to conflict with others, in this chaotic world, there are always people

who want to cause trouble, like Western Desert’s Fang clan.”

“With some support from Fang Yuan, Fang clan decisively invaded Wan clan, causing Wan

clan’s first supreme elder to perish in battle.”

“This is the signal of the upcoming chaotic world.”

“Even if Heavenly Court supported Wan clan to victory, what is the main difference between Star

Constellation Immortal Venerable and Fang Yuan?”

“As a wisdom path Gu cultivator, you must have understood it.”

Forgotten Daoist heaved a long sigh: ”It is better to be a dog during peaceful times, than a man

involved in brutal chaos. In the present world, Great Love Immortal Venerable, Star

Constellation Immortal Venerable, and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable are leading an ultimate

force of a region each. They have robust foundation, they can easily topple the balance

between super forces. As for you, Wu Yong, you can hardly restrain your excitement and urge to

make a move, but I can only see misery in this.”

“Lord Wu Yong, you don’t need to urge me anymore, please leave.”

Wu Yong sighed, he could only hold his expectations for the future. After looking at Forgotten

Daoist, he left while feeling it was a deep pity.

This world was huge.

There was Shi Zhong who worked hard and tried to refine Immortal Gu, there was also Xiao Qi

Xing who used his great-grandfather’s help to attempt a rank seven vital Gu even before

advancing to Gu Immortal.

There was Nu Er Tu, who already advanced to a Gu Immortal with the clan’s help, there was

also a Gu Master, Tie Ruo Nan, who cultivated metal path, she obtained her senior’s guidance

and learned of the secret of natural inspiration.

There was Wu Yong with great ambition, and also Forgotten Daoist, who was content with living

in seclusion and was unwilling to get involved in disputes.

And finally, there was a super force whose future was dark and currently faced a precarious

situation — Fang clan.

In Fang clan headquarters.

The atmosphere was heavy in the discussion hall.

Fang clan lost.

Their losses were severe!

What should they do?

Be it Fang Gong, Fang Di Chang, or Fang Leng and Fang Yun, their mood was extremely

heavy.

Wan Gu Chou reclaimed all the lost territories of Wan clan, but the anti-Fang alliance was still

there.

If not for the alliance discussing about the distribution of spoils, they would have already

attacked Fang clan.

Although Fang clan still had the strength to fight, their hope of winning was negligible.

Right at this time, Lu Wei Yin suddenly paid a visit.

The Fang clan immortals were moved.

“Quick, invite him in!” Fang Gong had just finished speaking, when he stood up, ”No, come with

me, we will welcome him together.”

Fang clan’s immortals invited Lu Wei Yin into the hall.

Lu Wei Yin saw the dejected expressions of Fang clan immortals: ”Everlasting sorrow is indeed

an amazing killer move. According to what I know, everlasting sorrow is a compound killer move

created from time path and wisdom path. Once the target’s feelings are influenced by this killer

move, their lifespan will decrease rapidly. The decreased lifespan will strengthen the killer

move’s power, making the sorrowful emotions even more violent. The emotions will shroud the

heart, and the target’s battle intent will fall to a minimum.”

Fang Hua Sheng sighed: ”This killer move is a lot different from the historical records. I tried my

best to treat it, but there are still many negative emotions left in our hearts, they can only

dissipate slowly with time.”

Lu Wei Yin laughed: ”Don’t worry, I brought a special Immortal Gu this time, please try it.”

Saying so, he gave an Immortal Gu to Fang Di Chang.

This was a rank seven wisdom path Immortal Gu.

After Fang Di Chang activated it with much difficulty, the Immortal Gu let out a profound light

that covered his whole body.

After a while, Fang Di Chang recovered his mental state. His body was relaxed and the

sorrowful emotions that shrouded his heart were already gone.

“This is a good Immortal Gu.” Fang Di Chang praised.

Lu Wei Yin continued his words: ”My alliance leader knows of Fang clan’s defeat, so he

specially refined this Immortal Gu. With this wisdom path Immortal Gu, it is easy to remove the

remnant power of the killer move everlasting sorrow.”

“Besides this Immortal Gu, there are also several killer moves with it as the core. One of them

can even defend against everlasting sorrow, albeit with difficulty.”

“You only need to pay a super resource point to buy them all.”

Fang Di Chang smiled bitterly and was about to speak.

But Lu Wei Yin added: ”No need to grieve, my friends. I know Fang clan lost Fang Dong Xi and

Fang An Lei in this battle. This is a disastrous loss for Fang clan!”

“But no worries. Heavenly Court has methods to revive Wan Gu Chou, how can my Lord Fang

Yuan not have them?”

“You only need to pay two giant resource points for Lord Alliance Leader to revive those two, but

their cultivation will be at rank six.”

This time, the Fang clan immortals’ expressions changed.

“Really? Can An Lei really be revived?” Fang Chen was very excited.

He was Fang clan’s son-in-law, Fang An Lei was his wife.

Lu Wei Yin smiled: ”In the previous transactions with your clan, there was one transaction which

asked for your human qi. These portions of human qi are the key to reviving you.”

“There are no issues with the revival. Not only this, there is also no issue with restoring the

cultivation of those two to rank seven. You just need to add two additional giant resource

points.”

“Naturally, if you want those two’s cultivation to be raised to rank eight, that is also possible. As

long as you can afford it, with the vast powers of our Lord Alliance Leader, you will not be

disappointed.”

“Even rank eight cultivation level can be transacted?” Fang Gong was stunned.

The other Fang clan Gu Immortals had complicated expressions.

Rank eight cultivation level had once been the highest achievement, but in the last few decades,

pseudo venerables took the stage one after the other, venerables also started reviving. The

status of rank eight cultivation fell again and again.

Now, rank eight cultivation had become a commodity to be transacted at will!

This made the Fang clan immortals become somewhat dazed.

Lu Wei Yin looked around and asked: ”You still don’t get it? The world has already undergone

an intense change ever since the destruction of fate Gu.”

“This is true for Immortal Gu Houses, rank eight Gu Immortals, and even venerables.”

“This change can be said to completely flip societal norms, even super forces will only be a

ripple in the waves of time if they cannot adapt to this change, wiped out in just a moment.”

Fang Di Chang narrowed his eyes: ”Lord Lu Wei Yin, you seem to have another meaning

behind your words.”

Lu Wei Yin chuckled: ”I will be direct then, your situation is very dangerous, how will Fang clan

defend against the anti-Fang alliance?”

“If you just defend, no matter how much more powerful the immortal formation you possess, you

will only be delaying your destruction.”

“You can only deal with this intense change by taking drastic measures!”

“Naturally, the choice belongs to you. Lord Alliance Leader will not personally interfere in

Western Desert’s internal battle. But if I were you, I would sell all the resource points to

exchange for Immortal Gu, immortal materials, and revive Fang clan’s Gu Immortals.”

Fang Gong’s and Fang Di Chang’s pupils shrunk slightly.

The remaining Gu Immortals were in an uproar.

“How can we do that? Such an action is too unfilial.”

“Our Fang clan’s foundation will be gone without these resource points.”

“If we do this, how can we face our ancestors when we die?!”

“This is my Fang clan’s foundation!”

The Fang clan immortals reacted agitatedly, looking at Lu Wei Yin with hatred and ferocity.

Lu Wei Yin shrugged his shoulders, saying calmly: ”Whether you sell or not, it is up to you. I am

only giving a small suggestion.”

“We will sell.” Fang Di Chang’s voice was extremely hoarse.

Fang Gong did not retort, he kept silent.

“Lord Fang Di Chang!!” Some Fang clan Gu Immortals stood up in agitation.

But Fang Di Chang’s next sentence silenced these Gu Immortals completely.

“If we don’t sell the resource points, are you able to defend them?”

Chapter 2264: Where There’s Life, There’s Hope

Sitting on a deserted mound, Fang Di Chang was still as a rock.

Ever since the two heavens merged, there was no longer day or night, in place of that was a mix

of black and white in the sky.

Thus, different areas had different intensity of brightness.

Fang Di Chang was currently in the darkness, he looked at the empty mound expressionlessly,

it was a barren desert with no vegetation in sight.

But because of the fusion of two heavens, this huge desert was split into two areas, one was

bright while the other was dark.

This was tassel desert, a super resource point of Fang clan.

Every year, at a certain period, earth roots would grow here like grass or willow branches, they

were soft but durable.

The earth roots were long or short, they ranged from mortal materials to rank eight immortal

materials.

At peak growth, the earth roots would cover the entire tassel desert, when wind blew, looking

from above, it would seem like a huge sea made of earth roots, the waves would look grand and

impressive.

This was Fang clan’s number one resource point, it was the pride of all Fang clan Gu Immortals.

But now, it was being sold to Fang Yuan.

Once this transaction was done, it would never be returned, this was farewell.

Fang Di Chang had a plain expression but his heart was like this desert, it was barren and cold.

Fang Gong flew over from afar, he landed on the barren mound and stood beside Fang Di

Chang.

“I knew you were here.” Fang Gong sighed.

Fang Di Chang, who was seated, suddenly had a twisted expression as he clenched his fists:

“Fang Yuan did this on purpose!”

“I’m afraid he has known about Wan Gu Chou all along, but he did not say it and caused our

clan to suffer a huge loss!”

Fang Gong was stunned.

Fang Di Chang continued: ”Even if he did not know about Wan Gu Chou, he concealed the

secret that he could revive our clan’s Gu Immortals! As long as he mentioned it, even if he

vaguely hinted it, I would have known.”

“If I had known that venerables are able to easily revive Gu Immortals, I would be on guard

against a threat like Wan Gu Chou!”

“In fact, we might have exchanged for that forgotten sorrow Immortal Gu earlier, if we could

defend against Wan Gu Chou’s killer move, we would not have lost, the alliance against Wan

clan would have succeeded!”

Towards the end, Fang Di Chang was basically screaming his lungs out.

He was right.

Back then, the situation was hanging on a thread.

The battle between Fang clan and the alliance against Fang clan was very close.

If they knew about Wan Gu Chou, Fang clan would not sent all six Immortal Gu Houses to

attack Myriad Age Building, Wan Gu Chou’s killer move had a limited range after all.

But at that time, Fang clan did not know about this information, they pressured Wan clan’s

members to try to obtain the greatest benefit.

“Alright.” Fang Gong smiled bitterly: ”Since it has already happened, second supreme elder, no

need to ponder upon it. We do not have Spring Autumn Cicada to return to the past.”

“Earlier, when Heavenly Court revived Gu Immortals, they were all their members. Everyone

guessed that their revival had something to do with their contributed immortal apertures.

Furthermore, because Fang Yuan nearly destroyed the entire immortal graveyard, it is very hard

to deduce Wan Gu Chou’s revival.”

Fang Di Chang had a cold expression: ”No, it is Fang Yuan, everything is caused by Fang Yuan.

He is the greatest mastermind behind everything.”

“I have woken up now!”

“Our Fang clan wanted to destroy the anti-Fang alliance, it was not something Heavenly Court

wanted to see, but Fang Yuan did not like that either.”

“If our Fang clan obtains victory, we will no longer attack the other super forces.”

“And in this current situation, we need to urgently move and sell our resource points to Fang

Yuan in exchange for Immortal Gu and also to revive Gu Immortals.”

“Now, what will we do?”

“Without resource points and the ability to provide for ourselves, we can only rely on Fang Yuan

increasingly!”

“We can only invade other super forces’ resource points and exchange them to Fang Yuan for

Immortal Gu and other cultivation resources.”

“Our Fang clan has become his vanguard, we are his bandits to loot Western Desert.”

“And this Gu Yue Fang Yuan is still staying in Eastern Sea, he is the high and mighty Great

Love Immortal Venerable!”

“He will declare to everyone that he is not interfering in Western Desert’s affairs. All of the vile

reputation will be shouldered by my Fang clan alone. He, Gu Yue Fang Yuan, has a clean

reputation!”

“Hehehe... hahaha...”

“What Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance? What Great Love Immortal Venerable?”

Fang Di Chang raised his head up and laughed in a pitiful tone of mockery.

His eyes were reddened, his hair was messy, the light of tears flickered in his eyes.

“First supreme elder Fang Gong, think about it, don’t you feel that Wan clan’s first supreme

elder died too peculiarly?”

“With his death, our Fang clan only has one route to take.”

“This is Fang Yuan, he is covered in a false human skin, but he is a vile beast that devours

everyone with no hesitation.”

“I hate him, I am truly hateful.”

Fang Di Chang gritted his teeth.

“I hate that my Fang clan got too involved with Fang Yuan.”

“I hate those Eastern Sea super forces who are too weak and meek, they let Fang Yuan rule

over them so easily!”

“However, the one I hate most is myself!”

“To think that I am a wisdom path Gu Immortal, not only did I fail to expose Fang Yuan’s

schemes, I caused our entire clan to become his pawns!”

“We were manipulated and toyed around by him!”

“I am the greatest sinner of Fang clan...”

Saying so, Fang Di Chang knelt on the ground, his head was lowered to the ground as he

punched the soil below him and cried out loud.

This proud wisdom path Gu Immortal had not lost his composure for over a hundred years, he

was crying so pitifully now.

Fang Gong sighed as he sat down beside Fang Di Chang.

“How could I have not been suspicious about the peculiar death of Wan clan’s first supreme

elder?”

“But even if this is Fang Yuan’s scheme, what can we do?”

“Do we have evidence?”

“Hehe.” Fang Gong smiled in a weak and powerless way: ”Even if we have evidence, what can

we do to Heaven Refining Demon Venerable?”

Fang Gong placed his arm on Fang Di Chang’s shoulder: ”Don’t lose your cool, second

supreme elder, you are the strategist of Fang clan. If the other Fang clan Gu Immortals see this,

what will they think? What will happen to Fang clan’s morale?”

Fang Di Chang gritted his teeth and stopped crying.

He sat upright and moved shoulder to shoulder with Fang Gong.

Fang Gong continued to speak: ”I feel hatred too, I hate Heavenly Court, I hate Wan clan, I hate

Fang Yuan, and I hate you. But similarly, I hate myself the most!”

“As the first supreme elder of Fang clan, I actually lost to Wan Gu Chou’s killer move. I am like a

dog that ran away pitifully, I cannot do anything.”

“My fist is so weak, my body is as fragile as glass.”

“Fang Di Chang, you are not the first supreme elder, I am!”

“Who is to blame for Fang clan’s current situation?”

“Nobody has committed a greater mistake than me!”

“If death can atone for my sins, I will immediately suicide in front of the anti-Fang alliance. But

that will not happen! We know the truth behind the righteous path, if Fang clan loses the only

rank eight like me, those people will be even more ruthless.”

“I need to live, I need to raise my fist and show a firm expression, I need to live with my chest

held high!”

“That is how I can help Fang clan, I want to make compensations for my sins.”

“I want to atone for my sins through actions!”

“I don’t want to be the greatest sinner of our clan, I don’t want our clan to end by my leadership!”

“Do you understand this? Fang Di Chang!”

Fang Gong screamed.

Fang Di Chang gritted his teeth, he started at Fang Gong: ”Of course I understand!!”

Fang Gong stood up and looked at tassel desert as well as the sky, he said: ”Today’s tassel

desert is like the moving rock crevice of back then. We must learn from the first generation Fang

clan immortal ancestor and face our difficulties head on.”

“What is our homeland?”

“It is not these resource points, but ourselves.”

“Where there’s life, there’s hope.”

“You are right.” Fang Di Chang also stood up as he showed a determined expression: ”Our

Fang clan still has hope!”

Immemorial two heavens.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s huge mountain-like body charged towards two Heavenly

Court Gu Immortals, Jun Shen Guang and Che Wei.

As qi tides blew, a formless pressure enveloped Jun Shen Guang and Che Wei.

“Oh no, why did he come to us?” Jun Shen Guang frowned tightly.

Che Wei sighed: ”Even if Spectral Soul Demon Venerable is not sane now, we are not his

match. Retreat!”

“But these stars were lured here after so much hard work, and this heavenly veil was given to us

by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.” Jun Shen Guang gritted his teeth, in the end, he also

chose to retreat.

The three headed thousand armed Spectral Soul Demon Venerable growled and raised

hundreds of thick black arms that were the size of ancient trees, he slashed at the space before

him.

With continuous cracking sounds, the empty space in the sky was torn apart, as if a huge veil

was shredded into pieces.

And within the veil, there were countless huge stars.

Bam bam bam...

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable charged into the field of stars, along the way, all of the stars

that touched his huge body were destroyed, he even used his arms to crushed many of the

stars he saw.

The two Heavenly Court Gu Immortals saw that their hard work was being destroyed, they felt

extremely angry.

But thankfully, stars scattered and flew away, the senseless Spectral Soul Demon Venerable

only managed to destroy a small portion of them.

Che Wei and Jun Shen Guang discussed among themselves, they decided to keep the

heavenly veil and bring all of the remaining stars to Central Continent.

After all, this was a mission handed out by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

“This is a heavenly veil?” Shen Shang suddenly appeared.

Che Wei’s and Jun Shen Guang’s expressions sank at once, they became very alert. Shen

Shang displayed pseudo venerable battle strength in Crazed Demon Cave, he was a huge

enemy to these two.

Shen Shang also collected some of the heavenly veil, he looked at Spectral Soul Demon

Venerable who was causing destruction to the stars and smiled at the two Heavenly Court

immortals: ”Can you tell me what Heavenly Court is collecting these stars for?”

Che Wei’s and Jun Shen Guang’s expressions became grim.

Shen Shang continued: ”So be it if you don’t tell me. Since you are using the heavenly veil to

collect the stars, you must be trying to act secretly, you don’t want to be disturbed.”

“In that case, I will take the heavenly veil and expose your actions to the public.”

Che Wei snorted coldly: ”Shen Shang, don’t go overboard. Fang clan’s outcome is also the

outcome of all those super forces who joined Fang Yuan! Your Shen clan’s good days are

coming to an end.”

Shen Shang squinted: ”I won’t trouble you with my Shen clan’s affairs. But what I do know is

that your good times are ending now!”

“Retreat!” Jun Shen Guang spoke while Che Wei acknowledged the decision.

Shen Shang chased and forced these Heavenly Court immortals to retreat before he returned

and stored the collected heavenly veil.

“The heavenly veil is an extremely precious heaven path immortal material, it is best if I

contribute this to Alliance Leader Fang Yuan!”

Chapter 2265: Grotto-Heaven’s Calamity

Hundreds of stars shot down at Profound Literature grotto-heaven.

Old Immortal Hua Yu’s subordinates had already heard the news, they waited in vigilance.

“They’re back!”

“Quickly activate the immortal formation!!”

Bam bam bam...

The stars landed on the immortal formation and erupted with immense power.

Profound light flashed as the stars broke into countless fragments.

The immortal formation suffered the heavy impact, the Gu Immortals coughed out blood from

injuries.

A moment later, the tattered immortal formation still remained, while several stars continued to

attack.

“Retreat.” Old Immortal Hua Yu ordered.

“Lord?!”

“But the grotto-heaven is right behind us.”

“If anything happens...”

“I refuse to retreat! Even if I have to give up my life, I will defend our home!”

Even though the Gu Immortals were currently weakened, their morale was very high.

Profound Literature grotto-heaven was originally condensed into a small dot in empty space, no

matter how the stars flew outside, it was unaffected. But with the fusion of two heavens, an

intense change occurred.

All of the two heavens’ grotto-heavens that were hidden were forced to reveal themselves.

Currently, behind the half-broken immortal formation was Profound Literature grotto-heaven’s

entrance.

Even though the entrance was shut, it was exposed and could not be hidden.

Old Immortal Hua Yu shouted: ”I have my ways, don’t hesitate, otherwise, you will lose your

lives in vain!”

The immortals went silent, they quickly dismantled the immortal formation and escaped into

Profound Literature grotto-heaven.

They all believed in Old Immortal Hua Yu.

“Here they come.” Old Immortal Hua Yu was alone as he watched the approaching stars, his

expression was grim.

Immortal killer move — Cold Words!

Immortal killer move — Shattered Words!

The first move created frost that slowed down the stars. The second move slashed at the stars

and shattered them into pieces.

However, large star fragments still continued to fly towards him with the remaining force.

“I’ll risk it!” Old Immortal Hua Yu shouted loudly, he disregarded his own life and used methods

without stopping, eventually blocking all of the star fragments.

Guh.

He spat out a mouthful of blood, his expression was pale and wounds were all over his body,

shining in star path light.

With the fusion of two heavens, the flying trajectory of the stars was affected by the Heavenly

Dao and became chaotic, they were also amplified and became more powerful.

Even the rank eight Old Immortal Hua Yu had great difficulty in blocking them.

Old Immortal Hua Yu was about to return when he suddenly turned around, seeing another

group of stars flying towards him.

If these stars really hit, Profound Literature grotto-heaven would not be able to take the impact!

His pupils contracted rapidly and his expression froze, but soon, he relaxed.

He was resolved for this.

Even if he had to sacrifice his life, he had to block them!

But at this time, Jun Shen Guang suddenly appeared.

Heavenly veil!

He flew while tossing with his hands, he quickly arrived in front of the stars and set up the

heavenly veil.

Once the stars landed on the heavenly veil, it started shaking intensely, clear ripples could be

seen on it.

“Heavenly Court’s Gu Immortal, Jun Shen Guang!” Old Immortal Hua Yu’s expression froze for

a second.

“Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance’s Old Immortal Hua Yu!” Jun Shen Guang was slightly

stunned and soon felt worried. It was currently the crucial period, if Old Immortal Hua Yu took

action, the heavenly veil would get destroyed again.

But Jun Shen Guang’s worries did not end up happening.

After fifteen minutes passed, Old Immortal Hua Yu still watched from the side and did not act.

Jun Shen Guang collected the heavenly veil and collected all of the stars successfully.

Finally, Jun Shen Guang cast a deep gaze at Old Immortal Hua Yu, before dragging the huge

heavenly veil bag and leaving with the stars.

Old Immortal Hua Yu had a complex expression as he opened the immortal aperture’s entrance

and entered the grotto-heaven.

He was actually saved by Heavenly Court.

Throughout the entire Profound Literature grotto-heaven, calamities struck everywhere, there

were earthquakes and floods, volcanic eruptions caused huge areas of thick smoke in the sky,

and acid rain had also been pouring for more than ten days.

“With the fusion of two heavens, the Heavenly Dao is stirred. Heaven’s will is chaotic, and all of

our grotto-heavens that are situated on the heaven vein node are suffering.”

“Lifeforms have perished, living beings are anguished!”

“Sigh, I am guilty...”

Old Immortal Hua Yu sighed deeply, he was filled with guilt, helplessness, angry, sadness, and

other complex emotions.

The Gu Immortals of the two heavens’ grotto-heavens had deep feelings for their own

grotto-heaven world. This was different from the Gu Immortals of the five regions.

Gu Immortals of the two heavens’ grotto-heavens were ostracized by the five regions, they had

to survive in this dangerous place.

Most of them were secluded cultivators, their grotto-heavens were the final and most important

homeland where they could experience peace and comfort.

Among these grotto-heavens, Profound Literature grotto-heaven established a dynasty ruled by

a single Gu Immortal force, it had deep literary development and the citizens saw this homeland

as the most precious thing.

The immortals quickly came to greet Old Immortal Hua Yu.

“This was too dangerous. We should get help from the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance

again!”

“With the fusion of two heavens, the environment has gotten incredibly dangerous. Those

Eastern Sea Gu Immortals live in peace and tranquility, why would they come here and do such

a risky thing?”

“Sigh, it is possible to get their help. But the price to pay is too high.”

“The entire Imperial Court’s foundation is running dry!”

“Skeleton grotto-heaven and others are also asking for help without caring about expenses. This

creates a negative effect where Eastern Sea’s Gu Immortals demand higher prices in response.

Damn it!”

“Sigh, Lord Alliance Leader is not even taking control of this!”

“Great Love Immortal Venerable is busy refining dao marks or making arrangements in Western

Desert. Why would he care about the affairs of our small Profound Literature grotto-heaven?”

“In any case, our Profound Literature grotto-heaven will get annexed by him eventually!”

Old Immortal Hua Yu’s expression turned solemn as he scolded: ”Everyone, shut up, don’t talk

about Lord Alliance Leader in such a manner!”

Even though he said that, Old Immortal Hua Yu had a thought flash in his mind, he recalled the

deep gaze that Jun Shen Guang showed earlier.

Longevity Heaven.

Golden light rippled constantly in waves.

“Hold on, hold on!” Several Gu Immortals among the Eight Extremities were controlling Calamity

Luck Altar as they tried to stabilize the situation.

The entire Longevity Heaven was shaking intensely.

The earth shook.

Not just Calamity Luck Altar, Bing Sai Chuan was also controlling Luck Suppression Heavenly

Palace.

However, both luck path Immortal Gu Houses were only barely able to keep the current situation

stable.

Boom.

With a loud sound, the ground cracked and also broke the entire Longevity Heaven into two.

Swoosh swoosh.

Waves surged from below, scarlet red light soared up into the sky.

A vast sea of blood appeared in front of the immortals.

“Longevity Heaven has such a huge Blood Sea?” Bing Sai Chuan and the rest were shaken.

Heavenly Court.

The bright and peaceful atmosphere was no more.

Qin Ding Ling, Red Heart Traveler, Nine Spiritual Fairy, Prince Feng Xian, and other members

were moving around everywhere.

Shabi Ninety-five, Ruan Dan, and even Qing Chou were mobilized to stabilize this situation.

Both the sky and earth were forming terrifying cracks.

The grand palaces had already been dismantled by Heavenly Court’s Gu Immortals, they were

condensed into ten or more rank six, seven, and eight Immortal Gu Houses.

No matter what the situation was, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not pay any

attention to it, she focused entirely on refining Heavenly Court’s wisdom path dao marks.

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

Fang Yuan’s soul was lying in the pool water, feeling extremely relaxed.

The water was hot and steam was coming out of it, forming a region of white smoke.

Once in a while, there would be ripples in the water that splattered on Fang Yuan’s soul.

Fang Yuan’s soul originally had hundreds of arms and two heads, after the cleansing of the pool

water, hundreds of arms had vanished, he also returned to having one head.

This was not an ordinary pool, it was Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool!

After Fang Yuan raised advance refinement Immortal Gu to rank nine, he started modifying Four

Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool. Some time ago, he started to refine his soul in

it.

Because the rank nine advance refinement Immortal Gu was added, Four Elements Square

Regret Blood Refinement Pool became a genuine rank nine Immortal Gu House.

This Immortal Gu House still had the same four cores, Advance Refinement, Water Refinement,

Regret, and Blood Asset.

Advance Refinement was rank nine, the other three were rank eight.

Among which, blood asset Immortal Gu had reached its limit, it could not be raised to rank nine.

Heavenly Court’s suppression of blood path’s development was showing great effect here.

Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool was created before the battle in Crazed

Demon Cave, after advance refinement Immortal Gu became rank nine, Fang Yuan could

modify it now that he was a refinement path supreme grandmaster.

Right now, Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool had undoubtedly gained a

huge boost in power in terms of refining Gu!

Fang Yuan’s soul used Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool to cleanse itself,

the effect was incredible.

The drawback of cultivating soul path was gradually weakening.

Fang Yuan’s soul path cultivation mainly relied on Spectral Soul’s soul path true inheritance.

This true inheritance had a huge drawback, it was completely exposed now!

Humans could reach hundred million man soul at most, that was their racial limit.

But after Red Lotus Demon Venerable damaged fate Gu, and with Spectral Soul Demon

Venerable’s innovation, he broke the limit of the human soul and created a qualitative change,

he allowed hundred million man soul to reach desolate soul. After that, it could continue to grow

to ten desolate soul, hundred desolate soul... all the way to hundred million desolate soul.

Hundred million desolate soul was the end point of Spectral Soul’s true inheritance, it could

create the Three Headed Thousand Arms Demon Soul which possessed quasi-rank nine battle

strength. The soul could directly resist calamities and tribulations, defy the heavens and stomp

the earth, slaughter deities and ghosts, and shock the world with unmatched might!

This was the peak of soul cultivation, it was the upper limit that this world could allow.

But Fang Yuan gradually found that this cultivation method had a huge drawback, because

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable overly pursued strength, many threats were left behind.

A human soul was a human soul, after becoming a desolate soul, the pure human nature would

gain beast nature, or more accurately speaking, heaven nature!

Hundred million desolate soul was truly terrifying, but the proportion of human nature also

became very low, the bestial traits took over most of its nature.

At this current moment, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable lost his senses and got controlled by

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable. Afterwards, he roamed the two heavens and acted

according to his beast nature, this was the most obvious flaw!

Fang Yuan had some estimations towards Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s current condition.

Some time ago, Shen Shang contributed his human path cultivation results, Fang Yuan

compared the two and confirmed the drawback of soul path cultivation.

“In the past, human path was not developed, thus, the limit of a human was hundred million man

soul. Spectral Soul Demon Venerable had to break through it forcefully, but truthfully, he had

gone in the wrong direction.”

“Of course, there are many reasons for this.”

“Back then, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable wanted to create killing path, he devoured the

black heaven heavenly spirit but failed to succeed, causing him to create soul path instead.

There is a huge secret behind this, the more I think about this, the scarier it is!”

Chapter 2266: Star Constellation’s Arrangement

Intense winds and storms filled Heavenly Court.

The silvery white sky turned dark at this moment.

Within the intense winds, more than ten Immortal Gu Houses were moving around the place, all

of Heavenly Court’s members were doing their best to salvage the situation.

“The northeast corner has large areas of black smoke, it can corrode the ground and create

rotten soil!”

“The immortal graveyard needs to be protected.”

“Branded Name Palace is severely damaged, please send reinforcements!”

“Can anyone help me, I can’t repair this huge crack in time!!”

The Gu Immortals conversed among each other, this situation had been going on for tens of

days, it was getting more dangerous as time passed.

Heavenly Court was filled with danger, and most importantly, its foundation was too immense, it

was the number one heaven vein node in the world. During the fusion of the two heavens,

Heavenly Court suffered the greatest impact.

Originally, Heavenly Court had a tight defense, but after two invasions, the defensive methods

left by Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable and others had either been destroyed or greatly

weakened, they were useless in this situation.

Crack.

Lightning flashed and bolted across half of Heavenly Court.

Eventually, Five Deity Hall blocked it but suffered huge damage in doing it, it fell to the ground,

creating a huge pit that emitted dense smoke.

This situation was caused by Heavenly Court’s immense foundation.

Even the rank eight Five Deity Hall could barely block such power.

Rain and wind continued unceasingly.

Under such a turbulent situation, in Central Great Hall, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable

opened her eyes slowly.

Her star pupils were clear and bright, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable looked through

Central Great Hall and observed the entire situation of Heavenly Court in one glance.

...

“Little Xing, from today onwards, this will be your home.” Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable

brought back the child Xing Su and said to her.

“Where is this?”

“Heavenly Court.” Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable said with deep emotions.

“Heavenly Court...” Xing Su muttered this foreign phrase.

“You can think of it as your home.” Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable patted Little Xing Su’s

head.

“Home?” Xing Su’s eyes brightened.

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable looked far and wide, across the five regions, he seemed to

be able to look into the future: ”Of course, this is your home, this will also be home to all of

humanity!”

...

Deep memories surfaced in Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s mind before fading away

quickly.

“Since when has Heavenly Court been in such a pitiful state?”

“Master.”

“This is our home, I will defend it till the end. After that...”

“I will wait for your return!”

At the next moment, purple light burst out of Central Great Hall and spread to every corner of

Heavenly Court.

“This is?!”

“Star Constellation Immortal Venerable made her move?”

“We are too incapable, we are a burden to Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable!”

“No, how can Star Constellation Immortal Venerable act unwisely? It is obvious that she has

already refined all of Heavenly Court’s wisdom path dao marks.”

Once Star Constellation Immortal Venerable took action, the situation immediately changed.

Under the rays of purple light, the raging wind and rain vanished, the intense lightning bolts

were dispersed, the crack of heaven and earth mended quickly.

The Heavenly Court Gu Immortals were all shaken internally.

This was the might of a Dao Lord!

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable refined all of the wisdom path dao marks in Heavenly

Court, her strength exceeded Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Spectral Soul Demon

Venerable completely in this domain.

Right now, even if Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Fang Yuan were to collaborate to attack

Heavenly Court, they would not be able to do anything to Star Constellation Immortal Venerable!

“Go! Let’s go meet Lady Star Constellation.”

Some Immortal Gu Houses landed while some stayed in the air, Gu Immortals streamed out and

moved towards Central Great Hall.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable activated her investigative method.

This investigation had a completely different effect from before.

Using the amplification of Heavenly Court’s countless wisdom path dao marks, the investigative

killer move’s power surged!

“The situation is still within my expectations. Both venerables are still refining natural dao marks,

Fang Yuan has little immortal essence and has the slowest progress. Giant Sun Immortal

Venerable has the most results, even exceeding me.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable quickly stopped her investigative method.

She needed to conserve immortal essence now.

It was time for Heavenly Court’s immortals to report the various situations.

Due to the fusion of both heavens, Heavenly Court was greatly affected and had huge losses.

“Back then, Profound Literature grotto-heaven faced the problem of crashing stars, thus, Old

Immortal Hua Yu did not attack me, I successfully brought back those stars to Central

Continent.”

Jun Shen Guang said an interesting event that made Star Constellation Immortal Venerable

develop a thought.

Human, Imperial Court, poetry, dynasty, Fang Yuan, mermaid immortals, the sovereign immortal

aperture...

All sorts of information related to Old Immortal Hua Yu and Profound Literature grotto-heaven

flashed past Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s mind.

With the help of Heavenly Court’s wisdom path dao marks, Star Constellation Immortal

Venerable only expended several hundred thoughts and a meager amount of immortal essence

to deduce the result.

“We can make this Profound Literature grotto-heaven betray his alliance!”

Old Immortal Hua Yu had deep attachment to the grotto-heaven, Star Constellation Immortal

Venerable understood why.

Interrupting Jun Shen Guang was a huge merit but Old Immortal Hua Yu did not do it. This

meant that in his heart, Profound Literature grotto-heaven was more important than his status in

the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance.

And most importantly, Old Immortal Hua Yu had once opposed Fang Yuan and the variant

human alliance, that was the reason why he joined the Righteous Qi Alliance.

But afterwards, Fang Yuan declared himself as Great Love, Eastern Sea’s super forces were

too meek and immediately joined him, Profound Literature grotto-heaven was forced to follow.

Why did Fang Yuan not annex all these grotto-heavens?

The reason was simple.

The sovereign immortal aperture was not stable, it was unable to expand anymore now!

Non-conflicting dao marks were a double-edged sword.

Long before the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had

already deduced this huge threat of Fang Yuan’s.

Fang Yuan took in many resource points and focused on earth path resource points at first, he

was likely constructing an earth path dao vein to stabilize the sovereign immortal aperture.

During the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, Fang Yuan lost many Gu Immortal subordinates.

Afterwards, he took the risk and took in six mermaid immortals, it showed that he was lacking

manpower, the sovereign immortal aperture was in a desperate state.

Thus, Fang Yuan could not annex these grotto-heavens.

“He is only skilled at defending against wisdom path deductions, Western Desert’s Fang clan’s

situation is also taking a lot of his energy. The lack of refinement path development is his

greatest worry, he cannot bother with Profound Literature grotto-heaven’s matter.”

Even though Fang Yuan was strong, he had become a venerable through refinement path, not

wisdom path.

His wisdom path attainment was not amazing in Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s view.

In the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, the reason why Fang Yuan succeeded was because Star

Constellation Immortal Venerable had focused on reviving, she did her best to try to get Crazed

Demon Cave’s eternal life research results, she also had to guard against Giant Sun Immortal

Venerable, it gave Fang Yuan the chance to succeed.

Wisdom path was not skilled at solving impromptu situations, Star Constellation Immortal

Venerable had too little time to prepare back then.

But as time passed, her wisdom path advantage continued to accumulate.

Ignoring other matters, just the fact that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable refined Heavenly

Court’s wisdom path dao marks meant that she already had an impregnable position in this

contest of three venerables!

“Even if Fang Yuan is not skilled in wisdom path, his wisdom path methods are beyond the

ordinary rank eight Gu Immortal. But Profound Literature grotto-heaven’s issue has just

surfaced, Old Immortal Hua Yu will not report the matter. This is our opportunity.”

“If we do not use this chance well and stall for too long, Fang Yuan will notice it.”

Thinking of this, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable immediately gave orders to send Jun

Shen Guang and Qin Ding Ling to Profound Literature grotto-heaven secretly in an attempt to

persuade Old Immortal Hua Yu.

“If we can recruit Profound Literature grotto-heaven, can we also do the same to Western

Desert’s Fang clan?” Wan Zi Hong’s will was present, she suggested this.

Duke Tong chuckled and showed an expression of disdain.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable shook her head and asked Wan Zi Hong’s will instead:

“Why do you think Wan clan did not choose to join Fang Yuan back then? They knew about

Fang clan and Fang Yuan’s relationship, why did Western Desert’s super forces still agree to

create the anti-Fang alliance before our Heavenly Court showed up?”

Wan Zi Hong’s will shook slightly, she seemed to realize something.

With the fusion of two heavens and contest of three venerables, the five regions’ political

situation was completely chaotic, the factors involved were not just strength or benefits, there

was also the people’s will.

The heart of the people was a very intricate thing, it was hard to assess at times, but also

extremely easy to decipher at times.

Back then, Heavenly Court was created and received resounding support from everyone, the

greatest reason was the people’s will.

Righteous path and demonic path, if one only classified them according to fixed criteria set by

the major players, it would be too shallow.

Heavenly Court could recruit otherworldly demons, they could recruit demonic path Gu

Immortals like Wan Zi Hong, this was because they could be said to be upholding justice, they

were giving demons a second chance to turn over a new leaf, this was their great benevolence.

But if Heavenly Court recruited Fang clan, they would lose everyone’s support.

Why did Heavenly Court support Wan clan, what was the reason? All along, what was the motto

of Heavenly Court? What stance did they take?

If they recruited Fang clan which had fallen into the demonic path entirely, then what difference

would Heavenly Court have when compared to those who only pursued benefits?

In these situations, if Heavenly Court wavered in their stance and went for petty gains, their

reputation would take the biggest hit. In fact, even the ten great ancient sects of Central

Continent would start having doubts.

Especially at this sensitive juncture, Fang clan was supported by Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan plotted secretly and made Fang clan attack Wan clan, it was because he knew that

his reputation and popularity would not be accepted easily just because he declared himself as

Great Love.

Eastern Sea’s super forces joined him merely out of fear.

Wu Yong made transactions with Fang Yuan for benefits. Not long after, Wu Yong also made

transactions with Heavenly Court.

If Heavenly Court did this, Fang Yuan might become overjoyed.

And this suggestion could only be brought up by someone like Wan Zi Hong, she was a former

demonic path member after all, other Heavenly Court members had not mentioned it.

Was it because they could not?

Of course not!

“The righteous path has the advantage in Western Desert’s conflict. The only worry is if Fang

clan goes all-in and sell all their resource points to Fang Yuan.” Star Constellation Immortal

Venerable had a thought.

She was the number one person in wisdom path, she had long expected such a situation, thus,

when she sent the members, she chose Zhou Xiong Xin.

Zhou Xiong Xin was an information path Gu Immortal, he was skilled at finding clues.

Once Fang clan abandoned everything and left, Zhou Xiong Xin would collect the relevant

information and let Star Constellation Immortal Venerable make deductions on them.

They had the duty of eradicating evil forces.

Fang clan had to be exterminated!

After Star Constellation Immortal Venerable refined all of Heavenly Court’s wisdom path dao

marks, she had to rest and accumulate immortal essence now before she could start her next

move.

“For the short period ahead, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s threat is even greater than Giant

Sun Immortal Venerable and Heaven Refining Demon Venerable.”

“It is time to send people to search for Fairy Zi Wei.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable arranged everything in meticulous and orderly fashion.

Chapter 2267: Little Du’s Revival

Eastern Sea.

Fang Yuan lightly let out a breath of air.

“This time, I succeeded in deceiving her again.”

Just earlier, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable used her investigative killer move to check

on Fang Yuan.

Obscured heavenly secret activated again and helped him to conceal the truth.

Heaven path...

So it be if Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not understand heaven path. But even Star

Constellation Immortal Venerable was deceived time and again, she had once become one with

the Dao, she was able to influence and alter heaven’s will.

“Even she was deceived by me, is it because of heaven path’s profundity, or because her

revival had flaws in it, in terms of heaven path, she did not regain her former life’s abilities?”

“Earlier, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s investigative method had unprecedented

power. It is very likely that she has already refined all of Heavenly Court’s wisdom path dao

marks.”

Fang Yuan was only making a guess, he did not use any investigative method now.

Looking into the sovereign immortal aperture.

Three earth path dao veins had been constructed already.

A wind path dao vein and a fire path dao vein were also almost completed too, he was just a

few more away from completing the first dao vein ring.

He had undergone countless Immortal Gu transactions in treasure yellow heaven to exchange

for resource points. There was also Fang clan’s contribution that led to such huge progress.

Western Desert’s fire path, earth path, and wind path dao marks were outstanding, these three

paths had the most resource points there.

Fang clan was forced into desperation, they had to cut their foundation to fight for survival.

The sovereign immortal aperture gained a lot, but even then, the entire immortal aperture was

still in a precarious situation.

Currently, Fang Yuan had already reduced the purchasing of earth path resource points, he

started to buy other paths’ resource points.

According to his deductions, he had to establish the various paths’ dao veins first and construct

the first ring. After that, there would be an immediate effect on the sovereign immortal aperture’s

stability.

“The sovereign immortal aperture is unstable and strange situations are occurring frequently.

The Gu Immortals within the immortal aperture are already working at their limit. Even the six

mermaid immortals that came into the immortal aperture are not enough anymore.”

During this period of time, many Gu Immortals had liver explosions.

Thankfully, Fang Yuan constructed a healing hall, otherwise, if these Gu Immortals had to

recuperate for a long time, the sovereign immortal aperture would fall apart instantly. In the end,

Fang Yuan would need to take action himself to suppress the turmoil.

“I need to bring in more manpower.”

Venerables were undoubtedly invincible, but with the contest of three venerables, the situation

became rather complex.

According to the current situation, the main priority of the three venerables was to refine natural

dao marks.

But the world itself had a vast number of natural dao marks, it would take a long time for the

three venerables to refine them all.

Currently, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was making the fastest progress, but he was still

refining Northern Plains’ dao marks.

The three venerables were not at the stage of having a decisive battle yet.

Because Longevity Heaven and Heavenly Court were refined, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable

and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had their own firm base. Even if the other venerables

collaborated, they could not overwhelm the target at their base camp.

And without sufficient advantage, it was unwise to have a battle now.

The venerables would not do that.

Thus, for the following period of time, the venerables would need other Gu Immortals to help

them and work for them.

In this situation, normal Gu Immortals were very useful to the venerables.

This value displayed its worth during their deadlock.

Even if Fang Yuan was a refinement path venerable, being capable of easily refining most rank

eight and below Immortal Gu and also creating countless Immortal Gu Houses, this could not

replace the use of Gu Immortals.

The earlier discussion on Fang clan showed this clearly.

What decided the outcome were not the Immortal Gu Houses but Fang Gong and Wan Gu

Chou.

For Gu Immortal experts, once the mechanics of the Immortal Gu House were deciphered, they

would be easy to target and deal with.

Be it Fang clan’s roof tile breaker or Zuo Qiu clan’s state of disunity, they were counters to

Immortal Gu Houses.

Thus, the people were most important.

Gu are the essence of heaven and earth, man is the spirit of all living beings.

Having more Immortal Gu was a good thing, but the human element was on par with the Gu.

Fang Yuan needed a large number of Gu Immortal subordinates.

One one hand, in a deadlock of venerables, he needed enough henchman, it would lead to

greater convenience.

Especially when he was refining natural dao marks and could not leave.

On the other hand, Fang Yuan’s sovereign immortal aperture often needed a large number of

Gu Immortals to suppress the strange phenomena that occurred frequently.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable also needed Gu

Immortals.

On one hand, when the venerables were in a deadlock, they could settle matters for them. For

example, when Star Constellation Immortal Venerable refined Heavenly Court’s dao marks, Jun

Shen Guang went to the two heavens to collect stars.

On the other hand, Longevity Heaven and Heavenly Court were also trying to nurture their

second venerable.

After the destruction of fate, it was possible to create new venerables. As for Giant Sun

Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, because of their conflicting dao

marks, they could not become the venerable of a second path themselves.

But how could they recruit Gu Immortals?

The most convenient source were the Gu Immortals of the five regions.

But this contained huge hidden threats.

On one hand, these Gu Immortals could be the spies of another venerable, the fact that Fang

Yuan brought in six mermaid immortals was already a huge risk in itself.

If he had to bring in Gu Immortals of the five regions, Fang Yuan was more inclined to bring in

variant humans.

After all, variant humans were on the opposite side of Heavenly Court and Longevity Heaven.

Other than bringing in more Gu Immortals, Fang Yuan’s other main method was immortal

ascension.

He could nurture Gu Immortals inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

But this had a merit and demerit.

The merit was that the Gu Immortal’s loyalty was assured.

The demerit was that the time needed to nurture Gu Immortals was very long. And as the saying

went, water in the distance could not quench thirst.

But Fang Yuan had an advantage over the other venerables, his sovereign immortal aperture

did not conflict with time path, so changing the time flow was very easy. Right now, the

sovereign immortal aperture definitely had the fastest time flow among the venerables.

In terms of nurturing Gu Immortals, Fang Yuan already had many good choices.

He had specially revived some of the Gu Immortals that died in Crazed Demon Cave as

mortals.

But now that the two heavens were fusing, heaven’s will was chaotic and Gu Immortals were

unable to get natural inspiration when they first ascend at this time.

This would not do!

Fang Yuan knew his own limitations. His wisdom path deductions could not match Star

Constellation Immortal Venerable, they were barely on par with Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Thus, Fang Yuan had to make full use of natural inspiration.

If he missed these opportunities, his killer move deduction and modification would be far slower

than the other two venerables.

If he could not bring in Gu Immortals or nurture them himself, what could he do?

Fang Yuan quickly thought of human path.

Fang Yuan’s clone was still trapped in Divine Emperor City, but through Shen Shang, he

transferred his human path cultivation results to Fang Yuan’s main body.

Together with Fang Yuan’s transaction with Shen Shang, he also gained a portion of the latter’s

human path cultivation results.

Fang Yuan obtained the incomplete Immortal Gu recipes of beggar Gu and merchant Gu.

If he had the complete Immortal Gu recipes, Fang Yuan would be able to refine merchant

Immortal Gu and beggar Immortal Gu. After activating them, he would gain manpower, there

would be no threat of betrayal as well.

But Fang Yuan lacked human path attainment level, while human path Immortal Gu recipes

were hard to deduce.

Were there natural human path Immortal Gu in the wild?

According to Fang Yuan’s estimation, the answer was no.

Such Immortal Gu recipes needed to be created by humans!

After deep consideration, Fang Yuan did not attempt to deduce the human path Immortal Gu

recipes, they would waste too much of his time and effort.

Thus, Fang Yuan held anticipation towards Central Continent’s human path development as

well.

Ignoring other matters, just his soul path cultivation needed the support of human path.

Looking at refinement path, it was able to grow to such a prosperous state today because of

refinement path’s own development and also because it supported all other paths in their

development.

Human Sea rippled as huge waves appeared.

After the rise and fall of tides, two fallen Gu Immortals remained on the beach.

“Where, where is this place?”

“I clearly died on the battlefield already...”

Fang Dong Xi and Fang An Lei were confused as they stood up.

This situation made them puzzled and shocked.

But soon, Fang Yuan’s will descended and informed them of the situation.

“Lord Fang Yuan actually has such a shocking method to revive us!” Fang clan’s two Gu

Immortals were filled with joy and excitement upon revival.

Right at this time, there was a giant wave in Human Sea.

The size of this wave was far bigger than the one carrying the Fang clan members.

As the huge wave crashed onto the beach, it receded rapidly.

A young looking Gu Immortal rode the waves and landed ashore.

He gave off rank eight aura, stunning the two Fang clan Gu Immortals.

They immediately recognized that this newly revived Gu Immortal was one of Fang Yuan’s main

clones — Zhan Bu Du!

When bringing in Gu Immortals, nurturing Gu Immortals, and human path Immortal Gu were all

unfeasible at this moment, Fang Yuan chose to revive Gu Immortals.

Originally, the Gu Immortals only revived as mortals.

But now, they kept their cultivation level.

Fang clan’s two immortals were rank seven while Zhan Bu Du was rank eight.

To achieve this, Human Sea expended itself at an unprecedented level, it could only revive

three more rank eight Gu Immortals at this rate.

Where there are gains, there are losses.

Following this, Fang Yuan would need to collect more human qi to replenish Human Sea.

But there was no rush in this.

The thing that needed replenishment the most was Refinement Sea.

At this point, Fang Yuan’s Refinement Sea was almost dry already.

After the two Fang clan Gu Immortals left, Fang Yuan gave all the transformation path Immortal

Gu to Zhan Bu Du. This way, as long as he used the transformation path killer move, Zhan Bu

Du would gain pseudo venerable battle strength again.

Zhan Bu Du went to handle the strange phenomena while Fang Yuan’s main body expended

heaven path immortal materials to replenish obscured heavenly secret.

After that, he secretly unsealed the truthful floating ice.

Right now, Fang Yuan’s transformation path and rule path attainment levels rose.

But the greatest growth was still heaven path.

Fang Yuan could sense that his heaven path attainment level was reaching a point of qualitative

change.

Black and white heaven.

A huge transparent pillar slammed down and killed most of the soul beasts under it.

From the body of a desolate level soul beast, two Gu Immortals flew out.

One was a female immortal who had a graceful figure with hair that extended to her waist, she

was adorned in a beautiful purple robe. Her eyes were like deep pools, with a sense of sorrow

shrouding her face.

The other was a male immortal, he had an ordinary face, his eyes were dark and he emitted a

soul path aura.

They were Fairy Zi Wei and Ying Wu Xie.

“What heaven path immortal material is this? When it fell, the soul beasts could not move or

dodge it at all.” Ying Wu Xie asked curiously.

Fairy Zi Wei inspected it and explained: ”This is a heavenly pillar. Each heavenly pillar is a rank

nine heaven path immortal material! Back then, Central Continent’s Tian Ti Mountain could

connect to Heavenly Court because it had a heavenly pillar.”

“We lost the concealment of soul beasts but gained a rank nine immortal material. Is this good

or bad luck?” Ying Wu Xie sighed.

“What’s the point of sighing now, the urgent matter is to find Master Spectral Soul, your main

body!”

Chapter 2268: Awkwardness of the Anti-Fang Alliance

Western Desert, Fang clan’s headquarters.

“Open!” Mo Sha Ta shouted.

The killer move was activated, the immortal formation ahead was forced open.

The inside was completely empty.

Not a shred of resources were left, it was completely barren.

“This again!” Many Gu Immortals were angry and frustrated.

“Emptied, they emptied this as well...” Some muttered to themselves with expressions of

dejectedness.

“Fang clan is so ruthless!” Some Gu Immortals’ eyes were spewing fire, they gritted their teeth

angrily.

“Just Fang clan alone cannot have such manpower or methods, they must be backed by

Heaven Refining Demon Venerable!” Some of the Gu Immortals felt helpless.

This was Fang clan’s final resource point.

Like the earlier resource points, nothing was left to the anti-Fang alliance.

The Gu Immortals discussed among themselves, it was a rowdy scene.

This was too different from their expectations!

Fang clan had not only emptied the resource points, they also left the immortal formations

behind. These immortal formations were created using natural dao marks and immortal

materials.

When the anti-Fang alliance tried to break the immortal formation, they had to spend immortal

essence as well.

They wasted a bunch of immortal essence and ended up with no gains.

Looking at these deep pits or desolate land, the anti-Fang alliance’s members had grim

expressions.

Xiao Ye Hu did not even have the energy to get angry.

He was feeling regret.

“Had I known this, I would not have interfered in this stupid matter!”

Xiao Ye Hu’s own injuries had not healed yet, and most importantly, his Immortal Gu House

Chamber Pot was ruined.

It was not that he had no gains, but the things he got could not make up for his losses.

Wan Gu Chou looked at this scene and sighed internally, she was also feeling quite helpless.

In her first life, she had not seen any super force with no bottom line like this, it was truly a new

experience now.

She led the anti-Fang alliance and attacked, along the route, they did not meet any Fang clan

Gu Immortal, even though they broke many immortal formations, there were no resource points

inside, many of the immortal formations were even tampered with, if they could not open it

properly, it would explode!

This was too devious!

Many Gu Immortals suffered injuries because of this.

Even Fang clan’s headquarters had been relocated, it could not be found.

This was a public blessed land, but Fang clan actually had a method to relocate the immortal

aperture!

There was a saying on Earth, the monk can run away but the temple cannot, but now, Fang clan

directly brought the temple with them.

Even though Wan Gu Chou did not know this saying, her mood was just as horrible.

Even though they defeated Fang clan, Wan Gu Chou was not feeling happy at all, she was

instead filled with worries.

Fang clan vanished but they retained most of their battle strength.

Right now, it was Wan clan and the other super forces’ turn to feel worried. It was possible that

Fang clan would attack one of their resource points one day, and the chance of defending it was

low!

Fang clan did not have resource points left, they did not need to have Gu Immortals stationed to

guard them. If they attacked all at once, they could turn their passive situation into an active

one.

Wan Gu Chou looked at the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals.

In this situation, Heavenly Court and Wan clan were on the same side, their benefits were tied

together.

And in fact, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had issued orders long ago to exterminate

the whole of Fang clan.

Thus, after Zhou Xiong Xin sensed Wan Gu Chou’s gaze, he said without hesitation: ”Fang

clan’s actions are crippling their foundation, they have completely submitted to Heaven Refining

Demon Venerable. This means that Fang clan is the same as Fang Yuan, they are all demons,

they are threats to this world!”

“Don’t say these things to us, what are we going to do now?” The other Western Desert Gu

Immortals did not want to hear his talk.

Zhou Xiong Xin smiled: ”Our Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable predicted that this

would happen, she sent me here specially to find clues and information about Fang clan’s

traces. Once we find something, the anti-Fang alliance will be able to go all-out and eradicate

Fang clan.”

Wan Zi Hong, who was beside him, knew why Fang clan acted like this.

Some time ago, she had raised a suggestion to Star Constellation Immortal Venerable but the

plan to recruit Fang clan was rejected. At that point, Wan Zi Hong knew that Fang clan had no

way to surrender. Heavenly Court needed to intimidate everyone by showing a tough stance on

this matter, in this situation, even she would react the same.

The anti-Fang alliance was too dragged on and slow in its movements, it gave Fang clan and

Fang Yuan ample time to relocate their resources.

The best tactic of the anti-Fang alliance was to immediately attack Fang clan.

But they spent too much time discussing their internal affairs.

Negotiations took time after all, only after they finished distributing the supposed benefits did the

anti-Fang alliance move out.

But Wan Zi Hong understood them.

If they did not do this, the anti-Fang alliance would not be able to send Gu Immortals out or

come up with an appropriate tactic.

Risks and benefits were interlinked.

Only by confirming the benefit distribution would they be able to assign the clans to attack first

and which ones to stay at the back, the entire anti-Fang alliance would have motivation to do

this as well.

This alliance had been established for too short of a period, many of the Gu Immortals came

from super forces that were not willing to take anyone’s lead, there was nobody who could have

sufficient authority or strength to take charge.

Without temptation, this anti-Fang alliance would not have even been able to form.

Like earlier, Wan clan had to pay out of their own pockets to lure the various super forces to

send people and organize the anti-Fang alliance. After Wan Gu Chou was exposed, they used

Fang clan’s assets to tempt them.

Without any clear distribution of benefits, the anti-Fang alliance could not send anyone.

If battle broke out and Fang clan retaliated forcefully, the Gu Immortals would immediately

retreat and protect themselves, without clear benefits, nobody would take any risk.

But Fang clan was forced into a corner, they were united at this moment.

In this situation, Fang clan was like a clenched fist while the anti-Fang alliance was like a pile of

loose sand, it was likely that they would fail.

Thus, the process of negotiating benefits was a necessity.

“But my strength alone is not enough. Everyone, you should know about the threat that Fang

clan poses, we need to get rid of these demonic path scoundrels as soon as possible, I would

like you to send information path Gu Immortals to assist in pursuing them.” Zhou Xiong Xin said.

“Fang clan is in the demonic path, they are no longer a righteous path super force, it is

everyone’s duty to eradicate them!” Western Desert’s Gu Immortals nodded.

“But we returned with no gains from this, Wan clan and Heavenly Court have to give us a proper

answer!”

“Indeed, indeed, in this situation, we can’t leave empty handed, right?”

“If we leave without any gains, we will be too disappointed in you, Wan clan. If Fang clan attacks

again, how can anyone come to support the anti-Fang alliance?”

The Gu Immortals went into a commotion again.

Wan Gu Chou felt a huge headache!

She thought about it and secretly transmitted to Xiao Ye Hu.

“Friend from Xiao clan, don’t be anxious, my Wan clan will guarantee your benefits first.”

“Accordingly, the first ancestor of Fang clan was the sole Gu Immortal in their clan. Back then,

Fang clan occupied moving rock crevice and was the smallest super force in Western Desert.

“When the sand calamity appeared, Fang clan’s first ancestor was faced with a choice. He could

have created an immortal formation and sacrificed some Fang clan mortals to block the sand

calamity. But he chose to protect Fang clan’s people and left, giving up moving rock crevice in

the process. Such an extreme nature is truly rare, but it is not hard to understand why he did

that.”

“Friend, you have captured many Fang clansmen, even though they are just from branch

families, we can still make use of Fang clan’s nature.”

Xiao clan was the strongest super force besides Wan clan, Wan Gu Chou had to pacify them

first.

Strength was the most important thing in a negotiation.

After getting Wan Gu Chou’s assurance, Xiao Ye Hu’s expression eased up and he stopped

creating a scene.

Wan Gu Chou’s words could be trusted, this was the attitude of the righteous path after all.

Furthermore, even if Wan Gu Chou disregarded her reputation and refused to pay, what could

Xiao Ye Hu do?

“Sell! I will sell these Fang clansmen as slaves to humiliate Fang clan! We can also tamper with

these people and use them to find out the location of Fang clan’s immortals.”

Xiao Ye Hu gritted his teeth and firmed up his mind.

A moment later, in treasure yellow heaven.

“Where, where is this?” Wang Xiao Er gasped.

The surrounding people were screaming in fear too, there was a loud commotion around them.

These people were floating in treasure yellow heaven, a formless force was restrained them,

keeping them in place together.

Thus, Wang Xiao Er felt horrible, he was not stepping on ground and he was surrounded by

people, they were all squeezing around him.

“We were sold!”

“This is the legendary treasure yellow heaven.”

Some knowledgeable Gu Masters explained the truth.

Fang clan’s members had pale expressions.

This was the consequence of losing!

“Fang clan’s Gu Immortals, listen to this. You have betrayed the righteous path and fallen into

the demonic path, you are the shame of Western Desert’s righteous path. Even if you ran away,

you will still face our judgment!”

“These people are all members of Fang clan. They are innocent, but because of you, they are

now slaves, this is all your fault.”

Xiao Ye Hu’s will entered treasure yellow heaven and spread the news, trying to humiliate Fang

clan.

Such words made the Fang clansmen cry out in deeper anguish.

“Will anyone save us!”

“Lord ancestors, we are here.”

“Why are you crying? Don’t be a disgrace to Fang clan.”

The best situation for them was to be bought by Fang clan’s Gu Immortals.

Wang Xiao Er was among them, he shouted alongside the rest.

He was feeling very uneasy now.

He was treated as a Fang clan member because the situation was too chaotic earlier. Fang

clan’s members did not know that an external Gu Master was mixed among them.

Different from the rest, Wang Xiao Er did not want to be bought by Fang clan Gu Immortals.

Because the Fang clan Gu Immortals knew he was an outsider, not long ago, Fang Dong Xi had

not just interrogated him roughly, he even used all sorts of vicious methods to torture Wang Xiao

Er before healing him.

“Chaotic times are starting, Fang clan is a super force but it has actually gotten into this state.”

“They courted death!”

“Fang clan definitely did not want to kill Wan clan’s first supreme elder, they held back. In my

opinion, Wan clan’s first supreme elder was too useless, he actually died so easily.”

“Right now, Wan clan is different. With Wan Gu Chou’s revival, they will rise up to power again

with such a legendary expert.”

“Cooperating with Fang Yuan will give us Immortal Gu transactions. But working with Heavenly

Court will allow us to revive Gu Immortals. They are both quite attractive!”

Fang clan’s members were now slaves, this was a warning to many Gu Immortals.

The five regions chaotic war had not started, but the super forces had already started to

destabilize.

At once, all of them felt varying emotions, Fang clan’s predicament was also their concern for

the future.

“How are you selling these human slaves?” Some people put up bids.

Human slaves were getting rarer and rarer, for the last hundred years, there were no such large

scale human slave trade activities.

After all, capturing human enemies and selling them as slaves was an undeniable demonic act.

But right now, these Fang clan members had lost the battle, there was a proper excuse to sell

them.

Chapter 2269: Heavenly Melody

Among the Gu Immortals who came to purchase Fang clan slaves, there might be Fang clan Gu

Immortals, but treasure yellow heaven would not decipher them.

Xiao Ye Hu did not care.

He quoted his price expressionlessly, it was a normal price that was neither too low nor high.

Immediately, several transactions were completed.

“With this batch of Fang clan members, I have made up for the final gap, I can try to refine

wealth Gu now.” Shi Kang was very happy.

“Please don’t let me get sold to Fang clan Gu Immortals!” Wang Xiao Er prayed in his heart.

“I’ll take this batch, they seem to be of decent quality.” The Gu Immortal spoke to Xiao Ye Hu

and chose a batch.

Even among human slaves, quality differed.

Among which, rank five Gu Masters were the most popular, following that were the young and

talented Gu Masters.

At once, crying sounds could be heard.

The Fang clan members were sold off, their families were broken up for good, they bid farewell

to each other here for the last time, it was a sad sight to see.

Here, the Fang clan members’ lives would be greatly changed, the future was bound to be very

different from now.

The pitiful Fang clan members would be sold to Shi Kang as Gu materials and used till they

died.

Some of the luckier ones would be specially chosen as Gu Immortal seeds to join certain sects

or clans. If they succeed in becoming Gu Immortals in the future, it would be a huge profit for

the buyer.

Of course, there were few who were regarded as Gu Immortal seeds.

“Fang clan lost but they are not out yet. It seems that this contest will still go on.” In the two

heavens, Fairy Zi Wei retracted her divine sense from treasure yellow heaven.

She had been paying close attention to the trend of the world recently.

Currently, she had already been in the two heavens with Ying Wu Xie for a few days.

During this period of time, they had a tough journey filled with difficulties and danger.

The immemorial two heavens were dangerous to begin with, ordinary rank eight Gu Immortals

had to be very careful when they explored.

Now that the two heavens had fused, the environment was chaotic and messy, it was filled with

changes. The five regions had already been implicated, while the fused two heavens itself was

even more intense.

From time to time, roaming immemorial desolate beasts would appear, there could even be

huge armies made of desolate beasts, ancient desolate beasts, and even immemorial desolate

beasts.

It was still relatively safer to meet wild beasts, the scariest thing was getting into a place with

dense dao marks, because the two heavens had shattered and fused together, many dangerous

and forbidden places were shifting around now.

If one got trapped, they would be like a mortal stepping into a quicksand in the desert, they

could only wait for death in despair.

Even an expert like Fairy Zi Wei would encounter danger.

“Ying Wu Xie, just how far away are we?” Fairy Zi Wei asked.

Currently, they were hiding within a soul beast army.

This soul beast army had many ancient soul beasts, Ying Wu Xie took control of it.

Ying Wu Xie replied: ”From what I sense, we still need three days to reach the main body.

During this period, if he moves, the timing could be extended or shortened.”

Ying Wu Xie used a soul path killer move and managed to sense the location of his main body.

But Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s speed was far beyond them.

Thankfully, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable had lost his senses, he did not use defensive

methods against investigations, he was also roaming around causing destruction, he did not

avoid them.

Thus, during this time, Ying Wu Xie and Fairy Zi Wei managed to get closer to Spectral Soul

Demon Venerable.

Howl!

The soul beast that was moving ahead suddenly stopped, it cried out in pain like it had slammed

into an invisible wall.

“What’s going on?” Fairy Zi Wei instantly became alert.

“Be careful, all of you, stop!” Ying Wu Xie also controlled his soul beast army and stopped,

floating in the air.

In the past few days, they had used the soul beasts to probe many dangerous areas.

The cost was thirty percent of the soul beasts they controlled.

“This is... heavenly chasm?” Fairy Zi Wei checked and gasped in surprise.

Heavenly chasm was a rank nine heaven path immortal material, it had an irregular form but

was incredibly big. It was formless and ethereal, although it seemed like empty air, it could not

be passed through.

“We are so unlucky, to think that we would be obstructed by this!” Ying Wu Xie was

disappointed.

The heavenly chasm was not dangerous but it was a huge problem for them.

Because they needed to get past the heavenly chasm, but they could not find out what its exact

shape or distribution was.

Both Fairy Zi Wei’s and Ying Wu Xie’s investigative methods had a smaller range than the size

of the entire heavenly chasm.

In other words, they could only test their luck by choosing one direction and trying to get around

it from there.

It was inestimable how much time they would need to use up now.

But there was no helping it, Fairy Zi Wei and Ying Wu Xie could only make a detour.

After moving for a long distance, the heavenly chasm remained in front of them, it was like a

huge wall that blocked their every path.

Suddenly, a sound was transmitted into Ying Wu Xie and Fairy Zi Wei’s ears.

Initially, they did not mind it, they thought that it was a normal wind sound.

But soon, it got louder and more delightful.

When the two immortals were attracted by the sound, their actions unconsciously slowed down.

After more than ten breaths of time, the entire soul beast army had stopped in the air, they were

completely entranced by the beautiful sound.

This sound did not contain any instrumental component, it purely composed of wind, rain,

thunder, bird chirping sounds and so on. However, the outcome was a beautiful melody that

made Fairy Zi Wei and Ying Wu Xie addicted to it.

“Oh no, this is the heavenly melody!” Fairy Zi Wei was internally shaken, she wanted to warn

Ying Wu Xie but she only gasped out loud, her body completely relaxed as she fell into deep

entrancement.

Ying Wu Xie had lower cultivation level than her, he was much more immersed in it, he was

already showing an expression of indulgence, he could not save himself.

Fairy Zi Wei’s heart was sinking.

She knew that this was a truly desperate situation.

If this went on, she and Ying Wu Xie, along with the soul beasts, would be completely immersed

in the heavenly melody, they would eventually lose their senses and become floating corpses.

Fairy Zi Wei wanted to save herself but after several attempts, she could not even activate any

Gu worm, not to mention killer moves.

If she had reacted in time and did her best to stop it, there might be a chance of survival.

But she had been listening to the heavenly melody for too long, she was like a human struggling

after falling into the water, her strength was depleting as she drank more and more water.

“Am I... going to die here?” Fairy Zi Wei felt her eyelids getting heavier, her vision was turning

blur, she could not help but feel like shutting her eyes and enjoying the beautiful melody with her

full attention.

This might be the most enjoyable way to die.

As Fairy Zi Wei approached death, her mind was filled with indulgent and wonderful emotions.

If she died, she would not feel any sadness, despair, pain, or other negative emotions.

But right when Fairy Zi Wei and Ying Wu Xie were about to die, the heavenly melody started

weakening.

A Gu Immortal was flying closer to them from afar.

He wore a red and white robe, standing straight like a spear or sword. His eyebrows were sharp

like swords, a mysterious and profound light was hidden in his eyes.

He revealed a faint smile from the corner of his lips, he gave off the aura of gentleness and

confidence.

It was the current rank eight sound path great expert — Feng Jiu Ge!

“What a beautiful heavenly melody.” Feng Jiu Ge laughed brightly as he looked at the soul beast

army and the two incapacitated immortals, Fairy Zi Wei and Ying Wu Xie.

The heavenly melody that almost killed the two Shadow Sect members did not manage to affect

Feng Jiu Ge, in fact, he used a mysterious method to contain and collect it.

“Feng Jiu Ge?!” As Fairy Zi Wei slowly recovered, she looked at the Gu Immortal in front of her

with shock.

Ever since the fate war, Feng Jiu Ge went missing without a trace. Had he been in the two

heavens all along?

Since he was able to take the rank nine immortal material heavenly melody, did this mean that

his strength had grown again? Did he retain his pseudo venerable battle strength?

It was a mystery.

As Feng Jiu Ge collected and stored the heavenly melody, he activated a killer move.

Two lumps of profound light shot into Fairy Zi Wei and Ying Wu Xie, wrapping around them and

slowly entering their bodies.

Because of the heavenly melody, Fairy Zi Wei still could not move, Feng Jiu Ge was free to do

this without resistance.

“What... what killer move is this? What are you trying to do?” Fairy Zi Wei slowly regained her

ability to speak.

Feng Jiu Ge replied: ”Don’t worry, I’m not seeking to harm you. After the fate war, haven’t our

circumstances become quite similar now?”

Feng Jiu Ge said this as he turned to leave.

Fairy Zi Wei could not catch up, she watched as he flew away casually.

“What, what happened?” Ying Wu Xie recovered and watched Feng Jiu Ge’s figure fly far away

in the sky.

“We were hit by the heavenly melody and fell into grave danger. But Feng Jiu Ge suddenly

appeared and collected the heavenly melody, he also used a mysterious method on us.” Fairy Zi

Wei explained the situation quickly.

Ying Wu Xie stared with wide eyes: ”What... Feng Jiu Ge didn’t kill us?”

“He is also a demonic path member, he has betrayed Heavenly Court, what is the point of killing

us?” Fairy Zi Wei sighed: ”If he wanted us to die, he could have waited by the side, he would

gain our corpses, immortal apertures, and Immortal Gu. His motive was to get the heavenly

melody, other than that, he also wanted to use that move on us.”

The two used their methods and inspected their bodies, but could not find anything strange or

peculiar.

It was as if Feng Jiu Ge’s killer move was just an illusion that had not actually been used.

“Regardless of whether he has pseudo venerable battle strength, his methods are becoming

more profound!” Fairy Zi Wei sighed.

“What killer move is this?” Ying Wu Xie frowned: ”Is he trying to use us as bait to harm the main

body?”

Fairy Zi Wei shook her head: ”We have too few clues, but according to my intuition, Feng Jiu Ge

does not seem interested in Master Spectral Soul. Also, even if your guess is correct, are we

going to stop here?”

Ying Wu Xie considered it and gritted his teeth while nodding: ”Of course we have to continue

moving. Even if Feng Jiu Ge wants to harm the main body, he is only rank eight, how can he

harm my main body?”

The two immortals set off again.

Because of the heavenly melody, half of the beast group was wiped out.

Since they were near the heavenly chasm, the army could not be replenished.

This time, to guard against the heavenly melody, the soul beasts were widely spread out, they

were far from each other.

“The main body, I can sense the main body!” Not long after, Ying Wu Xie suddenly shouted.

Following his sensation, the two immortals changed directions and saw Spectral Soul Demon

Venerable after a few minutes.

“So the main body was on the other side of the heavenly chasm, but because of this rank nine

immortal material’s interference, I thought that he was far away!” Ying Wu Xie suddenly realized.

He shouted: ”I am here!”

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable saw Ying Wu Xie and immediately roared.

Boom boom boom!

With a chain of sounds, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable landed several hundred fists on the

heavenly chasm.

The heavenly chasm shook intensely, it was on the brink of breaking.

Ying Wu Xie and Fairy Zi Wei turned pale, why did Spectral Soul Demon Venerable turn so

ferocious after seeing Ying Wu Xie? It was as if they were mortal enemies.

What in the world was going on?

Chapter 2270: Heavenly Court’s Assault

Qin Ding Ling and Jun Shen Guang flew carefully in the two heavens.

“This Old Immortal Hua Yu is really crafty! He actually wants us to convince Flickering Light

grotto-heaven first.” Jun Shen Guang said begrudgingly.

After the two of them received the mission to make Old Immortal Hua Yu change sides, they got

close to Profound Literature grotto-heaven and lurked there.

While Old Immortal Hua Yu was chasing away beast groups outside, they secretly met with him.

“Do you think Old Immortal Hua Yu is purposely wasting our time now, after we convince

Flickering Light grotto-heaven to join us, he will already have his trap prepared?” Jun Shen

Guang asked.

Qin Ding Ling sighed: ”This is unlikely. Old Immortal Hua Yu has been hesitating for a long time,

but the reason why he is staying on the fence and being ambiguous is because he is afraid that

Fang Yuan will try to kill him if he betrays him!”

“In this situation, he wants the attention on him to be smaller, thus, he wants to see more

grotto-heavens betraying Fang Yuan, in that case, Profound Literature grotto-heaven will not be

as big of a target.”

“But the situation that you mentioned cannot be ruled out as well.”

Jun Shen Guang asked: ”Then what should we do? Flickering Light grotto-heaven is led by Gu

Immortal Liang Jing Jing, but different from Old Immortal Hua Yu, we do not know much about

her, we cannot be sure of her true intentions.”

Qin Ding Ling pondered for a while and said: ”Even if we don’t, I’m sure Old Immortal Hua Yu

already has some leads. Otherwise, he would not have chosen this grotto-heaven specially for

us.”

“Maybe it is time to use that move.”

Qin Ding Ling started to fly slower as her expression became resolute, it was clear that she had

made up her mind.

Jun Shen Guang showed a look of confusion.

Qin Ding Ling said: ”Flickering Light grotto-heaven is not far away, but before taking the risk, I

want to use my luck path method to make some arrangements.”

Jun Shen Guang asked worriedly: ”Is the cost of this move too high?”

Qin Ding Ling shook her head: ”Although it will consume some of my luck path dao marks, for

the sake of Heavenly Court, this is a small cost. The reason why I hesitated was because this

move has a huge drawback. It is the same as using my future good luck in advance, it may have

the effect of helping our enemies.”

“So that’s it.” Jun Shen Guang nodded.

Qin Ding Ling continued to speak: ”But thinking about it, it is very important for us to recruit Old

Immortal Hua Yu. With the contest of three venerables, for a long time in the future, this balance

will continue to hold.”

“Western Desert’s Fang clan has already been driven out of their territory, if Old Immortal Hua

Yu and the others betray Fang Yuan, then Heaven Refining Demon Venerable’s reputation will

become the lowest of the three. Regardless of whether Fang Yuan goes to kill Old Immortal Hua

Yu, he will still face losses.”

“For us rank eight Gu Immortals to be able to influence the situation of the three venerables,

isn’t it normal that the price to pay is huge?”

Jun Shen Guang was convinced by her: ”That’s true! Lady Qin Ding Ling, go ahead and use it, I

will guard you.”

Not long after, Qin Ding Ling finished her preparation and used the killer move.

However, this killer move took a whole hour before it ended.

Qin Ding Ling was pale and covered in sweat, her expression was quite strange.

“Did something happen?” Jun Shen Guang sensed that something was wrong long ago, he

quickly asked.

Qin Ding Ling did not conceal the matter, she answered: ”When I used this killer move, there

was a mystical change like the entire world was responding to me. This killer move normally

takes ten or so breaths to activate, but in that situation earlier, with the help of heaven and

earth, I persevered and continued to use it. In the end, the move’s activation took one hour.”

Jun Shen Guang frowned: ”I’ve heard about the secret behind the power of a Dao Lord. After a

venerable refines natural dao marks, every move they make will be amplified by the dao marks,

which is the resonance of heaven and earth. Lady Qin Ding Ling, why did that happen to you?”

Qin Ding Ling shook her head: ”I can’t comprehend it either, but that is not a problem. On this

expedition to Flickering Light grotto-heaven, we will definitely receive huge help. Let’s go.”

“Mmm.”

The two Heavenly Court immortals continued on their way.

On the other side.

Boom!

With a loud rumbling sound, the heavenly chasm was unable to take any more hits, the weakest

segment was pierced by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s arm.

The two sides were connected at once.

Fairy Zi Wei’s and Ying Wu Xie’s pupils shrunk rapidly, in an instant, they sensed an

unparalleled killing intent surging from Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s body to the

surroundings.

His killing intent was so intense that even Fairy Zi Wei and Ying Wu Xie felt that they were

mortals about to be engulfed by a tsunami.

Helplessness, despair, fear, panic, these emotions appeared naturally in them as they spread

rapidly.

“Quickly go!” Fairy Zi Wei was a wisdom path great expert after all, she quickly reacted and

used her killer move.

With her help, Ying Wu Xie regained his senses too.

Boom boom boom.

More and more arms pierced the heavenly chasm as they extended towards the two.

The rank nine heavenly chasm could trap Fairy Zi Wei or Ying Wu Xie, but it was only a small

hurdle for the senseless Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

Fairy Zi Wei and Ying Wu Xie quickly retreated.

But suddenly, a black arm increased in speed and grabbed onto Ying Wu Xie.

At the moment of life and death, Ying Wu Xie activated his method.

Immortal killer move — Change Soul Technique!

At the next moment, he swapped position with a soul beast. This ancient soul beast took his

place and got captured by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable. Meanwhile, Ying Wu Xie appeared

far away and quickly escaped for his life.

During this period of time, Ying Wu Xie practiced hard and created his killer move, change soul

technique.

Compared to Fang Yuan’s switch soul in dream, this change soul technique had its own merits

and demerits.

Ying Wu Xie managed to escape.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable growled angrily and squeezed with his huge claw as the

ancient soul beast was ground into powder, its ancient soul core was absorbed by Spectral Soul

Demon Venerable instantly.

More and more huge claws slashed through the heavenly chasm and surrounded him.

Nearly ten hands opened up, an intense suction force appeared from the centers of the palms.

Ying Wu Xie’s soul beast group had no resistance at all, they were all absorbed.

As the claws contracted, they did not squeeze the soul beasts this time, instead, they were

molded.

Be it desolate beast or ancient desolate beast, the soul beasts cried out in agony. After several

breaths of time, the huge claws opened up as these soul beasts were released.

Not only did the size of the strength group change, their strength also rose dramatically, there

were actually three immemorial soul beasts among them.

These soul beasts were completely loyal to Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, they screeched as

they attacked Ying Wu Xie.

Ying Wu Xie spat out blood, he felt incredibly stunned.

The method that he used to enslave the soul beasts had been completely erased by Spectral

Soul Demon Venerable, he suffered a backlash as a result.

Fairy Zi Wei brought Ying Wu Xie along with her as they quickly retreated.

As purple smoke started to rise, these soul beasts were temporarily trapped, they could only

move around in the smoke.

After flying for some time, they two immortals heard a loud sound as the surrounding hundred li

started to shake.

The heavenly chasm was broken through by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable!

The two immortals turned pale as they did their best to flee.

But Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was incredibly fast, not long after, he reached them.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s left head roared loudly.

The silhouette of Dang Hun Mountain appeared immediately as it slammed towards the two

immortals.

They could not avoid it.

Immortal killer move — Purple Will Production!

At the crucial moment, Fairy Zi Wei used a killer move as her body shook, turning into purple

smoke that carried Ying Wu Xie as they vanished on the spot.

After a few breaths of time, purple smoke was produced out of nowhere several tens of li away.

The purple smoke turned back into Fairy Zi Wei while Ying Wu Xie fell out from it.

Thankfully, when they encountered the heavenly melody and after Feng Jiu Ge left, Fairy Zi Wei

used her method at every set interval of distance traveled.

This method was originally meant to defend against the heavenly melody. But to think that she

would have to use it to avoid Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

After using it, the two immortals managed to survive.

But danger was far from over, the two immortals were still in a perilous situation.

“Bring me along and leave. After using this move, there is a huge drawback, I need to

exterminate the large amount of purple will in my mind before I can use it again.” Fairy Zi Wei

said in an urgent tone.

Ying Wu Xie quickly used his soul path method as he flew away with Fairy Zi Wei.

After the two immortals escaped for some time, Ying Wu Xie was shocked to find that his speed

was getting slower, any soul path killer move that he used had increasing expenditure.

“I have been struck!”

“It happened when the main body caught me earlier.”

“What move is this?”

“It seems to counter all soul path killer moves!”

Ying Wu Xie was soon rendered useless.

Fairy Zi Wei had no choice but to take over and escape with Ying Wu Xie.

As Spectral Soul Demon Venerable approached, Fairy Zi Wei had no choice but to use purple

will production again to stall for time desperately.

“Let’s split up!” Ying Wu Xie gritted his teeth and suggested.

Fairy Zi Wei shook her head, she rejected him without hestiation.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable wanted to kill Ying Wu Xie now. If they split up, Fairy Zi Wei

would survive but Ying Wu Xie would definitely not be spared.

Fairy Zi Wei was affected by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s method and became absolutely

loyal to him. Currently, because Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was not in the right state of

mind, her loyalty went to Spectral Soul’s split soul.

She would do anything to protect Ying Wu Xie, even if it cost her life.

But right at this time, three rank eight Gu Immortals appeared before Fairy Zi Wei.

The left one had a round head and large ears, he wore a loose robe and had an intense qi path

aura, he was Heavenly Court’s Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch.

The right one wore a golden hoop on his head, it was Golden Hooped Great Immortal.

The Gu Immortal in the center looked kind and merciful, his eyebrows were very long, reaching

his chest, it was one of the three dukes, Duke Mei!

“Fairy Zi Wei is here after all!”

“Oh, Ying Wu Xie is here too.”

Duke Mei, Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch, and Golden Hooped Great Immortal were here

on Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s orders to capture Fairy Zi Wei.

Fairy Zi Wei’s immortal aperture was with Heavenly Court, with such an obvious lead, after Star

Constellation Immortal Venerable personally made deductions, the three immortals managed to

find her.

Fairy Zi Wei and Ying Wu Xie’s expressions changed.

They were facing danger from both directions.

This was a desperate predicament!

“What do we do?” Ying Wu Xie turned pale.

Fairy Zi Wei frowned deeply, at the moment of crisis, she shouted loudly: ”Feng Jiu Ge, I know

you are nearby. If you lend us a hand now, we will repay you tenfold in the future!

“Feng Jiu Ge... that Heavenly Court traitor?” Golden Hooped Great Immortal frowned.

Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch snorted coldly: ”Good, we will take care of him too.”

Duke Mei was about to speak but his brows suddenly rose as his long eyebrows shook

intensely: ”Oh no, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable is here!”

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s mountain-like body appeared in everyone’s vision.

Chapter 2271: Left To Their Own Devices

At once, the situation became very complex.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable broke through the heavenly chasm and chased after them.

Fairy Zi Wei and Ying Wu Xie were trapped in the middle.

Heavenly Court’s three immortals, Golden Hooped Great Immortal, Seven Fiendish Primeval

Monarch, and Duke Mei stood in front of the Shadow Sect members, while Feng Jiu Ge was

indeed hiding nearby like what Fairy Zi Wei predicted.

If Spectral Soul Demon Venerable had his sanity, Feng Jiu Ge would not do this, that was too

risky.

Fairy Zi Wei was really only trying her luck earlier.

She could not be certain of Feng Jiu Ge’s location, this was only a possibility she deduced.

After all, Feng Jiu Ge did not kill them but used a method on them. This meant that Feng Jiu Ge

wanted to make use of the two.

Fairy Zi Wei was in a desperate situation, she had to use all the methods she could think of, in

that situation, Feng Jiu Ge became her hope.

But Feng Jiu Ge showed no signs of helping.

He squinted as he looked at the two Shadow Sect immortals from afar, he sighed internally: ”It is

useless, I can already hear the cries of your destiny, even though it has some turbulence, it is

en-route to the abyss, the outcome has been decided.”

During this period when he went missing, he had been cultivating the killer move destiny song,

he made a lot of progress.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s left head growled as soul balls appeared out of nowhere.

The soul balls had tiny tadpole-like tails behind them as they quickly got close to Fairy Zi Wei

and Ying Wu Xie, before exploding intensely.

Fairy Zi Wei and Ying Wu Xie could not resist them, their souls shook and almost shattered on

the spot.

“Attack!” At the other end, Duke Mei was the first to use his killer move.

Golden Hooped Great Immortal and Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch followed closely after.

“I am going to die!” Ying Wu Xie’s expression was ashen.

“How can this be?” At the next moment, Fairy Zi Wei’s expression turned to shock.

Because the Heavenly Court immortals’ attacks were not aimed at them but Spectral Soul

Demon Venerable instead, they resisted the soul ball method while helping to defend the

Shadow Sect immortals.

Heavenly Court was saving the Shadow Sect immortals?

Even a wisdom path great expert like Fairy Zi Wei was stunned.

“Don’t tell me, because Star Constellation Immortal Venerable revived, she is allowing me to

return to Heavenly Court in exchange for betraying master?”

“Or maybe, they want to capture the crucial split soul, Ying Wu Xie, to use a method against

master?”

Methods to create clones were convenient but they also exposed a weakness.

In this world, nothing was perfect.

With benefit came cost.

Clone methods had many demerits, the main thing was that their connection to the main body

could be exploited.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s split soul had a weakness that was exposed long ago.

It was the sharing of attainment level.

It was an advantage and also a disadvantage.

When Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s clone created sovereign immortal fetus Gu, a vast

amount of attainment levels were expended, forming dream realms.

This caused Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s own attainment level to fall as well.

Regardless of the intention of the three Heavenly Court immortals, the Shadow Sect immortals

had survived because of them.

Far away, Feng Jiu Ge shook his head.

Be it the Shadow Sect immortals or Heavenly Court’s three immortals, their efforts were all in

vain.

As expected, the number of soul balls continued to increase, they grew to a scale that the five

immortals had trouble defending against.

Be it Fairy Zi Wei or Duke Mei, they were all in desperation.

“Is this the might of a venerable?!”

“Spectral Soul Demon Venerable has lost his senses and even has such heavy injuries...”

“Damn it!”

The Heavenly Court immortals could not save the Shadow Sect immortals, they were implicated

instead and became Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s next targets.

At the next moment, a huge number of soul balls would explode intensely and take the lives of

these five immortals...

At this moment.

Feng Jiu Ge’s expression changed.

“Oh?” At this moment, he felt a vast power rampaging into the battlefield.

This was the power of luck path, it was grand and vast!

“Luck path... is the representation of uncertainty.”

“This power was initially small, but as the luck path dao marks in the two heavens grew, a huge

variable was created. Who is the source of this?”

Feng Jiu Ge pondered deeply.

The power of luck path was so grand it was on par with a rank nine killer move!

Crack crack.

The power of luck path changed the two heavens, it changed the entire battlefield.

Originally, the two heavens were fusing together, black heaven and white heaven were joining

together piece and piece. The five immortals were in the area of white heaven.

But now, the immemorial black heaven fragment flew towards them from afar.

White heaven had abundant light path dao marks, while black heaven had more dark path dao

marks, because of the conflict of dao marks, as the immemorial black heaven approached,

white heaven’s fragment shattered.

A large number of black and white heaven fragments created a huge current.

The current swept like a torrent, bringing Spectral Soul Demon Venerable along with it.

Without Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s control, the soul balls stayed at their spots without

moving or exploding.

“We need to go!” Using this chance, Fairy Zi Wei brought Ying Wu Xie along as they flew into

the immemorial black heaven that was right beside them.

“Wait.” The three Heavenly Court immortals quickly chased them.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was swept away by the two heavens’ current, but after it

weakened, he was freed again.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was covered in injuries currently, heaven path dao marks were

carved all over his injuries. There were even fragments of the two heavens stabbed into his

body, it was as if he was stabbed by countless mirrors.

Because he was far away and due to the heaven path dao marks on his injuries, Spectral Soul

Demon Venerable could no longer sense Ying Wu Xie.

He was senseless and could not use investigative or tracking methods.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable roared in anger and vented for some time before he was lured

towards a nearby grotto-heaven.

This was Flickering Light grotto-heaven.

Inside, the leader of Flickering Light grotto-heaven, Gu Immortal Liang Jing Jing, was already

trembling in fear.

In the past, with Flickering Light grotto-heaven hidden and condensed into a tiny spot, Spectral

Soul Demon Venerable would not be able to find it in his current state.

But now, the fusion of the two heavens had reached the most intense moment, as a heaven

vein node, Flickering Light grotto-heaven was affected by it and got exposed to the outside

world.

“Alliance Leader, save me!!” Liang Jing Jing did not hesitate, she quickly asked Fang Yuan for

help.

“I am willing to contribute light heaven for a large amount of contribution points in exchange for

Lord Alliance Leader’s help to save my Flickering Light grotto-heaven!” Liang Jing Jing

screamed out in terror.

“Light heaven?” Fang Yuan quickly received Liang Jing Jing’s distress message while he was

unsealing the truthful floating ice.

After receiving the letter, he learned of light heaven.

Flickering Light grotto-heaven had devoured many fragments of the immemorial nine heavens,

but its inner space was still too small.

A certain generation’s Flickering Light Grotto Lord came up with a brilliant plan to develop the

grotto-heaven, that was to create an artificial heaven.

That was the source of light heaven.

From then on, the generations of Gu Immortals of Flickering Light grotto-heaven spent their

lives to work on this grand plan, contributing everything into this.

They collected heavenly light and refined them carefully, slowly expanding the light heaven of

Flickering Light grotto-heaven.

Its current size had already surpassed the original space of Flickering Light grotto-heaven itself.

Fang Yuan quickly considered this.

His original plan was to let Zhan Bu Du stabilize the immortal aperture while he built more

resource points and created more dao veins. After that, he would absorb the Primordial Domain

and gain a huge boost of attainment levels.

With the attainment levels and stabilized the sovereign immortal aperture, he would be able to

annex more grotto-heavens of the two heavens.

In the current situation, Flickering Light grotto-heaven was going to be destroyed, Fang Yuan’s

plans were unable to keep up with the development of events.

Fang Yuan was currently only a master in light path.

If he wanted to defend Flickering Light grotto-heaven, he would need to fight against Spectral

Soul Demon Venerable. If the battle becomes too intense and obscured heavenly secret fails,

he would be exposed, causing Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal

Venerable to attack him at the same time.

And most crucially, against other venerables, Fang Yuan did not have much of an advantage.

Even though he had two rank nine Immortal Gu, he had not created complementary killer moves

to use them with. He also had refinement path as his main path, it was not specialized in

fighting.

“If the venerables end up fighting, I only have an advantage in immortal essence. However, if

they join up to suppress me, my immortal essence will be countered by their sheer number.”

“I cannot save Flickering Light grotto-heaven!”

Fang Yuan decided to abandon Flickering Light grotto-heaven resolutely.

“Lord Alliance Leader, this light heaven is incredibly valuable, if you place it in the sovereign

immortal aperture, it will be a great addition.” Liang Jing Jing urged, this was the only thing that

she could offer to Fang Yuan now.

“Lord Alliance Leader, can you hear me? Please reply to me!!!” Liang Jing Jing stomped her feet

in anxiety.

But now, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable had already arrived, with a loud sound, he destroyed

the grotto-heaven’s entrance.

Hundreds or thousands of arms entered the immortal aperture, wherever they went, lives were

slaughtered, nobody could defend against the might of the venerable!

Liang Jing Jing had to hide in light heaven while she cried and sought help from Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan had an indifferent expression, he knew that this decision would affect his prestige,

but fighting against Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was even worse.

These subordinates were only tools in his contest against the venerables, he would not sacrifice

his own benefits for just one of these tools.

Chess pieces were pieces because they were meant to be used, they were also meant to be

discarded when necessary.

“Fang Yuan, I hate you, I hate you! How dare you call yourself Great Love Immortal Venerable?

I was wrong about you, you are leaving us to die, you are not fit to be the alliance leader!!”

Liang Jing Jing cursed in despair.

At this moment, Fang Yuan showed a joyful expression.

He had reached a qualitative development in unsealing the truthful floating ice.

His heaven path attainment level reached grandmaster!

The number of heaven path dao marks rose drastically, while other paths’ attainment level also

grew slightly.

And most importantly, he gained heavenly secret Gu’s rank nine recipe!

“Rank nine heavenly secret Gu?”

This was an unexpected gain for Fang Yuan.

Even someone like him could not help but feel his eyes light up.

“It was really wise to not save Flickering Light grotto-heaven.”

“That was close...”

“If I had interfered to save Flickering Light grotto-heaven, it would trigger a battle between

venerables later. I would have been a step away from obtaining rank nine heavenly secret

Immortal Gu’s recipe!”

This Immortal Gu recipe came at the perfect timing, it was very useful to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan immediately decided that his third rank nine Immortal Gu would be — Heavenly

Secret!

Chapter 2272: Doing Everything To Help

Qin Ding Ling and Jun Shen Guang flew rapidly along the way.

Ever since Qin Ding Ling used her luck path killer move, the two of them had a smooth journey

with nearly no hurdles.

Jun Shen Guang sighed in admiration and praised it many times.

Qin Ding Ling explained: ”The might of the move far exceeded my usual limits, I have already

comprehended a part of the reason for the resonance with heaven and earth.”

“Back then, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable placed Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace in

Northern Plains’ black heaven, it was there for three hundred thousand years.”

“In these three hundred thousand years, Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace had been exerting

its effect to lay out luck path dao marks, spreading nearly throughout the entire immemorial

black heaven.”

“Precisely because of this terrifying accumulation, it caused us to fail and suffer huge losses

when Central Continent invaded Northern Plains to try and take fortune rivaling heaven Gu.”

“Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had already predicted that the two heavens would fuse, thus, he

moved Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace away and used it in the battle in Crazed Demon

Cave.”

“But the three hundred thousand years of accumulated luck path dao marks are all carved in

Northern Plains’ immemorial black heaven. Furthermore, the number is too vast to imagine.”

“After the two heavens fused, both black and white heavens broke into countless fragments of

various sizes, this caused the luck path dao marks to spread out as well.

Jun Shen Guang asked: ”So why did your luck path killer move get amplified by these luck path

dao marks? Is it because a move was made by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable?”

Qin Ding Ling had a grim expression: ”If that is so, this will be part of Giant Sun Immortal

Venerable’s scheme. But this is quite unlikely, because I have already asked Star Constellation

Immortal Venerable about it, she told me that these luck path dao marks are natural dao marks,

they do not belong to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.”

Jun Shen Guang was more confused now: ”So why was there a resonance?”

Qin Ding Ling shook her head: ”Forget about this for now, the matter at hand is to recruit

Flickering Light grotto-heaven!”

Regarding this, Jun Shen Guang was even more confident than before: ”Lady Qin Ding Ling’s

luck path killer move is unparalleled, in my opinion, we will definitely succeed this time.”

A while later.

The two immortals got close to Flickering Light grotto-heaven.

They were shocked to see that Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was rampaging inside

Flickering Light grotto-heaven.

He did not enter the grotto-heaven physically, but he broke the grotto-heaven door and

extended hundreds of arms inside to slaughter and destroy everything he could reach, be it

mortals or immortals, it was a cruel sight.

Qin Ding Ling went into a daze.

She had never expected such a thing to happen.

The immemorial two heavens were too huge.

It was very improbable for Spectral Soul Demon Venerable to find trouble with Flickering Light

grotto-heaven at this very moment.

Jun Shen Guang’s mouth opened wide as he stared at Spectral Soul Demon Venerable before

turning around to look at Qin Ding Ling with a complex expression.

He seemed to be asking: ”Is this the effect of your luck path killer move?”

Qin Ding Ling coughed and said awkwardly: ”Spectral Soul Demon Venerable is a venerable,

even if my luck path method was amplified by the resonance of heaven and earth, it should not

have such an immense effect.”

Jun Shen Guang was dazed: ”What should we do?”

They had originally planned to recruit Profound Literature grotto-heaven, but Old Immortal Hua

Yu displayed the specialty of an information path expert.

He hinted to them that if they could recruit Flickering Light grotto-heaven, he would join them as

well.

But now, after Qin Ding Ling and Jun Shen Guang took the time to travel all this way to

Flickering Light grotto-heaven, they found that Flickering Light grotto-heaven was about to be

destroyed by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable!

“Quickly escape, grotto lord!”

“Let us draw the attention of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable!”

“Flickering Light grotto-heaven is going to be destroyed, but your immortal aperture and our

clansmen are all alive, please, you need to think of the big picture.”

At this time, six Gu Immortals flew out of Flickering Light grotto-heaven.

Rank eight light path Gu Immortal Liang Jing Jing was covered in heavy injuries, she was flying

away in tears now as the other Gu Immortals used their lives to defend her.

However, even if Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was not sane now, he was still a venerable.

He had overwhelming killing intent, seeing that these Gu Immortals were trying to escape, he

followed his instincts and tried to kill them.

The Gu Immortals of Flickering Light grotto-heaven were in imminent danger.

“A chance!” Jun Shen Guang shouted uncontrollably.

“So that’s it.” Qin Ding Ling understood at once: ”So this is the true effect of my luck path killer

move.”

Often, precious opportunities were hidden in dangerous situations.

“Let us help you!” Qin Ding Ling shouted and made a move first.

Jun Shen Guang quickly followed after her.

The Gu Immortals of Flickering Light grotto-heaven were initially fearful, according to their

current faction, they were enemies. But after realizing that the Heavenly Court immortals were

really helping them, these Gu Immortals developed an intense feeling of joy and gratitude.

Eventually, with the help of Qin Ding Ling and Jun Shen Guang, the Flickering Light

grotto-heaven Gu Immortals managed to escape.

Of course, they paid a huge price for this.

Qin Ding Ling was lightly injured while Jun Shen Guang was heavily injured, only three Gu

Immortals from Flickering Light grotto-heaven were left, one was unconscious while two were

heavily injured.

“This is the power of a venerable, we had no way to retaliate!” Jun Shen Guang sighed,

although he was safe now, he still sighed while feeling lingering fear.

He was a rank eight expert, but when chased by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, he was

fragile as a baby.

And this was when Spectral Soul Demon Venerable had no sanity, his actions were akin to a

soul beast.

“If Spectral Soul Demon Venerable chased after us with all his strength, we would not have

survived. Thankfully, his attention was mostly on Flickering Light grotto-heaven, he only chased

us for a while before returning to destroy the grotto-heaven!” Qin Ding Ling said.

“Sigh...”

“Our homeland...”

Of the three Gu Immortals of Flickering Light grotto-heaven, one was unconscious while two

had pale expression, they had a heavy mood and felt deep sadness, pain, anger, and

helplessness that could not be concealed.

“You have my condolences. Venerables are invincible while us rank eights are ants. It was

already our great fortune to have been able to escape.” Qin Ding Ling consoled.

Liang Jing Jing suddenly bowed and paid respects to Qin Ding Ling and Jun Shen Guang: ”I will

never forget the debt of saving our lives. We were enemies but you risked your lives to save us,

such righteousness and magnanimity is truly astounding, we are in deep awe.”

“Heavenly Court is truly the leader of humanity, you will forever be the number one force in the

world!”

“Compared to you, it is truly the biggest irony that our alliance leader called himself Great Love

Immortal Venerable and created the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance.”

Speaking of Fang Yuan, Liang Jing Jing felt immense hatred.

Qin Ding Ling and Jun Shen Guang looked at each other, seeing the joy in each other’s eyes.

The other Gu Immortal from Flickering Light grotto-heaven who was awake said: ”Friends from

Heavenly Court, our Grotto Lord is not a scheming person, Fang Yuan had really gone

overboard!”

“We had already asked him for help, we placed light heaven in treasure yellow heaven and

transacted it to him.”

“But he took our light heaven and ignored our plight, he showed no intentions of helping us, he

directly abandoned us!”

“We are his subordinates, we are members of his Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance!”

“Such an action is truly disappointing and shameful. To think that we believed he would change

his ways and become righteous after becoming venerable!”

Qin Ding Ling and Jun Shen Guang were very happy now.

Even without them saying anything, the Gu Immortals of Flickering Light grotto-heaven were

already hinting that they wanted to jump ship and join them!

“Lady Qin Ding Ling’s luck path killer move is truly profound and mystical.” Jun Shen Guang

praised internally.

Qin Ding Ling had a solemn expression: ”I won’t hide this from you, we came here because of a

certain reason.”

Next, Qin Ding Ling explained the details of why she came, she even requested for Liang Jing

Jing to help convince Old Immortal Hua Yu.

After hearing her words, Liang Jing Jing and the rest were also quite joyful.

They had no choice now but to try to join Heavenly Court, they were very uneasy about

betraying Fang Yuan.

If Fang Yuan came to them to settle the score, they would be in trouble.

Even if Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could block Heaven Refining Demon Venerable

for some time and protect, how could she guard them forever?

If Fang Yuan bore hatred and wanted to kill these traitors, he would have the initiative. He could

attack anytime he wanted to.

If he attacked on a random day, the Gu Immortals of Flickering Light grotto-heaven would not be

able to block him or wait for reinforcements.

They were absolutely sure of that now.

Because earlier, they saw the terrifying might of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

He was just a senseless venerable.

If he had sanity, if their enemy was Fang Yuan instead of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, that

would be incredibly terrifying. These Gu Immortals had no way of escaping at all.

The Gu Immortals of Flickering Light grotto-heaven confirmed that they were betraying him now,

in that case, they needed more traitors on this ship, so that his attention would be split among

them.

Thus, Liang Jing Jing did not even care about her injuries, she decided to go with Qin Ding Ling

to try and convince Old Immortal Hua Yu at Profound Literature grotto-heaven.

The group met with Old Immortal Hua Yu as they conversed secretly.

Qin Ding Ling spoke convincingly: ”Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable has already

deduced the result, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable seem to be roaming aimlessly and causing

destruction, but there is a pattern with his actions.”

“He is destroying the pillars that hold up immemorial white heaven. For example, the heavenly

chasm, heavenly pillar, or even heaven vein nodes like Flickering Light grotto-heaven.”

“Your Profound Literature grotto-heaven is the same as Flickering Light grotto-heaven, you are

both heaven vein nodes of immemorial white heaven. Spectral Soul Demon Venerable will

definitely come to destroy Profound Literature grotto-heaven in the future.”

Liang Jing Jing added: ”Old Immortal Hua Yu, we’ve known each other for many years. You’ve

seen what happened to me, Fang Yuan abandoned us, he even took away our light heaven, he

is cold, cruel, and shameless to the extreme!”

“Do you want to entrust your life to such an alliance leader?”

“You have to decide now. Once Spectral Soul Demon Venerable comes to find you, it will be too

late for Profound Literature grotto-heaven to relocate.”

Chapter 2273: Giving Heavenly Court Two Slaps

Old Immortal Hua Yu was convinced, he gritted his teeth and said: ”Does Heavenly Court have

a way to relocate my grotto-heaven?”

Qin Ding Ling smiled lightly; ”Of course we do. The foundation of Heavenly Court cannot be

matched by Longevity Heaven or Fang Yuan. Believe me, joining Heavenly Court is the wisest

decision!”

Old Immortal Hua Yu sighed deeply and replied: ”This is a huge matter, do allow me to return to

the grotto-heaven and hold a meeting with the other Gu Immortals.”

“We will wait here for the good news.” Qin Ding Ling showed a very understanding demeanor.

After Old Immortal Hua Yu returned to the grotto-heaven, he assembled the immortals and

explained the situation to them.

Although they were shocked, after three days and nights, they all agreed with Old Immortal Hua

Yu’s decision to switch sides to Heavenly Court.

Li Xiao Bai was among them, he also agreed to join Heavenly Court but he was feeling nervous

internally.

If Star Constellation Immortal Venerable used an investigative method on him, she might find

out his relationship with Fang Yuan. But he was just one person, while the intention to join

Heavenly Court had already been acknowledged among everyone.

Old Immortal Hua Yu led the immortals out of the grotto-heaven, they met with Qin Ding Ling

and Jun Shen Guang.

“Good, good, good.” Qin Ding Ling welcomed them as she said: ”Everyone, by joining the right

side, not only will you gain immense benefits, you will also create a brighter future for your

descendants.”

Old Immortal Hua Yu followed: ”Indeed, we should share such joyful news with others. I hope

Lady Qin Ding Ling and Lord Jun Shen Guang can help, I am willing to take a risk and rescue

more friends from this demonic Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance.”

Qin Ding Ling and Jun Shen Guang heard his words and laughed joyfully.

With Old Immortal Hua Yu taking the lead, and an example like Liang Jing Jing, because Qin

Ding Ling also used a luck path killer move earlier, their journey in convincing the rest to join

them went smoothly.

Several days later.

Nearly all of the human forces of the two heavens’ grotto-heavens had betrayed Fang Yuan,

they went to join Heavenly Court.

To speak the truth, Qin Ding Ling had only planned to recruit Old Immortal Hua Yu, but after

they took action, the results were actually much better than expected.

Such news could not be hidden, soon, the entire five regions’ Gu Immortals went into an uproar.

“Heavenly Court is still Heavenly Court after all!”

“Fang Yuan suffered a loss again.”

“Earlier in Western Desert, Heavenly Court won and forced Fang clan to sell all their resource

points as they fled from their territory.”

“Now, Fang Yuan’s influence in the two heavens has mostly been uprooted by Heavenly Court.”

“Even though Fang Yuan is a venerable, he cultivates refinement path. Star Constellation

Immortal Venerable is a wisdom path venerable, she is most skilled at plotting and making use

of people’s feelings.”

“To speak the truth, I can understand why they chose to join Heavenly Court. After all, Fang

Yuan did nothing and allowed Spectral Soul Demon Venerable to slaughter and cause

destruction in the two heavens, this is not what a leader should do. There are even rumors that

Fang Yuan took Liang Jing Jing’s light heaven without helping out!”

The Gu Immortals discussed among themselves.

Every action of a venerable, no matter how small, was a huge matter in the Gu Immortal world,

it would draw the attention of everyone.

Many people started to guess what Fang Yuan would do now.

Would he take revenge? Would he take action to pursue those grotto-heaven forces that

betrayed him?

Or would he just take this loss silently?

“If I were him, I would definitely take action! Traitors need to be punished, if they have an easier

life after this, what will the other members of the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance think?”

“If they can betray him so easily, aren’t they simply disregarding the status of Great Love

Immortal Venerable?”

“Maybe they are just bullying Lord Fang Yuan for being a newly advanced venerable.”

“How can the pride of a venerable be provoked so easily?”

Soon, waves of discussion erupted, becoming the main topic of treasure yellow heaven.

“Hehe.” Wu Yong smiled coldly, he did not need to guess to know that this discussion was

driven by Longevity Heaven.

If he could force Heaven Refining Demon Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable

to enter battle from this, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable would benefit immensely.

“Fang Yuan will not make a move, I know him too well.” Wu Yong looked in the direction of

Eastern Sea as he sighed deeply.

If it were him, he would not do anything either.

If a move was made, Fang Yuan would need to fight against Spectral Soul Demon Venerable,

this was extremely disadvantageous.

“With the contest of three venerables, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable clearly has the upper

hand. Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable have their

stronghold respectively, while Fang Yuan lacks in this aspect while also having the least

immortal essence.”

“In this situation, he needs to be even more vigilant. If he takes action abruptly, he will likely be

disadvantaged even further.”

“The rumors should be true, Fang Yuan took the light heaven but did not help her. In this aspect,

I cannot compare to him.”

Comparing himself to Fang Yuan, Wu Yong reflected upon himself and felt that his

shamelessness was still not enough, he had much to learn.

What were reputation and prestige?

They were just elements that were necessary to survive or gain victory.

If reputation or prestige were not useful for survival or claiming victory, then they should be

discarded immediately.

When it was time to be shameless, one needed to be resolutely shameless!

“It is time.”

“It is time to join the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance.”

Bright light flickered in Wu Yong’s eyes continuously.

Right when everyone thought poorly of Fang Yuan and felt that he was the weakest among the

three venerables, Wu Yong made a decision that was the opposite of everyone else!

Fang Yuan accepted it without hesitation.

Once news spread, Southern Border’s Gu Immortal world became shocked, the entire five

regions’ Gu Immortal world was shaken.

Fang clan who joined the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance lost their territory and had to

flee. A large number of super forces in the two heavens also left the Heaven and Earth Great

Love Alliance.

In this situation, Wu clan went against the trend and publicly joined the Heaven and Earth Great

Love Alliance, this was a questionable action that drew disdain from others.

Southern Border’s Gu Immortal world was shaken, doubts towards Wu Yong soon rose and

erupted into a storm.

But Wu clan, who was at the center of the storm, stayed united against all resistance, no matter

how they were targeted, they remained unmoving like a monolith, showing no weaknesses at

all.

Back in Western Desert.

“Southern Border’s Wu Yong... I’ve heard of his name long ago, but his courage and foresight

are truly admirable.” Fang Gong said in amazement.

Fang Di Chang nodded: ”I wonder how much benefits he obtained from Fang Yuan by using the

entire Wu clan as the stake to publicly join the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance.”

“Regardless of the results, this is a grand leader with huge ambitions! Wu clan has been

Southern Border’s number one super force for a long time, but they still made such a risky

move. My Fang clan is far inferior to Wu clan to begin with, so how can we not have the same

resolve as them?” Fang Hua Sheng smiled.

“Third supreme elder is right! Our Fang clan has already rested sufficiently, all sorts of resource

points have been transacted for Immortal Gu, Fang An Lei and Fang Chen have also returned

already, and our Immortal Gu Houses have been improved further. It is time to take action!”

Fang Leng shouted with great enthusiasm.

Fang clan lost all their territory, they became a roaming force without a base.

But in this situation, youngsters like Fang Leng grew up and matured rapidly, they became more

proactive and enthusiastic.

Fang Di Chang looked towards the other Gu Immortals as he said: ”What do you think?”

“I think we can make a move now!”

“If we stay cooped up in here, I feel like I will turn rusty soon.”

“We need to show those super forces that bullied our Fang clan that there is a huge price to pay

for provoking us!”

After seeing that their Gu Immortals had high morale, Fang Gong became very happy: ”Good,

we will teach them a lesson that they will never forget!”

The first supreme elder showed a clear attitude, Fang clan’s immortals had shining eyes as their

expressions became even more heated.

Fang Di Chang nodded lightly and tossed out an information path Gu worm which turned into a

map in the air: ”We will target this place.”

The immortals looked and had a change of expressions, they did not think that Fang Di Chang

would make such a decision.

“This is... earthly flame forest?”

“This is Dong clan’s number one resource point! It is tightly defended.”

“Is this too aggressive?”

Fang Di Chang smiled: ”Everyone, listen to me. The earthly flame forest is not made of trees but

flame pillars from underground instead. After reaching a breaking point, they will spew out of the

surface and form into flames that resemble trees. The cause is the fire path dao vein

underground.”

“However, with the unification of five regions, the regional walls vanished and the earth veins

relocated drastically. Thus, that fire path dao vein is also shifting.”

“Earlier, Dong clan set up an immortal formation there using the original location without any

Immortal Gu. Currently, it is at the breaking point, it is like a paper window that can be pierced

with just one strike!”

“And most crucially, the mission board of our alliance has changed. Earth path resource points

are now exchanging for less contribution points while wind path and fire path resource points

have grown in value. Thus, by attacking this spot, we can gain even more contribution points!”

After the Fang clan immortals heard this, they understood that Fang Di Chang had planned this

after much preparation and consideration.

“As expected of Lord Fang Di Chang.” Fang Chen sighed.

“Since second supreme elder has decided upon this, we will trust you!” Fang An Lei expressed

her view.

“Then let us take down this earthly flame forest, hahaha.” Old Ghost Bai Jun was Fang clan’s

slave Gu Immortal, he also showed his stance.

“I can’t wait anymore.” Fang Dong Xi rubbed his palms together.

Although he had revived and retained his rank seven cultivation, his immortal aperture was

empty and needed development.

Earlier, when the Fang clansmen were sold, he had gone to Xiao Ye Hu for a transaction but

found that Wang Xiao Er had been bought already.

As for the other Fang clan members, because of Fang Di Chang’s words, to play it safe for now,

they did not buy them.

Several days later.

Fang clan moved out all at once, successfully assaulting earthly flame forest.

Fang clan had a huge force now while Dong clan had just lost their Red River Wheel.

Dong clan’s first supreme elder did not hesitate, he immediately requested for help from the

other super forces.

After Dong clan gathered many Gu Immortals and several Immortal Gu Houses, they went to

reinforce the resource point but found that it was in a state of ruin and destruction.

Fang clan had not just retreated and vanished into thin air, they even moved the entire

mountain-like area of the earthly flame forest, including the ground itself, into treasure yellow

heaven.

Western Desert’s Gu Immortals were shaken!

The five regions’ Gu Immortals were stunned.

Right when Dong clan’s first supreme elder hesitated on whether to organize a second

anti-Fang alliance, Fang clan struck again and targeted the other super forces’ resource points,

after succeeding, they easily retreated.

The five regions went into an uproar!

Western Desert’s super forces started to become fearful, everyone started to focus on

defending themselves.

Fang Yuan did not make a move on the two heavens’ grotto-heavens from start to finish. But

Southern Border’s Wu clan and Western Desert’s Fang clan had taken action instead, this was

like giving Heavenly Court two slaps across the face, creating two loud sounds that resounded

in the entire world.

Chapter 2274: Beneath the Heavens and Above the Earth, I am the Most Dazzling One in Sight

Heavenly Court.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable let out a breath of air, her face was pale, she felt an intense weakness and fatigue spreading throughout her body.

“I finally created this formation, now, it is time for our human path to develop rapidly.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable looked at the derivation formation in front of her with much joy.

After she refined all the wisdom path dao marks in Heavenly Court, she did not set off immediately, instead, she made use of the time to quickly set up the derivation formation.

Although Star Constellation Immortal Venerable cultivated wisdom path and star path, she was not weak at setting up formations either.

In fact, she was even more formidable than most rank eight formation path experts.

Of course, compared to legendary formation path great experts, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was still unable to compare to them in formation path alone.

Regardless, with the full effort of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, this derivation formation was finally completed!

The core of this formation was rank nine derivation Immortal Gu.

This was a legendary Immortal Gu first recorded in <<The Legends of Ren Zu>>. It was once obtained by Limitless Demon Venerable and used in his Crazed Demon formation as the core.

After the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable took this piece of truthful floating ice that contained derivation Gu.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable used Heavenly Court’s heaven path research results to unseal the truthful floating ice and retrieve derivation Gu.

Afterwards, she used derivation Immortal Gu as the main core to establish this formation around it!

Limitless Demon Venerable used derivation Immortal Gu and the chaos outside the world to derive and create this truthful floating ice that did not belong to this world in essence.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable used the essence of the Crazed Demon formation to create her own derivation formation that was meant to develop human path.

The development of a path usually took over a hundred thousand or even millions of years and the effort of countless geniuses and talents. But using the derivation formation, the path’s development soared like a rocket, it shot up towards the sky with one thrust!

After inspecting the derivation formation, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable checked the various wisdom path killer moves that she used earlier.

These wisdom path killer moves could block detection methods and conceal her derivation formation, and also amplify Heavenly Court’s defenses.

Although the core Immortal Gu of these moves were only rank eight, under the amplification of Heavenly Court’s dao marks, even if the other venerables attacked at full force, they could last for some time.

After everything was done, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable took a rest, this was something that she barely did.

But her immortal essence had been depleted to a great extent, although her immortal aperture was developing, the rank nine immortal essence production could not keep up with her expenditure.

Furthermore, in order to create this rank nine formation, because Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was not a formation path venerable, she had to use up a vast number of thoughts.

Come to speak of it, ever since Star Constellation Immortal Venerable revived, she had not taken a proper rest.

The contest of venerables gave her immense pressure.

After three days passed, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable immediately went to settle Heavenly Court’s affairs.

Heavenly Court’s immortals (and wills) gathered for a discussion again.

Qin Ding Ling came to report everything that had happened in the two heavens.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable gave her some words of encouragement, the two of them, Qin Ding Ling and Jun Shen Guang, had done a great job in recruiting most of the grotto-heaven forces in the two heavens.

As for the mysterious amplification of Qin Ding Ling’s luck path killer move, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable also decided to spend some time to make deductions on it.

Northern Plains had no significant events happening, the demonic cultivators were gathering together under the pressure of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, they were either recruited by the Huang Jin tribes or went to the side of Chu Du, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, and Fairy Black Moon.

As for Wan clan, Fang clan created a commotion and attacked many of Western Desert’s super forces with great success. Western Desert’s righteous path was having a huge headache now, Wan clan and the others were seeking help from Heavenly Court.

In Southern Border, Wu Yong created a commotion. He was already close to Heavenly Court but he suddenly changed attitude and joined the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable rejected the request of sending help to Western Desert’s righteous path, while mobilizing almost all of the Gu Immortals in the Central Continent’s ten great ancient sects to create her star array calculation formation.

Western Desert’s situation was mostly led by Wan Zi Hong and Zhou Xiong Xin.

“Fang clan is just a small problem, how many resource points can Fang clan plunder? In the case of the sovereign immortal aperture, it is too insignificant.”

“The more Fang clan attacks, the more clues they will leave behind. One day, their location will be exposed to us.”

“Western Desert’s righteous path is losing, but that is not the loss of our Central Continent’s Heavenly Court.”

“As for Southern Border’s Wu Yong, let him go. Right now, Heavenly Court cannot send troops out yet. He is ambitious but he is not even a pseudo venerable. How many ambitious Gu Immortals are there in the world? Only more will appear in the future.”

“Right now, the fusion of two heavens has reached the most crucial moment, this is the natural development of the Heavenly Dao. Now that Spectral Soul Demon Venerable has lost his human nature, his actions are dictated by the nature of heaven. I have already deduced that there will be a huge change in the future.”

“Central Continent needs to create the star array calculation formation to prepare for the future, when the Heavenly Dao undergo new changes.”

After Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s words, some Gu Immortals pointed out their doubts: ”The creation of this formation is unprecedented in size and scale, I am worried that if we set it up without any concealment, the other venerables will attack.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable smiled plainly: ”No worries, I have a plan.”

On the same day, Central Continent’s ten great ancient sects sent a large number of Gu Immortals to gather above the sky of Central Continent, they started to place stars and arrange them according to the star array calculation formation.

The number of Gu Immortals involved and the height of their respective cultivation levels was simply unprecedented.

Such a huge commotion immediately drew the attention of the Gu Immortals of the five regions.

It was clear that only Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had the ability to gather such a large number of people.

The Gu Immortals started to guess what ability was contained in this formation that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was trying to build.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had already returned to Longevity Heaven.

His gaze pierced through the ground and into the Blood Sea at the bottom.

It was rumbling with huge waves, at the center of the Blood Sea, there was a huge whirlpool.

“It is finally time.” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable nodded slightly.

This Blood Sea had been hidden in Longevity Heaven all along, it was created by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s clone, Blood Sea Ancestor.

He wanted to create a blood path secluded domain of heaven and earth.

Blood Sea Ancestor left behind countless blood path inheritances, including nine true inheritances. He had naturally left behind the deepest profundities in Longevity Heaven, Blood Sea was one of them.

Initially, this Blood Sea was small and of low quality, but after countless years of nurturing, it had already reached an impressive level.

Before Giant Sun Immortal Venerable revived, he had already started making arrangements for Blood Sea.

Blood Sea was very important for the current Giant Sun Immortal Venerable. Thus, he let his subordinate who had the best Gu refinement ability, Yao Huang, stay here to control the overall situation.

Immortal killer move — Destined Birth Through Luck.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable activated this killer move, by combining the luck path method with Blood Sea, he could revive Gu Immortals!

Under the amplification of Longevity Heaven’s luck path dao marks, golden light radiated heaven and earth, penetrating deep into Blood Sea, every droplet of blood water was dyed golden in color.

Rumble...

Blood waves rose and crashed as thunderous sounds erupted, the huge whirlpool at the center became more rapid and turbulent.

Yao Huang had an exhausted expression, he had been guarding this place and using refinement path methods without rest, he was exerting his full effort without losing his concentration at all.

Right now, he thought to himself with intense anticipation.

“Blood Sea has the power to revive people on its own, while ancestor used his luck path killer move, destined birth through luck. With the combination of both, this Gu Immortal who revives first will definitely be of great help and importance to our Longevity Heaven!”

“Who will this person be?”

Boom!

After reaching a certain limit, the blood waves exploded into a shocking tsunami of great height.

The waves crashed into the huge whirlpool at the center from all directions, filling it up immediately.

Blood Sea became tranquil all of a sudden, it was still turbulent earlier but became clear as a mirror now, the contrast was quite jarring.

Suddenly, a pillar of light shot up from the sea.

Next, more and more lights appeared, over a thousand light pillars pierced through the sea like dozens of sharp swords.

A huge lump of light rose from Blood Sea like a miniature sun.

This light was so dazzling that Yao Huang had to squint his eyes and use a killer move, but he still felt like his eyes were going blind.

“A light path Gu Immortal expert...”

“In history, which person with Huang Jin bloodline fits this description?”

Almost instantly, a name appeared in Yao Huang’s mind.

As the dazzling light faded away, a Gu Immortal stayed floating in the air, he had no hair but his body emitted intense light in all directions, he was like a person made of light.

He pointed towards heaven and earth with both hands respectively as he shouted loudly: ”Beneath the heavens and above the earth, I am the most dazzling one in sight!”

Yao Huang was deeply shocked.

“There’s no mistake, with this tone and temperament, it has to be him.”

“Ancestor’s eldest son, the legendary light path cultivator who left his name in history.”

“Pseudo venerable — Light Emperor!”

At this moment, Light Emperor reacted as he looked at Yao Huang and asked: ”I actually revived, who are you?”

“I am the current generation South Desolation Immortal, Yao Huang.”

“You revived me?”

“I did.” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable spoke.

“Father?!” Light Emperor was shocked, he blinked rapidly: ”Oh, in that case, other than you, my father, in this world, I am the most dazzling!”

“Cough, cough.” Yao Huang interrupted: ”The truth is, Light Emperor, in the current world, there are four venerables in existence, while three are in a deadlock.”

Light Emperor was stunned, he rubbed his chin: ”Oh, in that case, other than the four venerables, I am the most dazzling person!”

“You are not the only pseudo venerable, my son.” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable spoke again.

“Ah, damn it.” Light Emperor rubbed his bald head, he could not frown without any eyebrows, but he still showed a bitter expression: ”This era has many dazzling people. But it is not a problem, I am the Light Emperor after all!”

“You were reborn at an opportune time, I have already checked that your fortuitous encounter is in the immemorial two heavens. Go there, my son.” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s voice gradually became softer as he left.

“Father, don’t leave so hastily. Give me a few Immortal Gu, how else can I shine brightly?” Light Emperor shouted.

“Lord, don’t worry, ancestor has already prepared your Immortal Gu.” Yao Huang said as he flew over and handed him some light path Immortal Gu.

Light Emperor was feeling quite vexed: ”Just these? No wonder father left so quickly. It will be quite hard to dazzle everyone now.”

Chapter 2275: Another Declaration From Fang Yuan!

“To think that Heavenly Court will arrange us to be here.”

“Hmph, where else do you want to be? Inside Heavenly Court?”

“Everyone, it is too late to turn back now. Now that we have joined Heavenly Court, we have no alternative but to obey them. Having internal strife now is very stupid.”

The leaders of the various grotto-heavens like Old Immortal Hua Yu, Liang Jing Jing, and Granny Skeleton gathered together.

Some of their expressions were quite unsightly.

After joining Heavenly Court, even though their grotto-heavens had devoured immemorial nine heavens fragments before, Heavenly Court still had an effective immortal aperture relocation method to use.

But these grotto-heavens suffered immense losses after a forceful relocation.

Furthermore, most of them were now gathered in the two heavens above Central Continent. According to Heavenly Court, their grotto-heavens were arranged in accordance with the star array calculation formation below, they were all treated as formation cores!

“Everyone, have you been well?” Qin Ding Ling smiled and flew towards them.

The Grotto Lords were all expressionless, most of them were even snorting coldly, in the end, Old Immortal Hua Yu and Liang Jing Jing were the ones to greet her.

Qin Ding Ling understood the reason behind the emotions of these rank eight Gu Immortals.

After these people joined Heavenly Court, not only did their grotto-heavens suffer great losses, they were even used by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable as the cores of her star array calculation formation.

This meant that if the three venerables fought in the future, when they try to break into the formation, these grotto-heavens would be at the forefront to deal with such attacks, they could become sacrificial pieces if they were careless.

Qin Ding Ling smiled as she spoke to Old Immortal Hua Yu and Liang Jing Jing, afterwards, her tone turned cold as she chided the rest: ”We’ve already explained it to you. Heavenly Court’s righteousness comes at a price, if not for the fact that we removed your grotto-heavens from the heaven vein nodes, will your homelands still exist now?”

The other immortals’ expressions changed.

Qin Ding Ling had not shown such an attitude when she went to recruit them back then.

But now that she showed her true colors, the Grotto Lords had no choice but to endure it.

As subordinates, they had no choice but to give in now!

Especially for the first batch of Gu Immortals like Granny Skeleton, their grotto-heavens were situated in immemorial black heaven, they were forced by the circumstances to join Heavenly Court like Old Immortal Hua Yu and the rest.

Right now, it seemed that the other variant human grotto-heavens were still left in the immemorial two heavens, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable only destroyed the grotto-heavens in white heaven, he did not do anything to those in black heaven.

Granny Skeleton and others felt very regretful, but at this point, what could they do?

After scolding these Grotto Lords, Qin Ding Ling saw that their expressions became more respectful, she snorted coldly: ”It seems that you’ve already woken up, now, come with me to meet Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was not in Heavenly Court now.

She refined Heavenly Court’s wisdom path dao marks and activated wisdom path methods to conceal the derivation formation, afterwards, she left to refine the natural wisdom path dao marks of Central Continent.

But because of a shortage of immortal essence, and because her immortal aperture could not produce enough essence to keep up with the expenditure, she helped the Central Continent immortals with the arrangement of the star array calculation formation while resting.

Under the lead of Qin Ding Ling, the two heavens’ Grotto Lords met with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable in the sky above Central Continent.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was currently inside Embroidered Tower, she used dao embroidery personally to weave wisdom path and star path dao marks in the surrounding ten thousand li, creating a beautiful work of art.

After the fate war, Reckless Savage Demon Venerable’s method was obtained by Fang Yuan. After Star Constellation Immortal Venerable revived, she quickly modified and changed Embroidered Tower.

Right now, not only was Embroidered Tower complete, it also became more profound and powerful.

After personally seeing Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s incredible method, the Grotto Lords were deeply shaken, they paid their respects.

Seeing them kneel in midair, the Gu Immortals of Central Continent’s ten great ancient sects who were setting up the formation became very enthusiastic and motivated.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable gave them a light gaze, she sensed their complex emotions, there was unease among most of them, some also felt angry and indignant about their predicament.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable consoled them expressionlessly: ”Friends, you are all humans, having been freed from the demonic grasp of Eastern Sea, it is a great victory for humanity. Ever since ancient times, Heavenly Court has been the sacred land of humanity, it is the greatest homeland of everyone. No matter what your ancestors did that caused them to hide in the immemorial two heavens, Heavenly Court will not hold you accountable, let the past remain in the past.”

“Don’t worry, Heavenly Court treats everyone equally, whoever makes contributions will be fairly rewarded by Heavenly Court. In the future, your glory of having joined Heavenly Court will also be passed on to your descendants.”

Old Immortal Hua Yu and the rest were still kneeling, after hearing her words, they expressed their gratitude and praised Heavenly Court’s righteousness, they declared their loyalty and confidence in Heavenly Court.

Eastern Sea.

Fang Yuan looked at the rank nine Immortal Gu recipe of heavenly secret Gu as he let out a breath of turbid air.

This Immortal Gu recipe was very different from before.

Originally, the rank nine Immortal Gu recipe of Heavenly Secret came from the truthful floating ice, it was part of Limitless Demon Venerable’s foundation, he had obtained it from digesting the chaos outside the world.

That was to say, within the Heavenly Dao of this Gu world, there was no rank nine heavenly secret Gu.

In order to pursue eternal life, Limitless Demon Venerable digested the chaos and gained many results that surpassed the current Heavenly Dao. Rank nine heavenly secret Immortal Gu was one of his gains.

This was a great achievement indeed, but there was still room for improvement.

After all, Limitless Demon Venerable died long ago, even though he revived earlier, he was not a refinement path venerable.

In terms of refinement path, Fang Yuan was the number one person throughout history, none of the venerables could match him.

Thus, using his own refinement path attainment, Fang Yuan modified this Immortal Gu recipe to a higher level, it was truly exemplary beyond the limit of the world!

Right now, Fang Yuan had a clear understanding of Heavenly Secret.

This was in essence a heaven path Gu worm, but Fang Yuan had once thought it was wisdom path.

This Immortal Gu was created by Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable, at that time, he already possessed heaven path attainment.

Afterwards, heavenly secret Immortal Gu was refined by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s split soul, Old Man Yan Shi, it was destroyed on Yi Tian Mountain.

Now, heavenly secret Immortal Gu was refined and owned by Fang Yuan, he had refined it using the refinement path killer move heavenly light ring.

By activating heavenly secret Immortal Gu, one could peek into the intention of heaven’s will, it could allow the Gu Immortal to get an answer from heaven and earth. There were no events in the world that heaven and earth did not know of. It was as the saying goes, except you and me, only heaven and earth know. It could expose the secrets of heaven and earth, even if the Gu Immortal did not have any evidences or clues, it could directly lead them to the truth.

But Heavenly Secret had a weakness when using it.

Out of ten activations, at least eight would fail. Once the activation fails, the user would suffer a backlash of ten to seventy years of lifespan.

This weakness was actually created because people did not understand the true essence of heavenly secret Gu.

Heavenly secret Gu was a heaven path Immortal Gu, a heaven path cultivator needed enough heaven path dao marks to be able to activate it normally.

When activating heavenly secret Gu, not only was immortal essence needed, one also had to expend heaven path immortal materials.

This was like Fang Yuan’s obscured heavenly secret.

Without using heaven path immortal materials, heavenly secret Gu could still be activated successfully, but the price was that the amount of heaven path immortal materials needed for the next activation would be much higher.

This was why backlashes occurred that took the Gu cultivator’s lifespan.

Lifespan Gu was a heaven path Gu worm, the lifespan of Gu cultivators were actually heaven path dao marks.

Looking back at it, Old Man Yan Shi did not truly understand heavenly secret Gu.

But this was a normal thing, paths developed over time, the essence of Gu worms was also explored and understood when using them.

Understanding something required a process that took time.

“With this Immortal Gu recipe, I can now advance my heavenly secret Gu.”

Fang Yuan did not lack heaven path immortal materials.

This was due to the unprecedented appearance of abundant heaven path immortal materials when the two heavens fused together.

Shen Shang, who was in charge of collecting heaven path immortal materials, worked very hard.

Earlier, because Fang Yuan wanted his human path cultivation gains but he only gave a portion of it, he felt very uneasy. For the sake of his clan and himself, he had to work very hard as compensation.

“As long as I refine rank nine heavenly secret Gu, the power of obscured heavenly secret will rise sharply, the two venerables will continue to be deceived.”

“But before that, I need to make another declaration.”

Almost all the human grotto-heavens in the two heavens had joined Heavenly Court, while the variant human grotto-heavens that remained in immemorial white heaven were wiped out by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

Regarding this, Fang Yuan had to express himself.

“Fellow cultivators from the five regions and two heavens, I am Great Love Immortal Venerable!”

“Firstly, I want to give my blessings to the human immortals who joined Heavenly Court. Rest assured, I will not pursue the matter. How can I, Great Love Immortal Venerable, do something so petty?”

“Regarding the destruction of the grotto-heavens in immemorial white heaven, I am deeply sorry.”

“Not long ago, I was hit by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s scheme and could not go to deal with Spectral Soul Demon Venerable personally.”

“I have already sent my people to arrange for the retreat of grotto-heavens.”

“No matter what, I believe firmly that this world needs love and peace, war is something that harms all of us. Be it humans or variant humans, or even all life in the world. Why can’t we all live in peace?”

“Because of my beliefs, Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable entrusted his inheritance to me. With such an aspiration, the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance was established.”

“It is not a super force meant for world domination, it is the homeland of everyone, it is an attempt at peace for everyone in this world.”

“Because of the actions of the two heavens’ grotto-heavens, I reflected upon myself.”

“I know that I was wrong, I was too restricted by traditions and the mindset passed down in history.”

“Thus, I have decided!”

“From today onwards, the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance is open to everyone, I will abolish all restrictive agreements, everyone is free to join and leave at any time. I, Great Love Immortal Venerable, make this declaration here and now to heaven and earth, I will not pursue the matter if you leave.”

“Even if you do not join the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance, I will still refine Gu for you, transactions will be done fairly.”

“Members who join my Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance will receive a twenty percent discount for Gu refinement requests!”

“That’s right, twenty percent, a full twenty percent discount, you heard it from me personally!”

“As for how to join the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance?”

“Very simple.”

“You just need to pay a membership fee.”

“In fact, even the fee that you pay will be converted into contribution points in the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance, in the future when you request to refine Gu, you can use these contribution points in place of Gu refinement materials!”

“Oh Liang Jing Jing, I did not take your light heaven out of greed. I have already converted it into contribution points for you.”

“To the human Gu Immortals who have decided to join Heavenly Court instead, I wish you well, you are welcome to join the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance anytime you want.”

“I will not mind your status at all.”

“Remember, the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance promotes freedom, fairness, and peace!”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable: ”...”

The two heaven’s human Gu Immortals: ”...”

Treasure yellow heaven: ”...”

Chapter 2276: Star Constellation, Come Join My Alliance

In the sky above Central Continent, the boundless star array calculation formation could be seen in its initial form.

A large number of Central Continent Gu Immortals were moving around rapidly.

“Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance...” Xiao Suan Zi set up the formation while muttering to himself, thinking hard about the situation.

“Sister Bai Qing, do you think we can join the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance?” Not far away, Rainbow Butterfly Immortal Concubine Han Cai Xin transmitted and asked.

Fairy Bai Qing wore a white gown with a green belt around the waist, she smiled plainly upon hearing this: ”Cai Xin, are you interested?”

“How can I not be? A total of twenty percent discount with no restrictions on entering or leaving the alliance, this is such a huge bargain. If I am not from Spirit Butterfly Valley, I will have joined already. Sister, aren’t you moved?” Han Cai Xin asked.

Han Cai Xin had colorful butterflies flying around her as she placed many Gu worms at their designated locations.

Fairy Bai Qing pondered to herself.

Although she was a Gu Immortal of Spirit Affinity House, she had a close relationship with Han Cai Xin, they called each other sisters in private.

She knew the intention behind Han Cai Xin’s question, it was because Fairy Bai Qing’s daughter was Feng Jin Huang, she was close to Heavenly Court as a result.

But Fairy Bai Qing shook her head: ”I can’t be certain about this, maybe we can ask Friend He Feng Yang.”

In the past, Fairy Bai Qing might state her own opinion, but after Fairy Zi Wei and Feng Jiu Ge’s betrayal, Fairy Bai Qing started to act with caution.

“Little Nine, get to work. After arranging this star path Immortal Gu, we will retreat immediately.” Far away, He Feng Yang secretly transmitted to the nine palace crane.

He had had enough!

After Fang Yuan’s second declaration, everyone knew of the great advantage of joining the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance, most importantly, they could leave at will and there were no restrictions at all.

He Feng Yang became the target of everyone’s inquiry as they assessed him closely.

He Feng Yang was instructed by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to openly hold an Immortal Gu transaction with Fang Yuan.

Forget about what the Heavenly Court members thought of it, currently, the Central Continent’s ten great ancient sects’ Gu Immortals were all moved.

Who did not lack Immortal Gu?

Especially after the five regions became one and the regional walls vanished, qi tides swept the world while heaven veins and earth veins merged, all sorts of immortal materials appeared like a pouring foundation. Among them, earth path, qi tide, and heaven path were most abundant.

The Gu Immortals had a lot of immortal materials, the transactions in treasure yellow heaven also increased in frequency, but Gu Immortals still had few Immortal Gu.

Everyone was specialized in one field, if one was not a refinement path Gu Immortal, their success rate of refining Immortal Gu was just too low.

From ancient times until now, after three million years of human domination, the pain of Gu refinement had never been lifted, countless heroes and geniuses had sank into this bottomless pit of agony throughout their lives.

Only several refinement path great experts could achieve great success, but their radiance could not reach everyone.

Most Gu Immortals were disheartened by their Gu refinement attempts, but they still had to continue trying regardless.

It was a painful but helpless process.

Now, there was a refinement path venerable, he was not like any other Gu Immortal as well.

He was very special.

He created the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance and publicly held transactions in treasure yellow heaven to refine Immortal Gu for others!

This made all the Gu Immortals who were drowning in despair feel hopeful, this was a type of warmth that entered their hearts.

Most Gu Immortals were moved.

No matter how hypocritical Fang Yuan’s Great Love declaration was, the benefits were still presented before everyone.

But the status of the Central Continent’s ten great ancient sects became their restriction.

These Gu Immortals were mindful of Heavenly Court’s attitude.

Thus, they all looked towards He Feng Yang as an indicator.

He was the first person in Central Continent’s righteous path to make a transaction with Fang Yuan openly, rumors said that this was due to the orders of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable!

He Feng Yang had received Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s orders, but how could he tell them?

Some things were allowed under the table, but they could not be spoken about. Once these things were exposed, the meaning would change.

Thus, He Feng Yang had to keep a tight lip.

But the more vague he spoke, the more others wanted to know.

For example, Vicious Lightning Fiend came to ask him personally.

Vicious Lightning Fiend had rank seven cultivation level and was a famous expert. Compared to him, He Feng Yang was just a tiny character, but now, because of his transaction with Fang Yuan, He Feng Yang became renowned in Central Continent, everyone paid attention to him.

Towards Vicious Lightning Fiend, He Feng Yang had to lower his head.

Although he spoke vaguely and hinted about the situation, Vicious Lightning Fiend wanted a definitive answer.

He Feng Yang faced immense pressure.

But right at this time, another Gu Immortal approached him.

It was Immortal Monkey King Shi Lei.

This expert had been rank seven for a long time, it was rumored that he was trying to reach rank eight now.

When Feng Jiu Ge was still part of Central Continent’s righteous path, Immortal Monkey King Shi Lei was merely below him.

“Brother He Feng Yang, tell me straightforwardly, can we or can we not do it?!” Shi Lei asked openly.

With this question, He Feng Yang’s pressure became even heavier.

Fairy Bai Qing and Rainbow Butterfly Immortal Concubine also asked him.

“Fairies, I don’t know either.” He Feng Yang was having a terrible headache.

“Brother He Feng Yang, try asking them.” Vicious Lightning Fiend said.

He Feng Yang was near the point of tears: ”Brother, please understand, I am just a helpless subordinate.”

Vicious Lightning Fiend chuckled: ”You’ve known Fang Yuan for a long time, your relationship is not normal, how can I not know that?”

He Feng Yang felt extremely grieved, he almost wanted to scream: ”I am really not close to this demon!”

He Feng Yang was still trying to find excuses to reply to Vicious Lightning Fiend without offending him when suddenly, Shi Lei directly suggested: ”I have a good idea, brother, join the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance now, I’m sure Star Constellation Immortal Venerable will not punish you.”

He Feng Yang’s eyes rolled white as he felt like he would rather pass out.

While He Feng Yang was in a tight spot, Liang Jing Jing was also facing a tough predicament.

Her divine sense had already entered treasure yellow heaven to communicate with Fang Yuan’s will.

After knowing that light heaven was converted into a large sum of contribution points in the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance, she felt conflicted.

She felt terrible!

This was a huge sum of contribution points, it would hurt her too much to give up on them.

Liang Jing Jing still had two Gu Immortals with her, because Flickering Light grotto-heaven was destroyed, in this situation, she needed cultivation resources badly.

But Heavenly Court would not help her for no reason.

She had to make good use of every cultivation resource, starting all over again.

Thus, the contribution points from giving up light heaven became her greatest temptation.

Liang Jing Jing was not afraid that Fang Yuan would go back on his words.

After all, he had made a public declaration. If Liang Jing Jing decided to join the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance again, Fang Yuan would definitely assure her safety in order to show the world that he was serious.

Liang Jing Jing was afraid of Heavenly Court and the other Gu Immortals in the world.

She had just betrayed Fang Yuan to join Heavenly Court, if she joined the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance again at this time, how would Heavenly Court feel? How would the entire world feel about it?

At this moment, Liang Jing Jing could not deny that she was feeling regretful.

Of course, her hatred and anger towards Fang Yuan was still dominant and had not wavered.

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

Fang Yuan started to officially refine heavenly secret Gu!

This was his third rank nine Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan was very confident in this Gu refinement attempt compared to the previous two.

Because for this Gu refinement session, he had made the most extensive preparation possible.

While refining Gu, Fang Yuan considered the big picture.

Now that he reduced the criteria for joining the alliance, a huge commotion was caused, the influence would only become deeper later on.

“Lord Great Love Immortal Venerable, I am Shang Tao Fan, may I join the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance?” A Southern Border Gu Immortal contacted Fang Yuan’s will in treasure yellow heaven.

Actually, by now, many Gu Immortals had already contacted Fang Yuan’s will, but this was the first person that stated his intention to join.

“You can join after paying a membership fee.” Fang Yuan’s will replied plainly.

A single person’s membership fee and a super force’s membership fee was different.

Shang Tao Fan asked: ”Can I join secretly?”

Fang Yuan’s will nodded in agreement.

“Then I will join the alliance.” Shang Tao Fan replied immediately, he made arrangements with Fang Yuan’s will on where and when to transact the resource point.

Indeed, the membership fees for joining the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance were resource points.

“Shang Tao Fan is a peripheral member of Shang clan, but this time, he was sent by Shang clan as a representative to join my Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance.”

Fang Yuan instantly understood that this was Shang clan’s move.

The resource point that he requested for was beyond Shang Tao Fan’s personal capabilities. But during the talk, he agreed upon it immediately, it was evident that Shang clan was backing him in this.

“Although Shang clan does not have Wu clan’s resolve, they are capable of seeing the big picture regardless.”

Fang Yuan smiled.

This was just the start.

Soon, with Fang clan’s agitation and Wu clan’s lead, more and more super forces would try their luck.

These super forces would likely behave like Shang clan by first sending one member over to make use of the benefits of being a member of the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance.

But this was all within Fang Yuan’s plan.

By giving them some benefits first, when these super forces are no longer to live without him, Fang Yuan would start to restrict the number of Immortal Gu each person could request to refine.

Afterwards, these super forces would send even more Gu Immortals to join him, they might even come to him as a whole!

Of course, Fang Yuan would not restrict them, if they wanted to leave the alliance, they could do so at any time!

While refining the Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan used information path methods to contact Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

“Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, have you been well?” Fang Yuan greeted with a warm attitude.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable quickly replied: ”I’ve been well, but some accusations came towards me from nowhere, Friend Great Love, do you have anything to tell me regarding this?”

Fang Yuan laughed heartily: ”To speak the truth, Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, I am here to lend you a hand. I’ve heard that you are undergoing a huge project recently to create a super immortal formation that covers the entire area of Central Continent.”

“To make such a huge formation, you will need many Immortal Gu. And I, Great Love Immortal Venerable, happen to be specialized in this aspect.”

“Why don’t you join my Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance, you will enjoy a twenty percent discount, that will save you a huge sum.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable laughed.

She was laughing from anger.

Chapter 2277: Spectral Soul Destroys The Sun

2277 Spectral Soul Destroys The Sun

Regarding Fang Yuan's shamelessness, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could only stare in amazement.

She had no choice but to admit that Fang Yuan's second declaration was a brilliant move that dealt with the situation effectively.

Fang Yuan lowered the entry and exit criteria for the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance, he did not consider the loyalty of these members, creating a whole new commotion!

Using benefits to lure them, he displayed the advantage of refinement path, this was something that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable could not match, they had no way of stopping him.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was certain: Right now, all the Gu Immortals in the world were greatly moved, even the Gu Immortals of Central Continent's ten great ancient sects were thinking of whether they could join the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance now!

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could restrain them and not let them join the alliance, but she could not stop them from thinking!

Human minds were fickle!

And in this entire fiasco, what did Fang Yuan lose?

Basically nothing.

In the first place, he had taken in subordinates from Eastern Sea and the two heavens, they had no loyalty towards him.

They had to join him because of the situation, it was not of their own will.

It was unrealistic for Fang Yuan to depend on them if he wanted to attack Central Continent or the other regions. From Qin Ding Ling's success in making these grotto-heaven forces betray him, it showed that none of them had any loyalty to him.

If there was only one venerable in the current world, everyone would be completely at his beck and call. But with the era of four concurrent venerables, as well as the contest of three venerables, these Gu Immortals were able to make a choice.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable snorted coldly.

She knew that Fang Yuan contacted her not to show off or brag about his move.

Fang Yuan's suggestion for Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to join the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance was a joke. He knew that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would not join the alliance and raise his prestige.

Fang Yuan's true goal was to threaten her.

Currently, Central Continent was assembling a formation of an unprecedented scale.

At this crucial moment, if Great Love Immortal Venerable or Giant Sun Immortal Venerable made their move, it could easily cause the formation to crumble and fail.

"Fang Yuan has little immortal essence, he does not want to come to destroy my star array calculation formation, but he does not want me to succeed either, thus, he contacted me."

Fang Yuan had always been showing an anxious attitude, he used various Immortal Gu to exchange for resource points, it seemed like he was trying to raise the foundation of his immortal aperture to increase his immortal essence production.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable made many investigation attempts but similar to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, they could not see the truth that Fang Yuan was concealing.

Thus, all along, she felt that Fang Yuan lacked immortal essence.

This was a deep impression that he imprinted in her.

She was not surprised that Fang Yuan contacted her.

Immediately, she agreed to have a transaction with Fang Yuan, Heavenly Court would pay resource points, Primordial Domain, and immortal materials in exchange for Fang Yuan's refinement of Immortal Gu for them.

The transaction was of a huge scale, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable even emphasized that the transactions would be done in batches, this entire duration would be quite lengthy.

Fang Yuan knew that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was doing this to ensure her formation's safety.

This was something Fang Yuan had expected.

According to the arrangement of this incomplete formation, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was not making an exceptional formation, it was within Fang Yuan's tolerance level.

Fang Yuan gave up on destroying it to obtain a beneficial transaction, this was an assured gain for him.

Especially when he was refining heavenly secret Gu now!

At this juncture, Fang Yuan could not attack abruptly.

But Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not know this.

It was even quite a surprise that she was willing to use Primordial Domain as one of the transaction goods.

Before this, Fang Yuan had always been negotiating with Heavenly Court to buy their Primordial Domain.

a portion of the Primordial Domain now will not allow me to gain any advantage in a short period of 21:32

time."

The Primordial Domain had much greater value to him than Star Constellation Immortal Venerable or Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had never agreed to it, but now, she was willing to give up some of the Primordial Domain to lure Fang Yuan into accepting the transaction.

"It is likely that from Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's perspective, I have not taken the Primordial Domain in treasure yellow heaven because I lack methods to retrieve it. Thus, giving me a portion of the Primordial Domain now will not allow me to gain any advantage in a short period of time."

"To think that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable will be the first person to sell me Primordial Domain, I thought that I would have gotten it first through a blood path transaction with Giant Sun Immortal Venerable!"

While thinking of this, Fang Yuan multi-tasked and contacted Giant Sun Immortal Venerable: "Giant Sun, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable has made such a huge move, the formation she is setting up must be quite important. She is the number one wisdom path cultivator throughout history, with this formation's help, she will be able to scheme in the future without us even knowing it."

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable laughed and quickly replied: "So what do you want to do?"

Fang Yuan said directly: "I am willing to collaborate with you to deal with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and destroy her formation! Wisdom path is not simple, we saw its power in Crazed Demon Cave. We really should not let her create this immortal formation."

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable gave an ambiguous answer: "That is a good suggestion, so, Great Love, have you considered Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's suggestion already?"

Fang Yuan chuckled: "We can always talk about it. I have a lot of blood path research results and also blood path Immortal Gu."

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had always wanted to buy Fang Yuan's blood path resources, now that Fang Yuan gave in, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable smiled and immediately contacted Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

"Heaven Refining Demon Venerable just contacted me, he wants us to attack your formation together. What do you think about that?" Giant Sun Immortal Venerable immediately exposed Fang Yuan.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable snorted coldly to herself, she used a similar method to make a transaction with Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

The three venerables continued to negotiate and plot against each other.

As a wisdom path Gu cultivator, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was superior to the others, she vaguely held the upper hand.

Eventually, she gave up some benefits to temporarily appease Fang Yuan and Giant Sun.

"I finally stabilized these two, but if the formation I am making is any stronger, this situation will be harder to deal with."

It was not that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable lacked a better formation, but she could not create it now.

If she tried, the two venerables would try to destroy it.

There would be no way of talking them out of it.

Star array calculation formation was specially chosen by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable as it did not cross their limits. The two venerables were willing to let her create it in exchange for some personal benefits.

This was the precise control of the situation that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had in this contest of three venerables.

"Of course, the most important thing is still Spectral Soul Demon Venerable." Star Constellation Immortal Venerable thought to herself: "The reason why both venerables are willing to watch on the fence is primarily because of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable."

Compared to Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's formation was nothing outstanding!

The three venerables were paying close attention to Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's actions.

Like what they expected, after getting rid of the white heaven grotto-heavens that Spectral Soul Demon Venerable could sense, he went after the sun!

Within the fused two heavens, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable charged towards the sun like a mountain-like shadowy figure.

This scene was seen through Fang Yuan's investigative method, he pondered: "Back then, I used up white heaven's heavenly spirit, causing Spectral Soul Demon Venerable to be unable to control immemorial white heaven directly. He has only devoured black heaven's heavenly spirit, so he can only devour immemorial white heaven through it all being engulfed by immemorial black heaven!"

"Right now, among the two heavens' grotto-heavens, those from white heaven are basically all destroyed. The heaven vein nodes that are contained within these grotto-heavens have all been destroyed by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable."

"As for Longevity Heaven and Heavenly Court, they have tight defenses that prevent Spectral Soul Demon Venerable from detecting them in his current state."

"Thus, his only target now is the sun!"

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable charged towards the sun, but this attempt was different from before, he shouted and roared with unprecedented determination and killing intent.

However, the closer he got to the sun, the more obstruction he felt from the massive number of fire path and light path dao marks.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's body started to melt like a candle, tiny flames could be seen appearing on his entire body.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable looked at the immemorial two heavens while paying close attention to this situation, he evaluated internally: "The sun has existed since immemorial times, it has vast and boundless power. It is the largest heaven vein node in the entire world, it is also the greatest light vein and fire vein node in the two heavens."

"Even in my previous life, when I was at my strongest, I could not deal with the sun easily. Now that Spectral Soul Demon Venerable has lost his mind, it will be even harder for him to deal with it."

When Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was alive back then, he was invincible in the world, he could naturally destroy the sun.

But doing that had no advantage to him, it was even very harmful to the living beings of the world.

Thus, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not do that.

Eventually, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable charged into the sun, countless black pillar-like arms stretched out and grabbed at it, his colossal body slammed into the sun and caused flames to flicker.

At the same time, he suffered severe injuries.

His body melted rapidly as a vast number of light path and fire path dao marks were carved on him.

All of his accumulated soul path dao marks were rapidly breaking apart!

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's three heads were screaming out in pain, his eyes became filled with anger and hatred.

Following his instincts, he activated a defensive killer move, a layer of eerie light covered his whole body, black smoke gushed out fiercely and resisted the immense power of the sun.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable managed to control the situation for now.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable stayed in Embroidered Tower as she looked out of the window.

"The sun is a congregation of heaven path, light path, and fire path dao marks, it is tangible but not solid. It can be seen as a tribulation that has been ongoing for countless years, it had started accumulating since the start of the world. Thus, even though it is not a chaotic disaster, it is hard to deal with even for a venerable."

"By attacking the sun, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable will likely end up in a bad state alongside it. By then, it will be time to make my move."

"If I can eliminate Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, it will benefit Heavenly Court greatly. By then, I can even give in to the other two venerables to a greater extent."

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable understood when to yield and when not to.

For Heavenly Court, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was a huge threat.

Because Heavenly Court was situated in immemorial white heaven, it was the largest heaven vein node in the world.

It was just that Heavenly Court was concealed by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's wisdom path methods, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable could not detect it.

But right at this moment, there was an abrupt change!

A hill-like beast escaped in fear while carrying a trace of the aura of a rank nine Immortal Gu.

"There is actually a legendary immemorial desolate beast hiding inside the sun? It has a rank nine Immortal Gu?" Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was shook.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's eyes widened: "No, not just one rank nine Immortal Gu, it has another one!"

The three venerables observed closely, the wild rank nine fire Gu within the sun was no longer concealed.

After a few breaths of time, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable arrived at the center of the sun, the remaining tens of arms stretched out and grabbed fire Gu despite the intense flames.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's left head opened its mouth and instantly devoured fire Gu.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable cried out in agony.

His left head was burning like a flame pillar.

Without the support of the two Gu, the sun exploded with a loud sound that spread throughout the entire world.

At this moment, all lifeforms in the world looked up, they had fearful expressions as they witnessed the sun turning into countless lumps of light and fire, breaking up and spreading throughout heaven and earth.

The sun — was destroyed!

Chapter 2278: Pursuing the Rank Nine Immortal Gu

This change had occurred too quickly.

Even the three venerables could not take action in time.

Their original plan was to wait for Spectral Soul Demon Venerable to go down with the sun, until they were both greatly weakened. Because Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was following his instincts now, he would also want to survive naturally. Thus, if he got badly injured, he would escape.

At this time, the three venerables would target the greatly weakened Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

In the contest of three venerables, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was a huge uncertainty. There was still a chance of him regaining his sanity, thus, the three venerables were in agreement that this uncertainty should be killed first.

Like during the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable decided to cooperate to kill all the pseudo venerables first.

But out of their expectations, the sun actually exploded first.

Different from what everyone thought, the sun actually contained two rank nine Immortal Gu and one mysterious legendary immemorial desolate beast.

The sun’s foundation far exceeded their expectations.

With this foundation and the fact that Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was not sane, it should be very hard to deal with, he would be the one to escape first.

But the issue was that the legendary immemorial desolate beast that hid inside the sun got shocked and escaped.

Not only did it run away, it even brought a rank nine Immortal Gu with it.

Once this Immortal Gu was taken, the sun lacked a core and its stable condition quickly destabilized spontaneous.

“No matter how strong a Gu house is, it can still be easily broken from the inside.” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable sighed as she thought of a logic in the Gu world.

This abrupt change disrupted her plan.

Among the three venerables, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was the one who wanted to kill Spectral Soul Demon Venerable the most.

Because she understood the threat that he held towards Heavenly Court!

Originally, she wanted to give in and accept some losses to lure the other two venerables into attacking Spectral Soul Demon Venerable and killing him. But to think that this happened.

Fire Gu was a legendary Immortal Gu recorded in <<The Legends of Ren Zu>>, it was rank nine but got devoured by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

Forget about that for now, but the mysterious legendary immemorial desolate beast also brought away a rank nine Immortal Gu.

It had to be pursued.

A rank nine Immortal Gu was concerned, while a legendary immemorial beast was not hard to deal with for a venerable.

Because it was too easy to succeed, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had to race against time now.

There were three venerables in the world, she did not want the Immortal Gu to end up with the other venerables.

“Be careful, fire is raining down like a storm.” Fairy Bai Qing was the first to alert the others.

“Oh no, what do we do?” Rainbow Butterfly Immortal Concubine looked at the sky and saw countless flames descending, she felt lost and helpless.

These flames were too high ranked.

Bright light glorious ring fire made up most of these flames, this was the heaven flame of the three flames in the world, it was a rank nine fire path immortal material!

One had to be a rank eight fire path great expert at least to deal with it.

But in the sky above Central Continent, there was a colossal immortal formation.

Central Continent’s Gu Immortals wanted to defend the formation so they had to deal with these flames.

“Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, please give us the orders.” Shi Lei shouted loudly.

Star Constellation sighed softly as she left behind her will and some rank nine immortal essence, controlling Embroidered Tower to deal with the situation here.

But her main body had left already, heading for the two heavens.

Eastern Sea.

Fang Yuan was currently using investigative methods to observe the five regions.

“With the collapse of the sun, countless immortal materials are scattered everywhere. Among them, the light path resources are mostly flying around in the two heavens while the fire path resources are scattered onto the five regions.”

“Fire rain is most common in Western Desert while least common in Eastern Sea.”

The reason was simple.

Conflict of dao marks.

In the five regions, Eastern Sea had the most water path dao marks, while Western Desert had the most fire path dao marks. Thus, the fire rain preferred to target Western Desert instead.

“These flames are top tier resources, if they are gathered to a certain size, they can be made into fire path resource points.”

“Especially the bright light glorious ring fire, this rank nine immortal material is extremely rare and barely found anywhere. It is a prime opportunity to gain a huge amount of it now, I need to make use of this.”

Fang Yuan immediately ordered his Gu Immortals to head to various locations to collect the fire path resources.

But regrettably, he had the most water path Gu Immortals and only a few fire path Gu Immortals, not to mention rank eight fire path cultivators.

Regarding this, Fang Yuan used his will in treasure yellow heaven to make an announcement:

“Good news, good news! The Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance is holding an event!”

“Anyone who collects enough fire path immortal materials can exchange them with us for alliance contribution points.”

“If you collect enough alliance contribution points, you will be able to join the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance officially, it will not cost you resource points!”

“After joining the alliance, you will also retain the contribution points from exchanging immortal materials.”

Fang Yuan’s will tossed out a list that wrote the details of each exchange clearly. Bright light glorious ring fire was listed at the top, it could exchange for the most contribution points.

The Gu Immortals of the world heard the announcement and instantly became moved.

Originally, joining the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance required resource points, but now, all they had to do was to collect fire path immortal materials.

For the bulk of the Gu Immortals, the entry requirement fell once again.

Fang Yuan’s will added: ”This event will only last for a short while, the fastest ones will gain the most, once I collect enough fire path immortal materials, this event will end immediately.”

“Fire path immortal material? What a pity, other than the bright light glorious ring fire, if I go to collect the other fire path immortal materials, the gains will be lower than just collecting heaven path immortal materials.” In the two heavens, Shen Shang was busy scavenging for resources.

“Are we not pursuing Fang clan anymore?”

“For what? Let Heavenly Court’s Zhou Xiong Xin do it. Let’s quickly collect these fire path immortal materials, we can use some ourselves while selling the rest to Great Love Immortal Venerable. This opportunity will not knock twice!”

More and more Gu Immortals in Western Desert started to move out.

Southern Border.

Wu Yong led Wu clan’s Gu Immortals as they started to move around with lightning speed.

Benefits tempted everyone, a large number of Gu Immortals in the five regions were mobilized by Fang Yuan as a result.

As for Fang Yuan, he personally headed into the two heavens.

The destruction of the sun also affected his plan. Originally, he wanted to wait for Spectral Soul Demon Venerable and the sun to both get weakened. If his refinement of heavenly secret Gu succeeded in time, he would be able to gain some benefits from Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

But now, he had to refine heavenly secret Gu while keeping up with the facade.

Thus, he had to enter the two heavens and pretend that he was trying to go after the rank nine Immortal Gu.

This was the normal reaction and behavior that he should have.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable were brilliant people, Fang Yuan had to do this to avoid exposing himself.

After the sun was destroyed, the five regions became dim.

Mortal Gu Masters were fearful and shocked while other lifeforms also panicked, the crying and growling of beasts and birds could be heard everywhere.

This was an unprecedented change!

A large scale panic was unavoidable.

Starlight flickered randomly as a legendary immemorial desolate beast charged out while bathed in blood.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was the first to arrive, she waved her hand as the blood and scales that were left in the air gathered in her hands.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable quickly made deductions with her wisdom path immortal killer move.

“This is You Tian Guang?!” She quickly deduced the identity of this legendary immemorial beast, she felt a little shocked.

You Tian Guang and Zuo Ye Hui had once terrorized the five regions, they whipped up a bloody storm. They were extremely crafty, they worked together and whenever a Demon Venerable or Immortal Venerable was alive, they would hide and not show up.

But eventually, Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable brought peace to the world and killed You Tian Guang.

This was recorded in history.

“But You Tian Guang is actually alive, did it fake its death?”

“Could it fake its death in front of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable? Or does that mean... this is part of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable’s arrangement?”

At this moment, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable thought of many things.

The situation had gotten quite mysterious and complex.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable pursued the beast while analyzing to herself.

The more she thought about it, the more she felt that this was Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable’s move!

According to the situation in Crazed Demon Cave, originally, once Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable revived, he would become a heaven path venerable. That would allow him to gain an immense advantage in the two heavens. Especially after he refines all the heaven path dao marks in the two heavens, he would be able to control all the heaven vein nodes.

By then, Heavenly Court and Longevity Heaven would be greatly threatened by him!

The sun was also a heaven vein node.

Back then, Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable intentionally placed You Tian Guang inside the sun as an arrangement for him to capture the sun in the future.

“Thankfully, Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable is dead now. From this aspect, I should thank Fang Yuan instead?” The moment Star Constellation Immortal Venerable thought of Fang Yuan, he appeared before her.

“Friend Star Constellation, we meet again.” Fang Yuan smiled as he greeted.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable snorted coldly internally but she showed a kind smile on her face, her demeanor was extremely elegant.

The two had a warm attitude but their movements did not slow down, instead, they moved even faster.

The two venerables were guarded against each other as they attacked You Tian Guang.

This You Tian Guang had human form, its back was bent and its forearms were long, there was a horn on its head and its body was covered in scales that resembled countless mirrors that reflected light in all directions.

Under the pursuit of both venerables, You Tian Guang actually managed to escape time and again.

“As I expected, You Tian Guang brought away rank nine light Gu! It has not been refined yet, this is still a wild Immortal Gu.” Fang Yuan noticed the peculiarity.

He sighed internally.

Inside sovereign immortal aperture, the refinement of heavenly secret Immortal Gu had reached a crucial moment.

He did not want to go after this rank nine light Gu.

If he obtained it, the two venerables would attack him in a frenzy to try and snatch it.

After all, a rank nine Immortal Gu was able to break the balance between the three venerables!

Nobody wanted this Immortal Gu to end up in another’s hands.

But Fang Yuan had to say what he had to say: ”You Tian Guang, I am best friends with your master Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable. After he died, he gave his inheritance to me but did not have time to tell me about you. Quickly leave with me, I will ensure your safety!”

You Tian Guang coughed out blood while shouting: ”That old bastard Paradise Earth, I was almost beaten to death by him, it took all my effort to hide in the sun to recuperate. I only managed to recover a little after sleeping for so many years. He did this to me, I will definitely not submit to you!”

“That means this is not Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable’s arrangement?” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was slightly stunned, she could sense You Tian Guang’s emotions, it was not lying.

“You Tian Guang was able to escape by faking death in front of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable, it is quite amazing.” Light Emperor who was hiding nearby thought to himself.

He was hiding inside a black cloud, at this moment, he did not want to dazzle anyone.

Chapter 2279: Retaliation of Three Venerables’ Luck

Immortal killer move — Sword Tongue Dragon Soul.

Fang Yuan’s body shook slightly as a hundred evil dragons appeared around him instantly.

The evil dragons danced and paraded, they gathered into a group and encircled You Tian Guang.

He had used this compound killer move before, if he used it against Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, there would be a risk of it getting unraveled or countered. But now, Fang Yuan used it to trap You Tian Guang.

The evil dragons attacked You Tian Guang from all directions, they bit, swung their tails, stabbed with their horns, or used their claws, some even shot out sharp sword qi with their tongues...

In this dangerous situation, You Tian Guang erupted with the strength of a legendary immemorial beast.

It waved its hands and its body moved like lightning, the horn on its head was extremely sharp, in just a whole, three evil dragons were sliced in half.

After a lot of effort, it managed to kill several evil dragons, but dragon souls came out of them to modify the battlefield.

The more evil dragons that died, the more dragon souls that gathered, the battlefield was filled with soul path dao marks that made the dragon souls even stronger!

The situation was increasingly dangerous, You Tian Guang tried to charge out from different directions as it fought a bloody battle, but it could not break free from the evil dragons.

Sensing the danger that its host was in, the wild rank nine light Gu in You Tian Guang’s body burst out with its power again.

A piercing light shone on the entire battlefield, it seemingly tried to escape with You Tian Guang by turning it into a ray of light.

Earlier, when Fang Yuan and Star Constellation chased after You Tian Guang, this was the move that caused them to fail in capturing it multiple times.

But now, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was already prepared.

Starlight specks flew out and surrounded You Tian Guang’s body.

The wild rank nine light Gu burst out with power but the starlight specks suppressed most of its strength, it failed to escape with You Tian Guang but caused it to suffer huge injuries instead.

Rank nine light Gu was a wild Gu, it was not in sync with You Tian Guang, thus, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable found its weakness.

But this was normal.

Even though You Tian Guang and light Gu had been together for a long time, it had spent most of the time sleeping.

Now that it was awake, with just rank eight cultivation level, it could not refine a wild rank nine Immortal Gu.

Back then, even Star Constellation Immortal Venerable who had become venerable spent a hundred years to refine the wild rank nine wisdom Gu.

As for Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, he attempted to refine rank nine love Gu and failed in the end.

You Tian Guang’s blood spewed out like a geyser, it fell into despair.

The enemies were too powerful, it had suffered huge injuries that caused it to become even slower than before.

But it still struggled.

For the meager hope in its heart that wanted to escape, it resisted!

“Don’t come here, don’t come here...” Light Emperor hid in the black cloud and watched as You Tian Guang approached him, he became flustered and anxious.

You Tian Guang coincidentally escape in the direction that led to him.

“Is this my so-called fortuitous encounter?” Light Emperor sudden shook as he recalled Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s words.

He immediately understood that his fortuitous encounter was rank nine light Gu, but...

“Father, this is too much!” Light Emperor glanced at Fang Yuan and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, he did not even dare to look at them for more than a moment in fear that they would notice him.

Light Emperor’s bald head almost wanted to hide in his chest.

All along, his body had been emitting light, but now, he kept the light concealed as only a thin halo was left.

But You Tian Guang still came in his direction at full speed.

At this moment, Light Emperor could feel nothing but hatred towards this huge fortuitous encounter!

He did not know that Fang Yuan was feeling the same.

“The timing is not right. If this happened after I refined heavenly secret Gu, I will be able to use my full strength to capture the wild light Gu!”

Fang Yuan attacked and chased You Tian Guang while secretly refining heavenly secret Gu.

Thankfully, he spent a lot of effort to modify heavenly secret Immortal Gu’s recipe.

Using Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool, and with the help of the hairy man Gu Immortals, heavenly secret Gu’s refinement proceeded without a hitch.

“The following is the most difficult part. But at this time, I need to chase after that rank nine light Gu! Sigh...” Fang Yuan sighed to himself.

He did not feel much attraction to rank nine light Gu.

Rank nine Heavenly secret Gu had far greater value to Fang Yuan than light Gu.

But the situation had progressed to this stage, Fang Yuan had to show that he was determined to take the Immortal Gu for himself.

“Fate Gu has been destroyed, this situation should have been caused by the contest of luck between the other three venerables and myself.” Fang Yuan had a vague comprehension.

Once Fang Yuan refined heavenly secret Gu successfully, his strength would grow immensely, the benefits would not just be limited to obscured heavenly secret, there were other advantages too.

But in that case, Fang Yuan’s advantage would be too huge.

Precisely so, the other three venerables were threatened by Fang Yuan. Although they did not notice it, their luck had already started to retaliate.

The luck of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable mixed together and attacked Fang Yuan in unison.

Precisely so, at the crucial moment of refining heavenly secret Gu, Fang Yuan faced such a huge difficulty and uncertainty.

“In this situation with the existence of four venerables and contest of three venerables, the current timing is a crucial turning point! Sovereign immortal aperture, rank nine Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus, rank nine advance refinement Immortal Gu, my cultivation of refinement path and heaven path, as well as other elements like obscured heavenly secret have given me a huge advantage that is deeply hidden, my luck is comparable to all three of them together.”

This comparison was under the situation where the three venerables did not know the truth. because they canceled out a portion of each other’s luck, this allowed Fang Yuan to match them evenly.

Once the venerables understood the situation and found out the truth, they would cooperate with each other and cause this cancellation to be smaller. By then, their collective luck would surpass Fang Yuan.

“If I get past this difficulty without the three of them finding out the truth, after gaining rank nine heavenly secret Immortal Gu, my luck will be higher than the three of them combined. After a qualitative change, when I refine other rank nine Immortal Gu in the future, I will no longer face such a hurdle.”

After making an analysis, Fang Yuan understood that this was a crucial fight.

If it were to be said that becoming a refinement path venerable was the foundation to resisting the other venerables.

Then after refining rank nine Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus, Fang Yuan shortened the gap between himself and the venerables.

After refining rank nine advance refinement Gu, the gap was shortened even further, it even deepened Fang Yuan’s advantage in refinement path.

And now, if he refined rank nine heavenly secret Gu, it would create the turning point in the contest of three venerables!

Once this crucial point was passed, Fang Yuan would surpass the other venerables, he would have a true advantage against them.

As star fog appeared, You Tian Guang’s path was completely blocked.

Evidently, this was an incomplete battlefield killer move.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable wanted to use this battlefield killer move to trap You Tian Guang and the wild rank nine light Gu before dealing with them.

Fang Yuan had not seen Star Constellation Immortal Venerable use a battlefield killer move before, he was hesitant now.

Should he try to destroy it now?

It was not something that he could not tolerate for Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to obtain the wild rank nine light Gu.

It was very difficult to refine rank nine light Gu, while Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not cultivate light path. After getting it, during the period that she tries to refine it, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s positive luck would fall greatly.

From the perspective of the situation, in order to prevent Fang Yuan from ruining her plan, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would definitely give up more benefits to Fang Yuan.

This was very beneficial to Fang Yuan.

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan activated his killer move.

Immortal killer move — Seven Kills Rainbow!

Metal path’s yellow light, wood path’s jade-green light, water path’s light blue hue, fire path’s red light, earth path’s brown light, wind path’s green radiance, and lightning path’s deep blue light; seven lights from these seven paths mixed together and shot forward in a drill shape towards You Tian Guang.

You Tian Guang immediately sensed fatal danger.

If he was hit by this move, it would definitely perish, alongside the rank nine light Gu in its body.

But Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was guarded against Fang Yuan.

“What are you trying to do?!” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable called out as starlight flew out, forming a veil made of stardust, it was like a wall between heaven and earth, blocking Fang Yuan’s seven kills rainbow.

Fang Yuan’s mind was also running out of thoughts, he had to refine heavenly secret Gu while maintaining his defensive killer moves and movement killer moves. Earlier, he even had to use an offensive killer move like seven kills rainbow forcefully.

Fang Yuan snorted coldly but did not show any weakness: ”Friend Star Constellation, even if you want to get rank nine light Gu, do you think it will be this easy?”

On the outside, Fang Yuan showed an attitude of relentlessness, he was prepared to fight to the end. But the truth was, he had already made up his mind to destroy this wild light Gu, if that failed, so be it if Star Constellation Immortal Venerable got the Gu.

In Fang Yuan’s condition, he could not obtain the Gu even if he tried. The priority was to destroy rank nine light Gu, followed by letting Star Constellation Immortal Venerable have it, the worst case was for Giant Sun Immortal Venerable to get it.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable were not light path Gu cultivators, but if Giant Sun Immortal Venerable got this rank nine light Gu, his own luck would grow explosively.

That was extremely useful for Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, with his attainment in luck path, he would become much stronger.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable sighed: ”Friend Fang Yuan, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable has not arrived yet, are we really going to fight now?”

Fang Yuan smiled coldly: ”Why not? If I wait any further, aren’t you going to obtain the rank nine Immortal Gu already?”

Fang Yuan and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable went into a standoff.

Fang Yuan targeted the incomplete star fog battlefield killer move occasionally, while attacking You Tian Guang and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable respectively at other times.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was worthy of being a wisdom path venerable, her mind was filled with thoughts, she managed to handle all the various aspects and keep her control over the situation.

Although the situation was in a deadlock, it was clearly tilting towards Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

During the contest of the venerables, You Tian Guang had already gotten severely injured, rank nine light Gu tried many attempts to escape with it but Star Constellation Immortal Venerable blocked it each time.

Seeing that the star fog was about to gather into a complete battlefield killer move, Light Emperor could not wait anymore.

“Dazzle them!” He attacked abruptly using his strongest method.

Blinding white light filled the entire battlefield, Light Emperor used all his effort to create a small opening in the star fog.

“Escape, escape, escape!” Light Emperor desperately charged towards the exit, he did not have the energy to care about the rank nine Immortal Gu.

He had waited for a long time before Fang Yuan weakened the star fog battlefield sufficiently without Star Constellation Immortal Venerable having the time to replenish it. Thus, he could make an opening in this battlefield.

If he waited any longer and the star fog battlefield formed completely, he would have no chance of escaping anymore.

Chapter 2280: Fang Yuan Takes A Risk

The appearance of Light Emperor stunned Fang Yuan and Star Constellation.

They did not expect that someone would be able to hide from right under their noses.

“This person has a profound luck path method on him, he must be related to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable!” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s pupils shrunk as the star fog quickly gathered.

Fang Yuan also made his move as he attacked Light Emperor.

Light Emperor’s eyes were staring wide open as he screamed internally: ”What does this have to do with me?! Why are they attacking me, I was just passing by!”

But immediately after, he turned around and saw that wild rank nine light Gu shining in white light, as it came towards him with You Tian Guang.

“I...” Light Emperor wanted to cry, he understood the situation now.

The wild rank nine light Gu had an intense instinct for survival, it stayed with You Tian Guang because this legendary immemorial beast had a lot of light path dao marks that made it have a familiar feeling, there was also the fact that You Tian Guang was not strong enough to refine it.

But in the hands of a venerable, the situation would be different!

Light Emperor opened the only crack in the star fog, he was also a light path cultivator who only had rank eight aura, the wild light Gu naturally came to him as an avenue of survival.

“Father, save me!” At the moment of life and death, Light Emperor shouted loudly.

“Son, don’t worry.” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable flew towards them from afar, he was getting closer rapidly.

Before he arrived, his killer move had already appeared, blocking Fang Yuan’s offensive method.

Fang Yuan did not have enough thoughts now, his offensive methods were not as agile as usual, otherwise, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable would not have such an easy time blocking him.

Of course, this was not strange in the eyes of the two venerables.

In this fight between three venerables, it was understandable for Fang Yuan to save his thoughts in case of emergencies.

After all, they thought that he had the least immortal essence.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable snorted coldly, she had already recognized Light Emperor now, she immediately used the star fog to pursue him and shorten the distance between them.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable activated his killer move again, golden aurora appeared behind Light Emperor and blocked the star fog.

“Could I have escaped on my own? I’m afraid that I would have to use rank nine light Gu’s power to get away from them! Oh father, you almost did me in.”

Light Emperor was a resolute person, thinking of this, he gritted his teeth and turned around, grabbing at You Tian Guang.

“If you don’t want to die, come with me!” Light Emperor shouted as he brought You Tian Guang and the wild light Gu with him, escaping towards Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

You Tian Guang was on the brink of death, it was currently in a stupor and unable to resist as Light Emperor brought it away with him.

Furthermore, because they were both light path cultivators, they were naturally close.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable stomped her feet as her body flew forward like a ray of starlight. Midway, she tossed with her hand, Star Constellation Chessboard flew out.

At the other end, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable approached and opened his immortal aperture’s entrance, Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace flew out.

Star Constellation Chessboard had countless pieces shooting out like a storm.

Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace sent out a wave-like golden aurora that shielded Light Emperor and prevented him from getting killed by those pieces.

But a large number of pieces still moved agilely as they attacked him.

Light Emperor struggled intensely, his expression was malevolent.

Facing Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s attacks, he dodged from side to side, when he could not evade some pieces, he would endure the impact.

Thankfully, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s attack was already weakened by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s golden aurora to a large extent. Light Emperor had pseudo venerable battle strength after all, he only suffered heavy injuries with blood flowing out of his mouth and nose, but his speed remained the same.

“Persevere!” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable shouted, this situation was quite urgent, his son’s life was at stake, he used his full strength as a result.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable gritted her teeth, she felt immense pressure from Giant Sun Immortal Venerable who was using his full strength.

Seeing that Light Emperor was about to escape, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable fought intensely while shouting at Fang Yuan: ”Great Love Immortal Venerable, how long are you going to continue watching?!”

Fang Yuan had only made some moves after Giant Sun Immortal Venerable appeared, he did not use his full strength.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was quite displeased with this.

Fang Yuan holding back meant a huge threat to her.

If Fang Yuan and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable were colluding now in a set up against Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, she could not use her full strength against Giant Sun, otherwise, Fang Yuan would sneak attack her while she was unguarded.

Fang Yuan was feeling quite troubled now.

He had already done his best!

The refinement of heavenly secret Gu had reached the most difficult part, he had to use a lot of thoughts and concentration on it.

Fang Yuan excelled in the defensive aspect of wisdom path, in terms of thought production, he could not match Star Constellation Immortal Venerable. But his compound killer moves had a huge requirement for the number of thoughts.

“Persevere.” Fang Yuan gritted his teeth while urging himself on.

“Giant Sun, take this!” At the same time, Fang Yuan shouted as he flew towards Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Fang Yuan did not use any offensive method, he only adjusted the movement killer move that he had been maintaining.

But simply this small movement made Star Constellation Immortal Venerable let out a sigh of relief, while Giant Sun Immortal Venerable became alerted.

This was because Fang Yuan went away from Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and approached Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, it reduced her wariness towards him.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable also had to save his son from two venerables, he felt immense pressure.

He shouted loudly and activated more trump card killer moves.

For example, this current method — Poor Luck Silver Hook!

Fang Yuan’s pupils contracted as he sensed a killer move approaching, the wind-light-fire-lightning wheels below his feet rotated rapidly as he instantly left the area.

At the next moment, a pure silver curved hook appeared at the spot that he was previously in.

The hook only appeared for a moment before vanishing again.

It was so fast it seemed like an illusion.

Fang Yuan continued to move around like a phantom, he did not stay at the same spot for more than a breath of time.

Meanwhile, the silver hook continued to appear at the spots he went to, only mere moments away from actually hitting him.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was angry that Fang Yuan was still holding back now. He had Cooking Luck Pot’s protection and could resist the silver hook to attack Light Emperor, but he chose to dodge the attacks, which was what Giant Sun Immortal Venerable wanted to see because it made Fang Yuan easier to deal with.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not know about Fang Yuan’s true circumstances after all.

“Giant Sun Immortal Venerable has never used this luck path killer move before, if I get hit by it, my luck will fall greatly. Right now, with the retaliation of all three venerables’ luck, it would be a detrimental blow to me!”

Fang Yuan had a clear observation of the situation.

He could not use offensive methods now because most of his attention was focused on the refinement of heavenly secret Gu.

But the two venerables were hard to deceive, he was having a hard time putting up this show!

Fang Yuan used various methods and overworked his mind, but his thoughts were still falling to a dangerous level.

Heavenly secret Gu’s refinement used too many of his thoughts, while this battle was also quite dangerous.

Fang Yuan did not even want to touch the silver hook.

It was as if he was walking on a tightrope now!

If he was careless, he would fall to a miserable death.

At this time, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable attacked Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, relieving some of the pressure off Fang Yuan.

Light Emperor was already very close to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable wanted to attack him but Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did everything to stop her.

“Fang Yuan!” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable shouted.

“I’ll take a gamble!” Fang Yuan’s eyes shone brightly as he expended nearly all his thoughts to take a risk and activate reverse flow protection seal.

Fang Yuan flew forward with reverse flow protection seal like an eagle diving for its food, he went towards Light Emperor with an explosive sound.

“Father, save me!” Light Emperor was shocked by Fang Yuan’s momentum, he screamed for help.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable endured Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s attacks forcefully and activated a killer move, golden light shot towards Fang Yuan like a huge pillar.

Fang Yuan did not dodge but approached Light Emperor instead.

“Trying to snatch an Immortal Gu in front of me? Die!” Fang Yuan snickered with barely any thoughts left in his mind.

Light Emperor stared with wide eyes in terror, he gritted his teeth as his body turned stiff as a rock.

At the crucial moment, the wild rank nine light Gu burst out with power.

Blinding white light flashed in the entire battlefield.

Fang Yuan was first hit by the white light before the golden pillar landed on him, he crashed towards the ground like a falling meteor.

Thoughts were produced in his mind and used in the Gu refinement, as well as sustaining his defensive killer move, he could not even use them to think.

After a few breaths of time, reverse flow protection seal started to become unstable.

If this move broke now, not only would Fang Yuan suffer huge backlash, the other venerables would also notice his issue!

Fang Yuan was in critical danger now, if the venerables attacked him, he would have no way to resist.

But this was all within Fang Yuan’s plan.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable were fighting over rank nine light Gu, they could not afford to care about Fang Yuan.

With Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s protection, Light Emperor finally arrived at his father’s location.

Because Star Constellation Immortal Venerable attacked furiously, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable suffered considerable injuries, there was already blood flowing out of his mouth.

The two venerables faced off with sharp gazes, they collided in the air, both sides were getting serious.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable gritted his teeth but did not make any rash move.

He wanted to open his immortal aperture’s entrance to put Light Emperor, the fainted You Tian Guang, and wild rank nine light Gu into his rank nine immortal aperture.

But he knew that he could not do something like that now.

As time passed, inside the sovereign immortal aperture, in Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool, the hairy man Gu Immortals were cheering loudly.

The toughest step of refining heavenly secret Gu was over, now, the refinement difficulty fell sharply, it was a smooth journey ahead.

The number of thoughts needed fell as well, Fang Yuan soon had enough thoughts to think.

He immediately realized that he was falling, he stabilized his body and flew towards Giant Sun Immortal Venerable again.

When he saw that Light Emperor was standing beside Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, he became anxious and shouted: ”We cannot let Giant Sun Immortal Venerable get rank nine light Gu! In the worst case, we need to destroy it.”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable snorted coldly, he looked at Fang Yuan with deep killing intent: ”Go ahead and attack, I will make sure you pay a painful price.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was silent.

Fang Yuan hastened the refinement of heavenly secret Immortal Gu while looking at Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, shouting with all his might: ”Star Constellation, this is a rank nine Immortal Gu!”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had a cold expression, she was very unhappy with Fang Yuan: ”If you had used your full strength, would we be in this situation?”

Chapter 2281: Spectral Soul’s Anguished Cry

Fang Yuan’s gaze flickered with uncertainty and his expression was grim: ”I did not expect that light Gu would erupt with an attack that cooperated with the golden pillar so perfectly!”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable smiled smugly: ”My soft gold crashing pillar was designed to counter your reverse flow protection seal, how does it feel?”

Fang Yuan nodded: ”This move can conceal its strength and unleash a mystical collision force on reverse flow protection seal to penetrate the Reverse Flow River, interrupting with the entire operation of the killer move.”

“But it is a pity that this move has not been completed yet. Otherwise, it would not have been resolved by me so easily.”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable nodded, he felt that this was a small pity, he could have given up on Light Emperor to save this killer move for the future to deal with Fang Yuan.

But Giant Sun Immortal Venerable would not do that.

He would rather expose it to save his eldest son.

“I was too rash, to think that a rank nine Immortal Gu would be involved.” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable said to Light Emperor.

“Father, what’s the point of saying that now? We need to find a way to flee! My hairs are all standing on end now!” Light Emperor replied quickly, although he had returned to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s side, the battle was still ongoing, he was very alert.

“Didn’t you create your own light body inheritance, your entire body is covered in light path dao marks, how can you have body hair?” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable asked in a peculiar tone.

Light Emperor rolled his eyes and retorted: ”Father, now is not the time for this! The situation is dire, we need to find a way to escape.”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable suddenly laughed out loud: ”Then we will leave!”

Saying so, he held Light Emperor and You Tian Guang in both hands respectively and rapidly made his move.

“You want to leave? Not so easy!”

“Giant Sun, leave the Immortal Gu behind.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Great Love Immortal Venerable attacked at the same time.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable roared and exchanged blows with the two venerables, even parts of the two heavens broke into fragments.

At the center of the explosion, under the terrifying force of the killer moves, nothing remained.

Even the fused immemorial two heavens was destroyed, turning into an area of void.

At the next moment, the surrounding fragments of the two heavens came rushing in like tidal waves, filling up the void.

Using this chance, a golden path extended over from deep within Northern Plains.

It was Calamity Luck Altar’s strongest method — Luck Changing Golden Light Path!

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable purposely left Calamity Luck Altar in Longevity Heaven along with his own will and rank nine immortal essence.

Thus, using the vast number of Longevity Heaven’s luck path dao marks, the power of luck changing golden light path rose explosively, it extended from Northern Plains to the battlefield.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable brought Light Emperor and You Tian Guang onto this path, their speed rose immensely, they went far away in just a moment.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Great Love Immortal Venerable did not let them off.

But their attacks were negated by each other due to the constant accidents that occurred around the golden path.

Even if a venerable attacked, under the chaotic situation of the fused two heavens, they were not only obstructed by soul beasts, there were black-white overturning clouds too.

This was the power of luck changing golden light path.

Fang Yuan attacked several times but nearly caused accidents to occur during heavenly secret Gu’s refinement!

Fang Yuan had seen the power of luck changing golden light path from long ago, but this time, it was so hard to deal with because of the amplification of Longevity Heaven’s dao marks.

Boom!

Both venerables gave chase into Northern Plains, eventually, they destroyed the luck changing golden light path.

At this moment, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable fell along with Light Emperor and You Tian Guang down, during the entire period of time, he could not find a chance to open his immortal aperture’s entrance.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had been using his full strength to maintain the luck changing golden light path to resist the two venerables’ attacks.

The intensity of the battle was clear with one glance!

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable fully displayed the power of wisdom path, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had no time to do anything else. There was another reason, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not dare to let You Tian Guang into his immortal aperture.

The wild rank nine light Gu was inside You Tian Guang’s body, after sensing Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s rank nine aura, it was feeling very restless.

If Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did anything excessive, light Gu might get agitated and do something unfavorable to him.

Thus, he could only bring Light Emperor and You Tian Guang towards Longevity Heaven.

“Heavenly secret Gu’s refinement is reaching the final few steps.” Fang Yuan was very happy but he showed an anxious expression as he shouted: ”Giant Sun, leave that rank nine Immortal Gu behind! I won’t let you have it.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s eyes showed a firm light, she did not speak but her attacks were getting more intense.

The battle of the three venerables finally got close to Longevity Heaven.

Light Emperor laughed loudly as victory was in sight, he shouted: ”Father is mighty!”

Longevity Heaven’s immortal aperture entrance was open, at the final juncture, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable showed a grim expression, he did not dare to be careless for fear of showing a flaw.

The moment he stepped into the immortal aperture’s entrance, rank nine light Gu sensed something amiss, it suddenly reacted and wanted to escape.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable snorted coldly and used his prepared method to suppress it.

But at this moment, Fang Yuan unleashed his refinement path killer move!

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable used his defensive measure but the refinement path killer move had been prepared by Fang Yuan for a long time, it had incredible power that affected rank nine light Gu.

Crack.

With a soft sound, the surface of light Gu cracked.

“Oh, oh no!” Light Emperor shouted.

But thankfully, light Gu was only injured, it survived and was not destroyed by Fang Yuan’s attack.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable stepped into Longevity Heaven at long last, he looked at Fang Yuan angrily as he asked: ”Heaven Refining Demon Venerable! What an impressive method... what is the name of your move?”

Fang Yuan smiled coldly: ”You have your soft gold crashing pillar, I have my crippled refinement.”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable praised it again before looking at Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, he shut the door and vanished into thin air.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable looked at Fang Yuan with a livid expression, she reprimanded: ”Since you had the killer move crippled refinement all along, why did you not use it earlier? Giant Sun Immortal Venerable succeeded in the end!”

All along, she did not notice that something was off with Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan gritted his teeth, his expression was dark: ”If I had not made deductions during the battle, even that last hit would not have been possible! I managed to injure light Gu, but what about you, Star Constellation?”

“Hmph. If I did not stall for time, could you have achieved that?” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was very unhappy, she did not want to waste time talking to Fang Yuan, she turned around and left.

The entire time, neither of them chose to invade Longevity Heaven.

“Having your own headquarters is really convenient.” Fang Yuan sighed and left.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was heavily injured, but because of Longevity Heaven, he was unbeatable once he returned.

“This is true for Longevity Heaven, Heavenly Court is even more terrifying.” Fang Yuan made deductions from seeing luck changing golden light path’s strength, he could not help but feel a chill.

He did not stay in Northern Plains, he returned to Eastern Sea immediately.

The effect of obscured heavenly secret that he had was greatly expended after this intense battle, barely any was left.

Longevity Heaven.

“Father, how is light Gu?” Light Emperor was very concerned.

“Don’t worry, although Fang Yuan is a refinement path venerable and heavily injured light Gu, I used that opportunity to suppress it as well.” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable coughed and spat out some blood.

“Father, are you okay?” Light Emperor asked.

In his memory, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was so magnificent and strong, he was an invincible existence. But now, he saw that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was tired and battered.

Times were different!

Light Emperor recalled the process and felt dejected. As a pseudo venerable, he was nothing more than a useless tool.

At most, he was the bait that lured light Gu.

In this battle, he was a burden for Giant Sun Immortal Venerable!

“Father, go and heal yourself.” Light Emperor was very worried, he had never seen his father with such serious injuries.

But Giant Sun Immortal Venerable shook his head: ”I need to watch them and make sure they leave Northern Plains, I can’t let them cause destruction or slaughter the Huang Jin tribes.”

Light Emperor was shocked: ”They are grand venerables, how can they act like that?”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable shook his head again: ”Star Constellation Immortal Venerable may not do it, but Fang Yuan is crafty and shameless, I cannot be sure of that. But most importantly, we obtained a rank nine Immortal Gu in this fight, the gains are just too much. You are truly my son.”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s praise made Light Emperor feel more energetic, he patted his chest and assured: ”Father, I will do my best. Cough cough!”

Because he patted himself too hard, he could not help but spit out some blood in response.

The father and son looked at each other with bitter smiles.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable waved his hand: ”You are heavily injured too, go and recuperate. We made the greatest gains this time, we need to rest now and digest our gains. Once our strength rises, we will repay them severalfold.”

Light Emperor hesitated: ”Father, light Gu is injured, what do we do? Even Heavenly Court spent a long time and countless resources to repair fate Gu.”

Speaking of this, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable frowned: ”We’ll talk about it in the future.”

Above Central Continent.

All sorts of fire path immortal materials were gathered by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and sent into Heavenly Court’s treasury.

“The star array calculation formation was not too badly interrupted.” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was pleased about this.

In her case, this battle was too abrupt.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not expend much immortal essence but the gains were plentiful.

“Even though Giant Sun obtained rank nine light Gu, it is an injured Immortal Gu. Giant Sun cultivates luck path and blood path, he cannot use light Gu easily.”

“Rank nine light Gu is not derivation Gu, the latter does not need to be refined but the former needs immortal essence to be used. This will cost Giant Sun a lot of immortal essence.”

“It is possible that Fang Yuan created crippled refinement at the last second, but it is more likely that he did not attack because he lacked immortal essence, because it was too urgent at the end, he exposed the killer move to attempt to destroy light Gu.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable looked towards the two heavens.

Without the sun, both heavens were dark and dim.

Deep within the two heavens, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was covered in fire, he was growling in pain.

This was the price for swallowing rank nine fire Gu!

“This might be a chance.” Starlight flickered in Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s eyes, she was very concerned with Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s situation.

Chapter 2281: Spectral Soul’s Anguished Cry

Fang Yuan’s gaze flickered with uncertainty and his expression was grim: ”I did not expect that light Gu would erupt with an attack that cooperated with the golden pillar so perfectly!”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable smiled smugly: ”My soft gold crashing pillar was designed to counter your reverse flow protection seal, how does it feel?”

Fang Yuan nodded: ”This move can conceal its strength and unleash a mystical collision force on reverse flow protection seal to penetrate the Reverse Flow River, interrupting with the entire operation of the killer move.”

“But it is a pity that this move has not been completed yet. Otherwise, it would not have been resolved by me so easily.”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable nodded, he felt that this was a small pity, he could have given up on Light Emperor to save this killer move for the future to deal with Fang Yuan.

But Giant Sun Immortal Venerable would not do that.

He would rather expose it to save his eldest son.

“I was too rash, to think that a rank nine Immortal Gu would be involved.” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable said to Light Emperor.

“Father, what’s the point of saying that now? We need to find a way to flee! My hairs are all standing on end now!” Light Emperor replied quickly, although he had returned to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s side, the battle was still ongoing, he was very alert.

“Didn’t you create your own light body inheritance, your entire body is covered in light path dao marks, how can you have body hair?” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable asked in a peculiar tone.

Light Emperor rolled his eyes and retorted: ”Father, now is not the time for this! The situation is dire, we need to find a way to escape.”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable suddenly laughed out loud: ”Then we will leave!”

Saying so, he held Light Emperor and You Tian Guang in both hands respectively and rapidly made his move.

“You want to leave? Not so easy!”

“Giant Sun, leave the Immortal Gu behind.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Great Love Immortal Venerable attacked at the same time.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable roared and exchanged blows with the two venerables, even parts of the two heavens broke into fragments.

At the center of the explosion, under the terrifying force of the killer moves, nothing remained.

Even the fused immemorial two heavens was destroyed, turning into an area of void.

At the next moment, the surrounding fragments of the two heavens came rushing in like tidal waves, filling up the void.

Using this chance, a golden path extended over from deep within Northern Plains.

It was Calamity Luck Altar’s strongest method — Luck Changing Golden Light Path!

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable purposely left Calamity Luck Altar in Longevity Heaven along with his own will and rank nine immortal essence.

Thus, using the vast number of Longevity Heaven’s luck path dao marks, the power of luck changing golden light path rose explosively, it extended from Northern Plains to the battlefield.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable brought Light Emperor and You Tian Guang onto this path, their speed rose immensely, they went far away in just a moment.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Great Love Immortal Venerable did not let them off.

But their attacks were negated by each other due to the constant accidents that occurred around the golden path.

Even if a venerable attacked, under the chaotic situation of the fused two heavens, they were not only obstructed by soul beasts, there were black-white overturning clouds too.

This was the power of luck changing golden light path.

Fang Yuan attacked several times but nearly caused accidents to occur during heavenly secret Gu’s refinement!

Fang Yuan had seen the power of luck changing golden light path from long ago, but this time, it was so hard to deal with because of the amplification of Longevity Heaven’s dao marks.

Boom!

Both venerables gave chase into Northern Plains, eventually, they destroyed the luck changing golden light path.

At this moment, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable fell along with Light Emperor and You Tian Guang down, during the entire period of time, he could not find a chance to open his immortal aperture’s entrance.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had been using his full strength to maintain the luck changing golden light path to resist the two venerables’ attacks.

The intensity of the battle was clear with one glance!

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable fully displayed the power of wisdom path, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had no time to do anything else. There was another reason, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not dare to let You Tian Guang into his immortal aperture.

The wild rank nine light Gu was inside You Tian Guang’s body, after sensing Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s rank nine aura, it was feeling very restless.

If Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did anything excessive, light Gu might get agitated and do something unfavorable to him.

Thus, he could only bring Light Emperor and You Tian Guang towards Longevity Heaven.

“Heavenly secret Gu’s refinement is reaching the final few steps.” Fang Yuan was very happy but he showed an anxious expression as he shouted: ”Giant Sun, leave that rank nine Immortal Gu behind! I won’t let you have it.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s eyes showed a firm light, she did not speak but her attacks were getting more intense.

The battle of the three venerables finally got close to Longevity Heaven.

Light Emperor laughed loudly as victory was in sight, he shouted: ”Father is mighty!”

Longevity Heaven’s immortal aperture entrance was open, at the final juncture, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable showed a grim expression, he did not dare to be careless for fear of showing a flaw.

The moment he stepped into the immortal aperture’s entrance, rank nine light Gu sensed something amiss, it suddenly reacted and wanted to escape.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable snorted coldly and used his prepared method to suppress it.

But at this moment, Fang Yuan unleashed his refinement path killer move!

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable used his defensive measure but the refinement path killer move had been prepared by Fang Yuan for a long time, it had incredible power that affected rank nine light Gu.

Crack.

With a soft sound, the surface of light Gu cracked.

“Oh, oh no!” Light Emperor shouted.

But thankfully, light Gu was only injured, it survived and was not destroyed by Fang Yuan’s attack.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable stepped into Longevity Heaven at long last, he looked at Fang Yuan angrily as he asked: ”Heaven Refining Demon Venerable! What an impressive method... what is the name of your move?”

Fang Yuan smiled coldly: ”You have your soft gold crashing pillar, I have my crippled refinement.”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable praised it again before looking at Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, he shut the door and vanished into thin air.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable looked at Fang Yuan with a livid expression, she reprimanded: ”Since you had the killer move crippled refinement all along, why did you not use it earlier? Giant Sun Immortal Venerable succeeded in the end!”

All along, she did not notice that something was off with Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan gritted his teeth, his expression was dark: ”If I had not made deductions during the battle, even that last hit would not have been possible! I managed to injure light Gu, but what about you, Star Constellation?”

“Hmph. If I did not stall for time, could you have achieved that?” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was very unhappy, she did not want to waste time talking to Fang Yuan, she turned around and left.

The entire time, neither of them chose to invade Longevity Heaven.

“Having your own headquarters is really convenient.” Fang Yuan sighed and left.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was heavily injured, but because of Longevity Heaven, he was unbeatable once he returned.

“This is true for Longevity Heaven, Heavenly Court is even more terrifying.” Fang Yuan made deductions from seeing luck changing golden light path’s strength, he could not help but feel a chill.

He did not stay in Northern Plains, he returned to Eastern Sea immediately.

The effect of obscured heavenly secret that he had was greatly expended after this intense battle, barely any was left.

Longevity Heaven.

“Father, how is light Gu?” Light Emperor was very concerned.

“Don’t worry, although Fang Yuan is a refinement path venerable and heavily injured light Gu, I used that opportunity to suppress it as well.” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable coughed and spat out some blood.

“Father, are you okay?” Light Emperor asked.

In his memory, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was so magnificent and strong, he was an invincible existence. But now, he saw that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was tired and battered.

Times were different!

Light Emperor recalled the process and felt dejected. As a pseudo venerable, he was nothing more than a useless tool.

At most, he was the bait that lured light Gu.

In this battle, he was a burden for Giant Sun Immortal Venerable!

“Father, go and heal yourself.” Light Emperor was very worried, he had never seen his father with such serious injuries.

But Giant Sun Immortal Venerable shook his head: ”I need to watch them and make sure they leave Northern Plains, I can’t let them cause destruction or slaughter the Huang Jin tribes.”

Light Emperor was shocked: ”They are grand venerables, how can they act like that?”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable shook his head again: ”Star Constellation Immortal Venerable may not do it, but Fang Yuan is crafty and shameless, I cannot be sure of that. But most importantly, we obtained a rank nine Immortal Gu in this fight, the gains are just too much. You are truly my son.”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s praise made Light Emperor feel more energetic, he patted his chest and assured: ”Father, I will do my best. Cough cough!”

Because he patted himself too hard, he could not help but spit out some blood in response.

The father and son looked at each other with bitter smiles.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable waved his hand: ”You are heavily injured too, go and recuperate. We made the greatest gains this time, we need to rest now and digest our gains. Once our strength rises, we will repay them severalfold.”

Light Emperor hesitated: ”Father, light Gu is injured, what do we do? Even Heavenly Court spent a long time and countless resources to repair fate Gu.”

Speaking of this, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable frowned: ”We’ll talk about it in the future.”

Above Central Continent.

All sorts of fire path immortal materials were gathered by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and sent into Heavenly Court’s treasury.

“The star array calculation formation was not too badly interrupted.” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was pleased about this.

In her case, this battle was too abrupt.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not expend much immortal essence but the gains were plentiful.

“Even though Giant Sun obtained rank nine light Gu, it is an injured Immortal Gu. Giant Sun cultivates luck path and blood path, he cannot use light Gu easily.”

“Rank nine light Gu is not derivation Gu, the latter does not need to be refined but the former needs immortal essence to be used. This will cost Giant Sun a lot of immortal essence.”

“It is possible that Fang Yuan created crippled refinement at the last second, but it is more likely that he did not attack because he lacked immortal essence, because it was too urgent at the end, he exposed the killer move to attempt to destroy light Gu.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable looked towards the two heavens.

Without the sun, both heavens were dark and dim.

Deep within the two heavens, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was covered in fire, he was growling in pain.

This was the price for swallowing rank nine fire Gu!

“This might be a chance.” Starlight flickered in Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s eyes, she was very concerned with Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s situation.

Chapter 2282: Implicating The World

Spectral Soul destroyed the sun, while the three venerables’ fight started and ended abruptly.

The impact of this battle was quickly spreading throughout the five regions.

Southern Border.

“What a large lump of tap fire.” Rank four Gu Master Xiao Yan did his best to dodge.

The lump of orange flame approached him like a rolling stone, it was large as an elephant, attempting to devour him.

Right when Xiao Yan was about to make a move and capture this tap fire, a Gu Master suddenly made an attack!

Boom.

With a loud sound, Xiao Yan was set flying far away.

“Who are you? This is Shang clan’s territory!” Xiao Yan shouted, not only did he fail to get the tap fire, he even suffered injuries.

“Hehehe, are you proud of being a lackey of Shang clan?” From the shadows, a demonic path Gu Master walked out.

He had rank four cultivation level too.

Xiao Yan’s pupils shrunk: ”So it is you, Fiery Star Bao Tong!”

He immediately understood why Bao Tong attacked him, the other party was also a fire path cultivator, he must be after this tap fire.

Boom boom boom!

The two engaged in an intense battle, sparks flew everywhere as explosions resounded.

Initially, both sides were evenly matched, but soon, Xiao Yan gained an upper hand.

Bao Tong became more furious as he fought, Xiao Yan was a junior but he was actually fighting on an even level, in fact, he was even slightly stronger.

This was the benefit of having a large force behind you.

A moment later, Bao Tong fell back while spitting blood, he held his chest and the unsightly expression on his face that was covered in soot could not be concealed: ”So the rumors are not wrong, you actually have so many rank four Gu. You must be the subordinate who climbed into Shang clan leader Shang Xin Ci’s bed?”

Xiao Yan was instantly enraged: ”Scoundrel, you dare to slander my clan leader!”

Xiao Yan had wanted to let Bao Tong off earlier instead of chasing after him, but now, he attacked Bao Tong with intense rage.

Bao Tong cried out in dismay internally, against Xiao Yan’s furious attacks, he had to retreat constantly and quickly fell into danger.

Meanwhile, at a dark corner, there was a Gu Master quietly observing this battle.

This Gu Master had rank five cultivation level, his face and body were unclear, covered by dense fog.

“Shang Xin Ci...” The rank five Gu Master gritted his teeth, it was clear that he had huge grudges with her.

A will was located in his mind: ”Little Tian, don’t be rash. Shang Xin Ci is a Gu Immortal seed of Shang clan, you have only just managed to escape and change your identity. Now, you need to hide yourself and cultivate seriously. You need to transcend the limits of a mortal and become a rank six qi path Gu Immortal!”

The rank five Gu Master was Kong Ri Tian, while the will in his mind was Kong Sheng Tian.

Back then, when Kong Sheng Tian obtained Sheng Tian true inheritance, Wu Ji, Shang Xin Ci, and the rest came to fight over it. He swore to take revenge!

Kong Ri Tian gritted his teeth: ”But ancestor, I already have confidence in ascending. But you told me not to do it because I should not miss the opportunity for natural inspiration?”

Kong Sheng Tian’s will explained: ”Spectral Soul destroyed the sun, he also got rid of many heaven vein nodes in white heaven, like heavenly chasms, heavenly pillars and others. Immemorial white heaven will soon be devoured by immemorial black heaven, the fusion of both heavens will not last long, along with the disturbance of heaven’s will. Once heaven’s will stabilizes, you will undergo immortal ascension.”

“So that’s it, I can’t wait.” Kong Ri Tian chuckled.

At the next moment, he attacked!

“Since I can’t take revenge on Shang Xin Ci, I will target her subordinates, I will kill her sweetheart Xiao Yan first and let her experience some pain.” Killing intent surged in Kong Ri Tian’s mind.

“You!”

“Don’t worry, after I kill Xiao Yan, I will frame it on Bao Tong! I am familiar with this.” Kong Ri Tian secretly moved towards Xiao Yan, because the latter was focused on Bao Tong, he did not sense anything.

“Sigh... you need to settle this quickly!” Kong Sheng Tian’s will sighed helplessly.

That night.

Golden flames burned the entire mountain, countless lifeforms perished in the sea of fire.

The light of the fire illuminated the sky, because it was near Shang Liang Mountain, Shang Xin Ci quickly detected it.

“Oh no, something happened to Xiao Yan, just the tap fire alone cannot produce such power!” Shang Xin Ci’s heart sank, she could not help but feel worried about Xiao Yan.

Even though she only had rank five cultivation level, she had abundant knowledge and knew that this was an immortal material flame just by looking at the light.

Shang Xin Ci did not send any reinforcements to help Xiao Yan, because this involved immortal materials, it was not a mortal matter, Shang clan’s Gu Immortals had to resolve it.

Shang Xin Ci looked at the sky.

Without the sun, the sky was pitch black.

This beautiful and kind woman sighed deeply as she showed a look of worry.

“I wonder how many people are suffering and in pain right now? Even as Shang clan leader, I am still too weak.”

The changes in heaven and earth shook everyone’s hearts.

In Southern Border’s Gu Master world, the demonic path had gotten quite rampant for a certain period. Shang Xin Ci did her best to salvage the situation but against calamities and natural disasters, her effort amounted to futility.

Eastern Sea.

White crane sea area.

Nan Gong Yuan was gathering the crane group.

Far away in the horizon, vast and grand frost energy swept over and caused the surrounding temperature to fall.

White crane sea area was originally owned by Eastern Sea’s lone immortal Qin Bai He.

After Qin Bai He was killed by Fang Yuan, white crane sea area was taken by the closest super force, Nan Gong clan.

Nan Gong clan invested a batch of resources and created the formation, they wanted to develop this place, but to think that the sun was destroyed by Spectral Soul.

Once the sun was destroyed, the temperature of the five regions fell sharply, because white crane sea area was right beside icy sea area, it was quite badly affected.

Recently, icy sea area had already expanded by four times of its original size!

White crane sea area was about to be engulfed by icy sea area.

“The changes in the world have created an unprecedented chaotic era.” Nan Gong Yuan sighed deeply.

Nan Gong clan was doing relatively fine.

Su clan’s light ripple sea fell greatly in value after the destruction of the sun, the entirety of Su clan was busy trying to salvage it now.

Of course, there were super forces who took the chance to gain a huge profit.

For example, Eastern Sea’s Hua clan.

Hua clan’s rank eight Immortal Gu House Green Cloud Spark Warship entered the two heavens to collect a vast amount of cloud path resources, the other Eastern Sea righteous path forces were feeling deep envy.

With the changes going on, not just mortals and Gu Masters were affected, even super forces and Gu Immortal experts were implicated in this commotion.

Some were overjoyed, some were worried, some decided to leave their homelands and start all over again.

In the pitch black night, Lu Qing Ming and Su Guang were flying over the border of Northern Plains and Western Desert.

They were originally the Traveling Three Elites but after Han Dong’s death, only two were left.

The two of them were Northern Plains lone immortals, they did not want to submit to the Huang Jin tribes, they also refused to join Chu Du, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, or Fairy Black Moon.

In the huge Gu cultivation world, everyone had their own intentions.

Some preferred freedom more than others.

As Longevity Heaven exerted more influence, there was less and less survival space for lone cultivators in Northern Plains.

The situation forced Lu Qing Ming and Su Guang to leave Northern Plains.

They were unwilling to go to Central Continent or Eastern Sea, thus, they could only head to Western Desert or Southern Border.

Because Lu Qing Ming cultivated wind path and Su Guang cultivated light path, they were more suited for Western Desert.

“Sigh, we had to leave Northern Plains after all. At this moment, I finally understand the meaning of why it is hard to leave your homeland.” Lu Qing Ming sighed gloomily.

Su Guang had a different opinion: ”Western Desert is chaotic now, with Fang clan drawing everyone’s attention, it is more suitable for us. Let’s go, the five regional walls are gone, the two heavens have fused, the world is our home.”

“Hehe.” Lu Qing Ming laughed: ”You are more carefree than me.”

But at the next moment, their expressions changed.

The terrifying darkness descended!

The two immortals could not put up any resistance, the mysterious expert grabbed and prevented them from moving at all.

Lu Qing Ming and Su Guang were filled with fear.

It was not a Gu Immortal who captured them but a legendary immemorial desolate beast.

This legendary immemorial beast was like a giant, it was blacker than ink. Its black hair flowed like a cape, extending to its waist, its eyes were huge and emitting a fierce red light.

Right now, two of its monstrous claws grabbed onto Lu Qing Ming and Su Guang.

It was Zuo Ye Hui!

Zuo Ye Hui said in a hoarse tone: ”Gu Immortals from Northern Plains, lead the way for me. Tell me, how do I... get inside Longevity Heaven?”

Lu Qing Ming and Su Guang heard this and their faces turned pale white.

Back in Western Desert.

A short battle had already concluded.

Flower petals descended but quickly gathered to form Wan Zi Hong’s body.

She looked at Ling Hu Xu’s vanishing figure as she muttered: ”Ling Hu Xu... very interesting.”

Zhou Xiong Xin had an unsightly expression: ”This Ling Hu Xu deserves death! If he had not used Fang clan’s name to rob various places, why would we have been misled?”

Zhou Xiong Xin wanted to find out where Fang clan was hiding, but to think that he followed the wrong traces.

Ling Hu Xu was a rarely seen theft path Gu Immortal, he had once stole Fang Dong Xi’s soul cores in Sand Heap blessed land.

Evidently, he did not just steal soul cores then, he even had a method to disguise himself as Fang Dong Xi.

While everyone was flustered after Spectral Soul destroyed the sun, he committed crimes everywhere and purposely left clues to frame them on Fang clan.

In the end, Zhou Xiong Xin exposed him.

The pursuit was very short, Ling Hu Xu only had rank seven cultivation level but he used peculiar theft path methods to defy the odds, escaping from the two Heavenly Court rank eight experts!

Above Central Continent.

Many Gu Immortals were focusing their gazes on Gu Immortal Zhang Ji.

Zhang Ji successfully arranged the final Immortal Gu.

“Alright, prepare to activate the formation.”

“Tell the two heavens’ grotto-heavens’ Gu Immortals to be mindful of the formation in their grotto-heavens!”

“Ask the immortals in the formation cores to inspect it again.”

The star array calculation formation was finally activated slowly under the massive arrangement.

One star shone brightly first, followed by the second and third star...

After more than ten breaths of time, countless stars illuminated the sky of Central Continent, a beautiful star map was drawn above the sky.

“The star array calculation formation has finally been completed.”

Li Xiao Bai looked at this as he sighed internally.

Not long ago, Fang Yuan had secretly contacted him.

After Profound Literature grotto-heaven joined Heavenly Court, Li Xiao Bai started to show immense value.

But at the same time, Fang Yuan needed to be very careful.

Li Xiao Bai was his clone, if he was exposed and captured, he would become a huge weakness of Fang Yuan’s!

Chapter 2283: Three Venerables Scheme Against Spectral Soul

In the starry sky, countless stars that resembled a sea floated above Central Continent.

The pale blue light of the stars weaved together to form an illusory view.

If one look at the five regions from above now, Northern Plains, Southern Border, Western Desert, and Eastern Sea would be shrouded in darkness, while the center was shining brightly with specks of light.

Central Continent was a clear contrast from the other regions.

Starlight radiated Central Continent.

Compared to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had a clear understanding of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable in his current condition, she had started to make plans from long ago.

Even Fang Yuan was behind Star Constellation Immortal Venerable in deducing the true condition of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

This was the power of foresight and planning that wisdom path excelled in.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable stayed inside Embroidered Tower.

She was currently multi-tasking, refining Central Continent’s natural wisdom path dao marks, healing herself, controlling the star array calculation formation, and even handling the internal affairs of Heavenly Court.

This was the advantage of wisdom path — an abundance of thoughts!

The star array calculation formation slowly operated normally with no issues.

Although this formation only had basic offensive and defensive abilities that could not even reach pseudo venerable level, it was for this reason that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Great Love Immortal Venerable chose to make a transaction with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable instead of destroying it, obtaining benefits instead.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had a huge desire for blood path related results, while Fang Yuan wanted Primordial Domain.

The star array calculation formation’s main power was to collect information in Central Continent through the wide area that it enveloped, through deductions, they could mobilize Central Continent Gu Immortals to cooperate seamlessly.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was the number one person in wisdom path, in fact, wisdom path was created by her, and now, she was still the number one wisdom path Gu Immortal. Nobody understood wisdom path more than her!

Wisdom path emphasized on control, it researched upon certainty.

Wisdom path had three main elements: thoughts, wills, and emotions.

Thoughts were ever-changing, wills were intense, while emotions interrupted, wisdom path cultivation meant having control over these three aspects!

This was the most basic thing.

Thus, wisdom path cultivators were often calm and composed, they knew how to handle their own state of mind.

On this basis, wisdom path Gu cultivators could handle information by storing them or understanding certain things, this allowed them to control the present.

Going a step further, the wisdom path Gu cultivator would use all sorts of clues and information to deduce certain possibilities according to the rules of heaven and earth or the behavior of people, this gave them control over the future.

This was the essence of wisdom path!

Precisely because of this essence, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was the only person who became one with the Dao among all of the venerables in history.

She fused with heaven’s will and influenced fate Gu, it turned fate into the biggest certainty in the world.

From this aspect, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was unique.

All sorts of information flowed into Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s mind like countless tributaries within the star array calculation formation.

These information included the fundamental structure of the mountains and rivers, weather changes, the arrangements of various Gu cultivation forces, or even the locations of Gu Immortals and their current conditions.

A vast amount of information entered Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s mind like a tidal wave that was entering the boundless sea.

If this was Giant Sun Immortal Venerable or Great Love Immortal Venerable, they would not be able to handle it.

But Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was different.

She cultivated wisdom path and had a huge mind far surpassing the other venerables, she could calmly process all this information with ease.

A faint feeling of joy appeared in Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s heart.

Her control over Central Continent’s situation was rapidly increasing.

The more information that a wisdom path Gu cultivator had, the more advantage they could unleash as a wisdom path cultivator.

Otherwise, why would people say that information path and wisdom path were the most compatible?

“With the star array calculation formation, I can oversee Central Continent at all times, it is like a miniature Heaven Overseeing Tower.”

“Central Continent’s emotions are quite stable, while the ten great ancient sects have higher morale than usual. It seems that they have already seen the situation in the other four regions.”

“But the current star array calculation formation is still at the most foundational stage, it has much room for improvement.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable planned secretly.

For example, in terms of collecting information, the investigative methods were not outstanding.

Not to mention Gu Immortals, even mortal Gu Master experts could keep their own secrets to a certain extent.

In the star array calculation formation, information path Immortal Gu that could store information were rare and needed to be added. The best arrangement would be to directly transplant the Qian Kun Crystal Wall into it.

Or for example, the star array calculation formation’s own deduction, thinking, and deployment abilities also had room for growth.

But this needed a lot of Immortal Gu as well.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable created electric brain Gu, wisdom brain Gu, light brain Gu, and others.

Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable invented a special type of immortal plant — brain melon.

Reckless Savage Demon Venerable had once owned monkey brain Gu, dragon brain Gu, phoenix brain Gu, as well as the brain muscle Gu that could be used alongside strength path methods.

There was also Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s food path research result — brain juice Gu.

These Gu worms were all suitable for the star array calculation formation.

Other than these, the star array calculation formation’s own offensive and defensive capabilities also contained huge potential to get stronger.

“But the current star array calculation formation has already reached the bottom-line of the venerables. If I raise any aspect, they may come to attack it.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable understood the situation well.

Because of external pressure and the fact that it needed many Immortal Gu, the star array calculation formation could only be developed to this extent.

“Next, I need to collate the information of all the Gu Immortals in the Central Continent’s ten great ancient sects. Their lifespan, cultivation level, path, Immortal Gu, killer moves, immortal aperture situations, attainment levels, and others, after processing this information, I will let the star array calculation formation deploy them accordingly.”

“As for the Gu Immortals of the two heavens’ grotto-heavens...”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable decided to slow down.

This could not be rushed.

Probing a Gu Immortal’s information was something that went against the social norm.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable forcefully pushed through this plan, because the ten great ancient sects were subsidiaries of Heavenly Court, it was possible.

Even so, immortals of Central Continent’s ten great ancient sects did not feel comfortable about it, they still concealed some information.

But these were minor issues, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not want to force them.

By forcing them now, she would only lose the support of the people, it was not worth it.

Would Star Constellation Immortal Venerable act so unwise?

After these immortals start gaining benefits, their mindsets would change, they would actively contribute to the star array calculation formation.

After that happened, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would urge the Gu Immortals of the two heavens’ grotto-heavens to contribute their own information to the star array calculation formation.

Now was not the time.

Many super forces of the two heavens’ grotto-heavens had just joined Heavenly Court. If Star Constellation Immortal Venerable forced them, they would become disheartened, the rest of the world would also see the sorry state that they ended up in after joining Heavenly Court.

For the long term situation, it would not benefit Heavenly Court.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable first refined Heavenly Court’s dao marks, she then interfered in Western Desert and interrupted Fang Yuan’s plans, she then created the derivation formation and recruited many of the two heavens’ grotto-heavens, after that, she worked with Fang Yuan to fight against Giant Sun while creating the basic form of the star array calculation formation.

All sorts of measures and countermeasures were used in a stable manner. Now, Heavenly Court was revitalized, it got over the repeated history of failure and had a bright future ahead.

“Giant Sun Immortal Venerable is even more injured than me, he has to recover and refine rank nine light Gu.”

“As for Fang Yuan, he lacks immortal essence, be it refining natural dao marks or the contest between venerables, it will be tough on him.”

“The greatest uncertainty is still Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.”

Thinking of this, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable looked afar again.

In the two heavens, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was bathed in flames, his mountain-like body was melting and regenerating at all times, his three heads were twisted and growling in painful agony.

“Spectral Soul...” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable muttered lightly, intense killing intent rose in her heart.

Eastern Sea.

Fang Yuan shook slightly as intense joy filled his heart, yet, his expression remained the same.

Rank nine heavenly secret Gu was refined!

Ever since the battle over light Gu, Fang Yuan’s refinement of heavenly secret Gu passed the most difficult trial.

After that, Fang Yuan returned to Eastern Sea and did not refine the natural dao marks, he pretended to be storing up immortal essence while secretly refining heavenly secret Immortal Gu.

Just earlier, Fang Yuan finally achieved success, rank nine heavenly secret Gu was created!

It was really rare.

This was the first attempt at refining it but he succeeded.

The main reason was rank nine advance refinement Gu, it helped Fang Yuan greatly. Secondly, heavenly secret Immortal Gu had an amazing recipe that was modified by Fang Yuan, it had reached a certain limit of perfection.

But looking at the overall situation, the difficulty was still quite high.

If Fang Yuan had not taken a risk by staking his life, he could have lost terribly.

Once rank nine heavenly secret Gu was refined, Fang Yuan went on to modify the killer move obscured heavenly secret.

This was not difficult.

Fang Yuan was very confident in succeeding.

He had accumulated a lot of experience when modifying heavenly secret Gu’s recipe, while obscured heavenly secret itself was an amazing killer move, it had a firm foundation.

“I need to find a time to meet with Li Xiao Bai and use rank nine obscured heavenly secret on him. That way, he will be able to stay undercover safely.”

“Maybe I can make use of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable to create a chance?”

Longevity Heaven.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was focusing on healing.

Using the vast number of Longevity Heaven’s luck path dao marks, he slowly refined the star path, wisdom path, and refinement path dao marks on his body.

Even though he gained rank nine light Gu, he felt an even greater sense of urgency now.

“Spectral Soul Demon Venerable devoured the wild rank nine fire Gu, that is an extremely stupid move.”

“He is insane now, there is no way he can refine fire Gu. To save itself, fire Gu will fight desperately inside his body, expending Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s soul path dao marks.”

“Once Spectral Soul Demon Venerable weakens to a certain level, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable and Heaven Refining Demon Venerable will attack, an intense battle will erupt again.”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not use any investigative killer move.

He had to save immortal essence now.

This time, in order to protect Light Emperor and take rank nine light Gu, he consumed a lot of immortal essence in fighting both venerables at once.

If he continued to fight against Spectral Soul Demon Venerable in the upcoming battle, because of his advantage with light Gu, the two venerables might join up to target him.

The fact that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had rank nine light Gu was also quite troublesome.

Chapter 2284: Human Path Breakthrough

Heavenly Court.

Ten rank five Gu Masters carried intense excitement as they arrived at a certain important location deep within Heavenly Court.

They were the ten children of human path.

“This is the derivation formation?” Xiao Qi Xing walked at the front.

Behind him were the other nine, Sun Yuan Hua, Fairy Bi Xia, Gu Ting, Wei Wu Shang, Ying Sheng Ji, Chen Da Jiang, Tang Ru Qi, Sun Yao, and Zhao Shu Ye.

These were the most outstanding Gu Masters of Central Continent’s ten great ancient sects, they were nurtured by Heavenly Court and cultivated within Divine Emperor City’s painting worlds, becoming the rising stars of human path.

They each carried a heavy burden, they were the budding sprouts of Heavenly Court and the venerables’ desire towards human path, integral to the goal of Central Continent’s dominance of the world.

The ten of then looked ahead and saw a vast field of grey-white smoke presented before everyone’s vision.

The light continued to transform continuously, it was slithery like a dragon, fluttering beautifully like a butterfly, standing on the wall, or even tranquil like still water.

“This derivation formation is arranged by Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable personally, it is Heavenly Court’s greatest secret!”

“We are immensely fortunate to be the first batch of Gu Masters allowed to cultivate in this formation.”

“The outcome of black heaven engulfing white heaven is set, heaven’s will is going to become stable again. Soon, we will be able to advance to become human path Gu Immortals.”

“Thus, the derivation formation is our greatest fortuitous encounter before becoming a Gu Immortal, we need to make use of this unparalleled opportunity!”

“That’s right, after entering the formation to cultivate, the relevant memories will be deleted in our minds, after that, who knows when we can come here again.”

The ten children of human path discussed among themselves and arranged the order of which they would enter.

Sun Yuan Hua was the first to enter the derivation formation.

After fifteen minutes, he slowly stumbled out of the constantly changing light.

“How was it, what did you experience in the formation?”

“Are there any gains?”

“Quick, tell us.”

The other nine quickly went to him and asked.

Sun Yuan Hua was still a little dazed now but he soon recovered his senses.

He recalled: ”After I went in, all I saw was vast white fog. I tried stepping in and vaguely saw a human figure so I gave chase.”

“I chased it for a long time, after an unknown distance, more and more human figures appeared in the white fog.”

“There were five or six of them initially, after that, there were fifty or sixty, followed by six hundred or seven hundred. By the time I reacted, I was already inside a vast sea of humans, I was surrounded by people!”

“I wanted to ask them questions but I could not speak. I tried to smile to communicate with them. But in the end, I found that they were all smiling at me too.”

“Their smiles were very fake, it looked like... a painting drawn using lines.”

“Can you imagine? Countless people showed a fake smile at me as they squeezed around me, slowly getting closer and tighter, making me feel suffocated.”

“I tried my best to push them away, but my strength became smaller and smaller.”

“Eventually, I was engulfed by the sea of humans with fake smiles.”

“By the time I regained my senses, I had already stepped out of the formation and saw you guys.”

“At the same time, in the depth of my mind, I found the Immortal Gu recipe of shadow puppet Gu!”

After explaining his encounter, Sun Yuan Hua still showed some fear on his face.

His description was very useful for the others in their preparation.

“Why does it seem like a nightmare?”

“This formation is truly extraordinary.”

“Looking at the situation, it seems that after entering the derivation formation, we will get a human path Immortal Gu recipe?”

“One attempt is not enough for a conclusion, who will go next?”

After the remaining nine discussed for a while and came up with no explanation, the second person was decided, Gu Ting.

Under everyone’s gaze, Gu Ting slowly walked into the light fog.

Several minutes later, Gu Ting walked out of the formation in a daze, it was similar to Sun Yuan Hua’s situation.

But soon, he recovered.

Everyone got around him and listened to his encounter.

Gu Ting’s situation was quite different from Sun Yuan Hua, he did not see any human figures, instead, he felt like he did not even open his eyes.

The only thing he heard was music.

The music created by some instrument constantly played in his mind.

After the tune ended, Gu Ting walked out of the immortal formation.

“I received an Immortal Gu recipe, it is the vital Gu that I had recently swapped to — musician Gu.”

The ten children of human path talked among themselves again.

Shadow puppet Gu and musician Gu were both human path Gu worms, they were also Sun Yuan Hua’s and Gu Ting’s vital Gu.

“That means the reward has something to do with our vital Gu?”

“Or more accurately, the reward is our vital Gu’s Immortal Gu recipe? That is so useful to us!”

“That’s right, we may be able to use the excess tribulation qi during our ascension to refine our vital Immortal Gu!”

The ten children of human path were very excited.

Heavenly Court had arranged for them to cultivate human path.

There was a benefit and demerit in doing so.

The benefit was that a new path had no counter in this world, the more human path developed, the greater its advantage against other paths.

The demerit was that a new path was too young, without the help of predecessors, the ten children of human path had to develop human path step by step on their own.

Although Heavenly Court had the human path killer moves made by the past venerables, they were too high ranked and of utmost secrecy, the ten children of human path had no authority to learn of them.

They understood that it would be extremely hard for them to create human path Immortal Gu recipes on their own. The time, effort, and resources needed were unthinkable.

Even if they could use the opportunity of natural inspiration to ask heaven’s will when undergoing tribulation, they were not guaranteed an Immortal Gu recipe.

They were the pioneers of human path, it was possible that the world itself did not have the corresponding human path Immortal Gu they needed.

However, when the third person, Ying Sheng Ji, left the immortal formation, he did not obtain an Immortal Gu recipe.

“I obtained the rank one to five recipe of a brand new human path Gu, it is called pill refiner.”

Ying Sheng Ji’s vital Gu was doctor Gu, but after entering the formation, he actually obtained a new human path Gu recipe.

Ying Sheng Ji was a little disappointed.

In his case, the immortal ascension was coming soon, without doctor Gu’s Immortal Gu recipe, he would not have a human path Immortal Gu to use for a very long time.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had always been keeping a close eye on the ten children of human path.

“After Sun Yuan Hua entered the formation, his comprehension and understanding of human path resonated with the inheritance of Heavenly Court’s former shadow path Gu Immortal, Immortal Monarch Gu Ying. Thus, he obtained the Immortal Gu recipe of shadow puppet Gu.”

Immortal Monarch Gu Ying was someone who appeared after Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s era.

But after inspecting the historical records, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had a deep impression of him.

Immortal Monarch Gu Ying had stated in his inheritance that although shadow path was just a small branch of dark path now, it had more potential. In fact, shadow path was not just a branch of dark path, it was also part of light path. How could there be shadow without light? Precisely so, if shadow path developed in the future, it could potentially fuse both light path and dark path to become a huge, more powerful path!

“After Gu Ting entered the formation, he resonated with a sound path inheritance and obtained musician Immortal Gu’s recipe.”

“As for Ying Sheng Ji, after entering the formation, because there was no resonance with any Gu Immortal’s inheritance which was skilled at healing, Ruan Dan’s pill path was drawn to him instead and created a result.”

“Pill refiner Gu...”

Different from Ying Sheng Ji, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable felt that his gains were greater than the rest.

Human path was the path that Heavenly Court was trying to develop, while pill path was also a new path.

The result of the clash between these two paths was pill refiner Gu.

It was the fusion of Ying Sheng Ji’s human path research result and the essence of pill path, this was a new accomplishment.

“The Gu recipe of pill refiner Gu consists of rank one to five, after refining them, we can produce a large number of pill refiners. These pill refiners are most skilled at refining pill Gu.”

Most pill Gu were consumable Gu, from the ones that Ruan Dan created, one could see that they were very effective and powerful.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable acutely sensed that if pill refiner Gu was spread widely, it could change the current situation of the Gu Master world, there would be a huge revolution!

After Sun Yuan Hua, Gu Ting, and Ying Sheng Ji, it was Xiao Qi Xing’s turn.

This person was seemingly the leader of the ten children of human path, after getting out of the derivation formation, he obtained the Immortal Gu recipes of soldier Gu and sergeant Gu.

Regrettably, his vital Gu was commander Gu.

Chen Da Jiang was the fifth to enter.

His vital Gu was constable Gu, but he had not gotten its Immortal Gu recipe.

“I obtained the recipe of police gate Gu, from rank one to six. They are one police gate Gu, two police gate Gu, and all the way to six police gate Gu.”

“The police gate Gu are mutually connected, after they are refined, my constable Gu can create constables that are able to travel from one gate to another gate instantly.”

After Chen Da Jiang, Zhao Shu Ye went in.

Her vital Gu was craftsman Gu.

After entering the formation, she resonated with a certain metal path inheritance and obtained the rank six Immortal Gu recipe of blacksmith Gu.

The ten children of human path entered the derivation formation one by one, they all had great gains, but these gains were all different as well.

“No matter what, this derivation formation is too amazing!”

“In just half a day, all thanks to it, the entire world had a huge breakthrough in human path’s development.”

“Star Constellation Immortal Venerable is truly the number one wisdom path expert throughout history.”

The ten children of human path were extremely amazed, their eyes were shining brightly.

They wanted to enter the formation again but were rejected.

It was not that the derivation formation could not, but they themselves had reached a limit.

The essence of the derivation formation was to use the research results of the ten children of human path to clash with the inheritance of past Gu Immortal experts, to attempt deriving new human path research results that had never been possible before.

The ten children of human path had only cultivated for a short time, they were all rank five Gu Masters, their foundation was limited.

All of their current potential had been used up already, even if they went in again, their minds would only be corrupted by the inheritances, preventing them from innovating and creating new ideas, restricting their future development.

They were like young sprouts now, after this injection of essence, they would need to recuperate for a long time. Otherwise, excessive help would ruin their creativity in innovating for human path, their bright futures would become dim and hopeless, with no expectations left for them.

Chapter 2285: Jiu Ge Helps Spectral Soul

Immortal killer move — Obscured Heavenly Secret!

Everything happened stealthily.

Only Fang Yuan knew how much immortal essence was used to activate this rank nine killer move.

Three hundred and sixty rank nine immortal essence beads!

After heavenly secret Gu was raised to rank nine, obscured heavenly secret was also finally modified by Fang Yuan, it became a true rank nine killer move.

Compared to the rank eight obscured heavenly secret, the rank nine version used much more immortal essence and the activation time was lengthened to over ten times of before. In addition, the steps were also six times more complicated, and Fang Yuan needed much more thoughts in the process.

After paying such a price, rank nine obscured heavenly secret also became much more powerful!

It was not a quantitative growth but a qualitative change.

Originally, rank eight obscured heavenly secret killer move could create temporary heaven path dao marks that resembled fishing nets, they were layered over each other in a criss-cross fashion, covering Fang Yuan’s entire body.

It was like how a caterpillar used its threads to create a thick and hard cocoon around itself.

Right now, although the heaven path dao marks were still in a fishing net form, they were more tightly connected and were no longer overlapping, he only had one simple layer around him.

This layer of heaven path dao marks were not temporary dao marks, they had stabilized into a certain constant state.

Fang Yuan understood the reason behind this, after observing closely and using investigative killer moves, he barely managed to detect this layer of the heavenly secret fishing net.

It was in a state of existence and non-existence!

The heavenly secret fishing net immediately made Fang Yuan think of the killer move that Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable left behind, ghostly concealment.

Honestly speaking, the heavenly secret fishing net was still inferior to ghostly concealment. But Fang Yuan could sense that the two had already become similar, they shared a type of special trait.

Ghostly concealment could last for a long time without expending immortal essence.

The heavenly secret fishing net was also the same.

But the heavenly secret fishing net could not compare to ghostly concealment, the reason was that although it could stabilize, it could still be consumed.

As long as the investigative method used on it was strong enough, the heavenly secret fishing net would be expended while resisting it, as long as the expenditure exceeded the natural recovery speed, then the heavenly secret fishing net would start experiencing a deficit, it would be like a sinking ship that got gradually submerged.

Of course, ghostly concealment had such a flaw too, but its recovery speed and durability were much higher than the heavenly secret fishing net.

Naturally, the information of Fang Yuan’s ghostly concealment was already known by his enemies, they had created countermeasures against it.

Thus, ghostly concealment’s actual value was much lower than obscured heavenly secret.

Even though it was more refined than obscured heavenly secret, it was outdated.

Other than the huge boost in power of obscured heavenly secret due to the qualitative change, there was another benefit, the amount of heaven path immortal materials needed to activate it had fallen greatly, by a total of eighty percent!

The reduction in consumption of heaven path immortal materials was very beneficial to Fang Yuan in his attempt to accumulate them.

Heaven path immortal materials were not easy to obtain.

Fang Yuan had only gotten a good opportunity recently when the two heavens were fusing.

In fact, the appearance of so many heaven path immortal materials was also thanks to the senseless Spectral Soul Demon Venerable. This was truly an extremely rare opportunity.

Rank nine heavenly secret Gu and rank nine obscured heavenly secret had many tactical implications to Fang Yuan.

This was an advancement!

If the advancement failed and Fang Yuan got exposed, he would get attacked by the two venerables.

It was clear from how Giant Sun Immortal Venerable got targeted by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable after he took rank nine light Gu.

She was very overbearing and showed a tough stance.

Eventually, she only gave up after Giant Sun Immortal Venerable brought Light Emperor into Longevity Heaven.

If Fang Yuan was exposed, everyone would see that he had two rank nine Immortal Gu!

He did not have an impregnable base like Longevity Heaven or Heavenly Court.

Once Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable cooperated, they would be very terrifying!

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s wisdom path controlled certainty.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s luck path explored uncertainty.

The two were mutually conflicting, but if they worked together, they would complement each other perfectly. With the potential of such coordination, even Fang Yuan could not stop them.

After all, Fang Yuan had not created his own rank nine offensive method.

Even if Fang Yuan could stop them, the external situation of the contest of three venerables would start to emit pressure on him. He did not have enough strength to obliterate Longevity Heaven and Heavenly Court.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could not be taken down, if they deepened their cooperation, it was very likely that they would become a huge hindrance to him.

One could say, if Fang Yuan was exposed, he would fall into an extremely passive state.

But the situation was fine now.

With rank nine obscured heavenly secret, he could stabilize the situation at the critical moment.

The refinement of rank nine heavenly secret Immortal Gu was not hard, but Fang Yuan still had to take a fatal risk to succeed.

He succeeded on his first attempt at refining it, he was quite fortunate.

This was the turning point of the contest of three venerables!

Right now, Fang Yuan’s foundation in heaven path was as such. He had heaven path grandmaster attainment level, various killer moves like heaven envies heroic geniuses, heavenly web protection veil, emotionless heaven and earth, heavenly summary earthly norm, obscured heavenly secret, and others, as well as Immortal Gu like Heavenly Web, Heavenly Secret, Heaven’s Envy, and Heavenly Birth.

He also had the truthful floating ice.

At this point, he had already unsealed over half of the truthful floating ice.

Worth noting was that after becoming a heaven path grandmaster, his speed of unsealing the truthful floating ice also became faster!

This was easily understood.

Fang Yuan’s heaven path attainment level was like a foundation, once it rose, he would be able to understand and comprehend the heaven path profundities within the truthful floating ice at a faster rate.

Back then during the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable obtained the truthful floating ice and unsealed it rapidly, he almost became a heaven path venerable!

“However, my heaven path attainment level only rose to grandmaster after using more than half of the truthful floating ice. It will be too hard for me to reach great grandmaster using the remaining portion.”

The higher the cultivation level, the greater the difference between ranks.

This was the same for attainment level.

If half of the truthful floating ice could help Fang Yuan go from ordinary to grandmaster attainment level, then it would be very hard for the remaining half to elevate Fang Yuan to a great grandmaster.

Regardless, Fang Yuan was satisfied.

The truthful floating ice he gained from Crazed Demon Cave had been extremely useful to Fang Yuan.

Ignoring anything else, just the rank nine heavenly secret Immortal Gu recipe was something that did not originally exist in the world.

Fang Yuan knew clearly.

This Immortal Gu recipe was the research result of over a million years through the Crazed Demon formation that Limitless Demon Venerable created, using the chaos outside the world and rank nine derivation Gu as the core.

The concept was ahead of the entire world.

It was too hard to achieve it on his own.

Fang Yuan’s human path attainment level was not low, he was a grandmaster. But why did he not try to create rank six human path Immortal Gu recipes?

It was too hard.

Such an attempt would expend too much of his time, energy, resources, and manpower. In fact, success was not guaranteed.

In the current world, wild human path Immortal Gu were very rare.

Creating a rank six human path Immortal Gu recipe was making something that did not exist in the world, it was the development of human path beyond its current limit, it was also pushing the current world beyond its current boundary and limit.

Going from zero to one was like going from nothing to something, this process was very difficult.

But from one to two, the process was just quantitative growth, gradual development was possible with much lower difficulty.

Rank six human path Immortal Gu recipes were very hard to create, as for rank nine heavenly secret Immortal Gu’s recipe, the difficulty was countless times higher!

Fang Yuan was almost certain, this rank nine Immortal Gu recipe was the most valuable part of this largest piece of truthful floating ice.

“In the following period, I need to find a chance to meet with Li Xiao Bai and secretly use obscured heavenly secret on him.”

Rank eight obscured heavenly secret could deceive Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, the rank nine version was even better.

Of course, that was under the situation that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not have their own path’s rank nine Immortal Gu.

If there was no opportunity, he would create one.

But it would be hard for the two venerables to not become suspicious.

Fang Yuan looked afar and cast his gaze on Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

Different from Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s intention to kill, Fang Yuan wanted to use Spectral Soul Demon Venerable as his shield to conceal his true actions.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was currently bathed in fire.

Under the threat of survival, rank nine fire Gu erupted with its strongest attack.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable had been tortured for tens of days, he was in a state of distress.

His originally colossal body had already shrunk by thirty percent.

Although his rank nine aura was still domineering, there was already a hint of tiredness.

Only several hundred of his countless thick black arms remained, while one of his three heads was burned to ashes.

However, fire Gu was not longer as powerful as before, its firepower had clearly fallen.

A rank eight Gu Immortal slowly approached Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

“If Spectral Soul Demon Venerable still had his senses, he could definitely capture fire Gu. It is a pity that he has no sanity now, he cannot even isolate the natural essence of the world, otherwise, fire Gu would not have such terrifying power.”

This Gu Immortal had an incredibly deep gaze, he could comprehend a certain profound concept from Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s body.

It was Feng Jiu Ge!

At this moment, a soul beast army was moving a hundred li away.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable seemed to have sensed the soul beast army, his expression was ruthless as he roared and flew to them.

The soul beast army was easily disoriented by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, he opened his mouths and devoured them. In a few breaths of time, he had already eaten over ten thousand soul beasts.

These soul beasts immediately melted into soul path dao marks that were transferred to Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s body.

His injuries healed rapidly, but soon, the fire burned and created new injuries.

“Although Spectral Soul Demon Venerable has the instinct to consume, he was just lucky to have met a soul beast army, prolonging his struggle.”

“Let me lend you a hand in that case.”

Feng Jiu Ge slowly activated his immortal killer move — Destiny Song!

His voice was illusory and deep, it was filled with unique contradiction.

Initially, the song was like a small stream of water in the mountains, flowing slowly. Gradually, the stream turned into flowing lava that expanded the river’s width, in the range of mountains, it sounded like a dragon’s roaring echo.

At the same time, the river of lava on the mountain turned into a raging tide, swish swish swish, ebb and flow, it continued without stopping.

The lava and waves collided, reacting and creating steam that covered the entire sky.

The steam condensed into clouds that wanted to fly towards the high heavens.

Suddenly, lightning struck and thunder roared, the lightning bolts landed on the clouds, the immortals felt like they had fallen from the sky, they felt a sense of hollowness in their hearts.

Phantom or real, high or low, being proud and confident at times, feeling lost and desperate during disasters. Bending one’s back at times, spreading one’s words at times...

Feng Jiu Ge’s expression soon turned pale.

His current destiny song was far stronger than before. In fact, his voice was wondrously beautiful and contained the essence of heaven and earth, clearly, after retrieving the heavenly melody, Feng Jiu Ge had gained a lot of insight.

Destiny song only lasted for over ten breaths of time before Feng Jiu Ge stopped using it and retreated.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was still engulfed in terrifying flames as he growled in pain, it was as if Feng Jiu Ge’s destiny song had no effect.

However, three days later.

The red flames on Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s body went from burning hot to an grey-blue cold.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable quietened down like an injured beast, he finally had time to recuperate.

He did not refine the wild fire Gu, while fire Gu also stopped attacking and resisting him. Inside his body, a certain intricate relationship was formed as they started helping each other!

Puff, huff, puff......

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s breathing became slower as the huge grey-blue fire around him became dimmer, until it was completely gone.

His entire body was like a gravestone, he gave off an endless aura of death accompanied by an icy chill.

Then, at the next moment!

Rumble!

Flames surged and burst out over several thousand li, quickly spreading throughout the area in all directions.

Everywhere it went, living beings crumbled, they broke down and burned into ashes as their soul essence was rapidly absorbed by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, it was as if they were returning to the source.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s injuries healed quickly, his body also started to expand at an observable rate.

Chapter 2286: Derivation’s Immortal Might

The shocking change to Spectral Soul Demon Venerable who was inside the two heavens ruined the plans of the venerables again.

Eastern Sea.

Fang Yuan raised his head and used his investigative killer move.

He saw that the icy flame had covered half of the immemorial two heavens, everywhere it went, all life was extinguished. Even immemorial desolate beasts could not last long.

This was definitely a slaughter.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable benefited greatly from this, his entire body had grown to a hundred times of when he was in Crazed Demon Cave! He had over ten thousand black pillar-like arms now.

His terrifying aura and killing intent permeated the entire heaven.

Although he was motionless in the two heavens, he took the role of the old sun of white heaven, he was now the absolute overlord of the night sky.

“Feng Jiu Ge...” Fang Yuan’s gaze was deep.

He had already found out that the cause of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s huge change was Feng Jiu Ge.

Ever since the fate war, Feng Jiu Ge had betrayed Heavenly Court and gone missing.

To think that the next time he showed up, he did such a shocking thing.

But the suspicious thing to Fang Yuan was that Feng Jiu Ge seemed to still have his pseudo venerable battle strength!

This was the only explanation for how he could quickly affect Spectral Soul Demon Venerable and escape successfully.

Be it Fang Yuan, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, or Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, they could not use their investigative method on Spectral Soul Demon Venerable all the time. This required thoughts and immortal essence.

That was also why Star Constellation Immortal Venerable created the star array calculation formation, it helped her to monitor the whole of Central Continent.

“Destiny song...”

“It is able to allow Spectral Soul Demon Venerable and the wild fire Gu to coexist, achieving harmony. Feng Jiu Ge’s killer move has gotten stronger.”

Fang Yuan was now a refinement path venerable.

In the entire world, aside from the venerables, Feng Jiu Ge was the number one person who deserved Fang Yuan’s attention the most!

This person’s talent was shocking to the world, he was even Feng Jin Huang’s father.

In the five hundred years of Fang Yuan’s previous life, Feng Jiu Ge was plotted against by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable and died while attacking Lang Ya blessed land.

Now that Fang Yuan thought about it, he could see that Spectral Soul Demon Venerable had also paid a lot of attention to Feng Jiu Ge!

Precisely because of this, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable plotted and killed Feng Jiu Ge. Otherwise, during those five hundred years, he would have created his own legend and shone brightly like the stars.

The weird thing was that although Spectral Soul plotted to kill Feng Jiu Ge in that life, currently, Feng Jiu Ge seemed to be helping the former instead!

“So, is the pseudo venerable battle strength that Feng Jiu Ge possesses a result of future self or did he cultivate himself during this period of time?”

Fang Yuan pondered deeply.

This was a crucial question.

If Feng Jiu Ge still had future self killer move, that meant that he still had a close connection to Red Lotus Demon Venerable!

In that case, the person behind Feng Jiu Ge would be Red Lotus Demon Venerable, meaning he was plotting from behind the scenes.

Fang Yuan knew about the relationship between these two.

Back then, after he failed and was reborn, in order to destroy fate Gu, he gave crucial intel to Feng Jiu Ge and allowed him to get his own Red Lotus true inheritance.

Why was Feng Jiu Ge helping Spectral Soul Demon Venerable? There was also Heavenly Court’s attitude towards him that Fang Yuan had to consider now.

Right now, Fang Yuan knew that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had sent Heavenly Court Gu Immortals to hunt down the remnants of Shadow Sect like Fairy Zi Wei. Then, why was Star Constellation Immortal Venerable not going after Feng Jiu Ge? Why did they leave Feng Jin Huang alone, as if they forgot about her?

What was Star Constellation Immortal Venerable planning?

Spring Autumn Cicada could not be used anymore, while Fang Yuan did not know of many secrets and hidden information now.

And because he lacked effective investigative methods that could be used on the venerables, he had to pretend to be weak and only make guesses blindly.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had already healed, after leaving Heavenly Court, she had been refining Central Continent’s wisdom path dao marks these days.

At the same time, she was making deductions.

“Feng Jiu Ge... destiny song...”

“I cultivate wisdom path which controls certainty. Giant Sun Immortal Venerable cultivates luck path which explores uncertainty. This destiny song actually contains both certainty and uncertainty, it involves heaven path and human path!”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable recalled her own experiences, throughout humanity’s history, or even the variant human’s history, in terms of pure talent, Feng Jiu Ge was definitely top ten.

“Feng Jiu Ge met with Fairy Zi Wei and the rest, he might have helped them. Right now, he helped Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, these actions will greatly benefit his destiny song killer move.”

Heavenly Court’s pursuers failed.

They could not bring back Fairy Zi Wei and the rest.

But through the traces left behind, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable managed to deduce many details of the truth.

At this moment, inside Heavenly Court.

Derivation formation was currently in operation.

Che Wei and several other Gu Immortals stood before the formation and waited.

The ten children of human path had left Heavenly Court already, their memories regarding this were deleted.

This was done by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable personally, she did not remove their memories carelessly, she had altered them meticulously.

In the following period, these ten children of human path would have bursts of ’inspiration’ which would allow them to ’create’ the respective Gu recipes.

Fang Yuan was a vigilant person, but Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was even more vigilant when it came to this.

She did the same to anyone who had come into contact with the derivation formation.

In this case, as long as one did not have higher wisdom path attainment than her, they would not be able to gain intel about the derivation formation from the ten children of human path.

The derivation formation was too important to Heavenly Court.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had to think of ways to protect this secret to the best of her abilities!

Ruan Dan flew out from the derivation formation.

Che Wei and the rest quickly went up and asked for the results.

Ruan Dan’s expression soon went back to normal, it was extremely excited: ”Amazing, this derivation formation is too amazing! I obtained over a thousand pill path Gu recipes, among which are a hundred Immortal Gu recipes! I’ve tried to create pill path killer moves for so long without much progress, but now, I obtained more than two hundred killer moves, among which, there are over fifty immortal killer moves!!”

Che Wei and the rest were shook.

Ruan Dan was the first to enter the formation, to think that the gains would be so immense!

Different from the ten children of human path, Ruan Dan was a legendary immemorial desolate beast, it had a long lifespan and countless experiences, its foundation was very deep.

“Friend Ruan Dan, although you created pill path, you do not know much about other paths. With this derivation formation, you can come into contact with the research results of other paths by using pill path as the core. After creating a resonance, countless new results would be derived, thus, your gains were so immense!” Feng Da Qi analyzed.

She was a Gu Immortal of Heavenly Lotus Sect, this time, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had chosen her to become one of the people entering the derivation formation.

Ruan Dan nodded in agreement: ”Fairy Feng is right. For a brand new path like pill path, the first step of development is to popularize it. After many generations of Gu cultivators come into contact and cultivate it, through their various life experiences and perspectives, they will slowly build pill path with their unique ideas.”

“After that, more and more cultivators will emerge, among which, geniuses will create new advancements and breakthrough, obtaining huge research results.”

“But now, the derivation formation has taken the place of all these steps. Using all sorts of exceptional Gu Immortal inheritances, the historical characters are helping us in this development. In just a short period of time, we can accumulate a vast amount of pill path foundation.”

After hearing the analysis, Che Wei and the rest had increasingly heated gazes.

“I will go next.” Che Wei was the second person to enter the formation.

Several days later, he came out.

His gains were as huge as Ruan Dan!

The immortals continued their analysis.

Ruan Dan said: ”Friend Che Wei, although you have only created weapon path for a short time unlike me, you are a purebred human with the strongest spirituality. Therefore, your gains are equal to mine. If you had created this path for a longer time, your gains will even exceed mine.”

Che Wei shook his head in response: ”I do not agree with this conjecture.”

“Any path that reaches grandmaster attainment can learn about any path using their own as a foundation. Through their path, they can mimic the expertise of other paths. For example, one can use fire path Gu worms to create a move with water path abilities.”

“The derivation formation might be a forceful type of mimicry.”

“The vast number of true inheritances stored in the immortal formation were described through Ruan Dan’s pill path and my weapon path. For example, the iron rod Gu recipe that I obtained is the result of converting metal path into weapon path. There is also leather whip Gu which is the resulting derivation by combining transformation path and weapon path.”

Che Wei’s words made the immortals’ understanding of derivation formation deepen again.

It was Feng Da Qi’s turn.

She only had rank seven cultivation level but was Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable’s bloodline descendant.

After entering the formation, she only spent a day and night before getting out.

After returning, she had a smile on her face.

“I’ve obtained painting path research results, next, I will refine painting path Immortal Gu and change my vital Gu to painting path.”

The immortals congratulated her.

The use of the derivation formation was not just to help develop human path, pill path, and weapon path, it could also extract the specific essence of the various paths to create new branches of an existing path.

Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable did not leave any painting path inheritance for his descendants.

But through the derivation formation, Heavenly Court could directly nurture their own painting path Gu Immortals!

Gu are the essence of heaven and earth, man is the spirit of all living beings.

There was no point in discussing the strongest Gu worm, only the strongest Gu Immortal mattered.

The way of Gu involved nurturing, use and refinement, these were all integral.

Limitless Demon Venerable used rank nine derivation Immortal Gu and other cores to create his Crazed Demon formation.

He created the truthful floating ice and tried to utilize his eternal life research results but failed in the end, more than half of the truthful floating ice was lost. The remaining portion was split into three by Fang Yuan and the two venerables.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable used derivation Immortal Gu to create the derivation formation, allowing the various paths to develop rapidly. A vast amount of research results were produced, saving a lot of time and also preventing these results from leaking to the outside world, which was a huge drawback of development.

If Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had such a method, he would not have needed to make his Blood Sea clone distribute blood path inheritances worldwide.

Chapter 2287: Spectral Heaven

For the three venerables, the shocking change to Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was only beneficial to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Longevity Heaven.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable let out a breath of turbid air as he sat cross-legged with a bare upper body.

Muscles could be seen on his strong upper body, his black chest hair gave off a manly aura.

“My injuries have healed.” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable let out a sigh of relief.

If Spectral Soul Demon Venerable continued to fight against fire Gu, the two of them would suffer heavy injuries, causing the venerables to fight over them again.

However, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s injuries were more severe than Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

If he chose not to participate, he would lose the opportunity.

But if he went with such injuries, he would be at a disadvantage.

Not long ago, because of the contest over light Gu, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable face pressure from two venerables. He even had to protect his son Light Emperor, causing him to pay a huge price in the end.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable healed long ago while Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had only just recovered.

Due to Feng Jiu Ge’s action, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable became much stronger, forcing Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Great Love Immortal Venerable to continue observing.

Thus, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable benefited from this.

The feeling was very familiar to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable as it was experienced in his previous life.

He was a luck path cultivator who explored the uncertainty.

The stronger he got, the more advantages these uncertain situations would bring to him.

After preparing for a while, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable activated his luck path investigative killer move.

But this time, he did not inspect the venerables, he checked himself.

After Star Constellation Immortal Venerable refined Heavenly Court’s wisdom path dao marks, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable reduced the number of times he inspected others, he started to focus on himself.

His luck was not good.

“I successfully obtained rank nine light Gu but my luck is still bad. Just what is causing this bad luck?” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable frowned.

“Don’t tell me the reason is because rank nine light Gu does not suit me? Furthermore, it is currently injured and is being nurtured inside Light Emperor’s body?” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable guessed.

Rank nine light Gu was injured after Fang Yuan used his crippled refinement killer move.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not have any method to heal it, but Light Emperor was more specialized in light path, he thought of the only solution to this.

That was to use his light body to refine and nurture it, eventually converting light Gu into his vital Gu, allowing him to make use of it. If this was a normal wild rank nine light Gu, Light Emperor would have no way of refining it.

But light Gu was injured, its will was heavily affected, together with Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s help, Light Emperor saw a chance of success.

This had its flaws.

For a long period of time, Light Emperor would lose all mobility, he even needed assistance in eating and drinking.

Longevity Heaven immediately lost a pseudo venerable battle strength expert.

But Longevity Heaven could not do anything else.

They could not give light Gu to Fang Yuan and ask him to repair it!

This was a rank nine Immortal Gu.

While Fang Yuan was someone with no bottom-line.

Giant Sun and Light Emperor were not stupid enough to ask Fang Yuan for help.

Looking at his poor luck, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable sighed helplessly: ”If I had obtained a rank nine luck path Immortal Gu instead of light Gu, no matter which luck path Gu it is, the situation will be much better now.”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was also very familiar with this situation.

Although many sudden events would often benefit him in the end, most of the time, they were not things that he needed.

After all, this was uncertainty, not certainty.

Currently, if Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had a rank nine luck path Immortal Gu, he would be able to create a rank nine investigative killer move and find out who was his biggest threat.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not have a rank nine luck path Immortal Gu, thus, when he used an investigative killer move amplified by Longevity Heaven’s dao marks, he could only see the general trend of the luck.

The contest of three venerables, the rampage of the senseless Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, the interference of pseudo venerables like Feng Jiu Ge, as well as the possible plotting of other venerables in the background. All of these types of luck intertwined together and prevented Giant Sun Immortal Venerable from seeing the specific details, he could only see a trend.

Rank nine Immortal Gu was very important.

It signified a qualitative change!

No matter how much the amplification of dao marks became, it was only a quantitative boost.

“I may be the person with the most progress among the three venerables. Looking at this luck, it is likely that the other venerables will attack me because of rank nine light Gu. This will cause their luck to collectively suppress mine.”

“Of course, there is another possibility — someone surpassed me! I’ve already lost my advantage. But if that is the case, who is the one hiding so deeply?”

Like what Fang Yuan did when he thought about Feng Jiu Ge and Heavenly Court, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable could only make a guess, he could not see the truth immediately.

Now, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had to leave Longevity Heaven and continue to refine Northern Plains’ dao marks.

After thoroughly refining Northern Plains’ luck path dao marks, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable would expand his base from Longevity Heaven to the entire Northern Plains.

There were many benefits in this.

For example, if Giant Sun Immortal Venerable got attacked by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Great Love Immortal Venerable again.

He would not need to escape to Longevity Heaven, as long as he was inside Northern Plains, he would receive the amplification of power.

Naturally, the amplification would be weaker than being in Longevity Heaven, but it would be enough to resist two venerables.

At the same time, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s control over Northern Plains would increase, he would be able to specially nurture Gu Immortal descendants. He would not need to worry about a certain shameless venerable who could slaughter the Huang Jin tribes while disregarding his status, who Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not have a good way to stop.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable understood that as time dragged on, the venerables would continue to get stronger, and as they progressed, the immortal essence storage would also become more abundant.

At the initial stage of development, the venerables lacked immortal essence. At this time, it would be the best opportunity to refine the natural dao marks of the world.

If he missed this opportunity, it would get tougher.

If one was interrupted when refining natural dao marks, their progress would be very small.

If other venerables took the lead, it would be even worse.

For example, if Star Constellation Immortal Venerable first refined the wisdom path dao marks of an area, then her strength would be much higher there.

By then, if Giant Sun Immortal Venerable wanted to refine the luck path dao marks of that area and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable attacks, his best option would be to retreat.

Excluding the senseless Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, among the three venerables, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had the clearest advantage.

He had refined the most luck path dao marks.

Once he refined all of Northern Plains’ luck path dao marks, he would not allow the other venerables to attempt the refinement here.

Be it Star Constellation Immortal Venerable who would want to refine Northern Plains’ wisdom path dao marks or Fang Yuan who would want to refine Northern Plains’ refinement path dao marks, they would have to face Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s all-out retaliation!

Thus, now was the best timing to refine natural dao marks.

After some time, the difficulty would rise greatly.

Other than this reason, there was another crucial secret that forced the venerables to quickly refine these dao marks.

That was, one had to completely refine all the natural dao marks in the world to maintain their supreme grandmaster attainment level!

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable emitted a cold flame and slaughtered the lifeforms of the two heavens while the three venerables refined their respective natural dao marks, the five regions’ Gu Immortal world experienced temporary peace for the moment.

Countless beast groups were escaping from the fused two heavens, landing in the five regions.

The super forces of the five regions were extremely busy, they had to move out to defend their territories.

As most of the beast groups were killed by the icy flame, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s body continued to expand as his aura surged like the boundless sea.

Some time later, his icy flame covered the entire two heavens.

As the three venerables and countless lifeforms of the five regions watched, the blue fire burned for two days and night.

The white heaven and black heaven fragments in the fused two heavens melted and joined together in this blue fire, becoming one entity.

A new heaven had appeared!

People named it — spectral heaven.

With immemorial black heaven as the foundation and white heaven being completely conquered and absorbed, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable who had devoured black heaven’s heavenly spirit became the ruler of the new heaven.

His body was colossal, on par with the previous sun.

As the blue fire slowly extinguished in spectral heaven, only Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s body was left burning, even the smallest spark of fire on his body was tens of feet tall.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable became the greatest source of light in spectral heaven, he emitted a cold and chilly killing intent at all times, spreading his aura to the five regions.

This was an unprecedented change!

Even in the five hundred years of his previous life, Fang Yuan did not see such a phenomenon.

The entire Gu cultivation world’s environment was slowly changed by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

Light path was suppressed while dark path was amplified.

Conflicts and deaths arose all around the world, most lifeforms including Gu Masters could not avoid the influence of the immense killing intent.

Soul beasts started to appear all over the world.

At the same time, heaven’s will also stabilized.

Eastern Sea.

A rank five female Gu Master looked at spectral heaven and the majestic figure at the center of it.

She looked for a while before quickly lowering her head, retracting her gaze entirely.

In just this short time, the killing intent in her heart accumulated to her limit, almost exceeding her endurance. If the killing intent overwhelmed her, she would need to perform a massacre to calm down.

The female Gu Master was very old, she was ninety-three years old. Her name was Hua Ben Ku, she had just passed down the role of clan leader in Eastern Sea’s Hua clan.

She stared at Spectral Soul Demon Venerable intentionally.

After the killing intent dissipated, she started the greatest attempt of her life.

Immortal ascension!

First step, breaking the aperture.

Heaven and earth qi surged and formed grand calamities and tribulations.

Hua Ben Ku had a solemn expression, although she had the information provided by Hua clan, facing the calamities and tribulations now, she was still shook internally.

Second step, taking in qi.

Heaven, earth, and human qi surrounded Hua Ben Ku as she focused to try and balance all three qi.

At the same time, natural inspiration occurred!

Regarding the external calamities and tribulations, Hua clan’s Gu Immortals took action to defend her.

This was the benefit of being a super force.

Third step, putting in the Gu.

Her vital Gu was placed into the lump of three qi as an explosion occurred, creating a new small world!

At this time, Hua Ben Ku’s rank six immortal aperture was formed, her immortal ascension succeeded.

A high grade blessed land.

But there was no extra heaven and earth qi to refine a vital Immortal Gu.

But Hua Ben Ku was satisfied.

She could barely calm down.

During the natural inspiration, she had huge gains.

Her lifetime accumulation included her proudest killer move, it had received a qualitative transformation, becoming an immortal killer move.

As long as she used this move, she could sit on top of an Immortal Gu House and cry, it would cause the target to suffer heavy damages and even reduce the reputation of the Gu Immortals inside.

Chapter 2288: Trend of Immortal Ascension

After spectral heaven formed, it gradually stabilized. The beast groups that escaped earlier returned and lived in the new heaven again.

All the various grotto-heavens’ doors were tightly shut as they condensed into one spot, although there were some losses, they had managed to survive at least.

Despite Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s dominance of spectral heaven, he rarely moved.

The two heavens’ grotto-heavens tried not to open their doors and connect to the outside world, otherwise, it was possible that Spectral Soul Demon Venerable might approach them.

Fang Yuan, Star Constellation, and Giant Sun were busy refining natural dao marks, they were competing with each other as they fell into another deadlock.

While the venerables had ceased fire and everyone gained some respite, a large number of Gu Immortal seeds started to prepare for the attempt at immortal ascension!

Central Continent.

Heavenly Lotus Sect’s headquarters.

“Mu Huai greets first supreme elder.” A newly advanced rank six Gu Immortal knelt on the ground and greeted.

Heavenly Lotus Sect’s first supreme elder nodded and gave Mu Huai some words of encouragement before telling the immortal beside him: ”Wu Zhang, you nurtured Mu Huai so you will be the one making arrangements for him now.”

“Understood.” Wu Zhang answered as he brought Mu Huai out of the hall.

Wu Zhang was the fifth supreme elder of Heavenly Lotus Sect, long ago, he had created the Five Virtues Sect in Central Continent under his own name.

Five Virtues Sect had the five virtues elders, among them, Mu Huai was the wood virtue elder.

This time, he took a risk to undergo immortal ascension and succeeded, obtaining a medium grade blessed land. Wu Zhang brought him to Heavenly Lotus Sect as he gained the first supreme elder’s recognition.

From now on, Mu Huai was a member of Wu Zhang’s faction.

Days later, in Northern Plains.

An immortal ascension had just ended. Ouyang Bi Sang only had half of his body remaining, but he barely survived.

“Second brother, you succeeded!” Mo Shi Kuang shouted loudly as he ran forward in excitement.

Ouyang Bi Sang could only smile as he could not speak, he looked towards Liu Wen Wu with a grateful gaze.

If not for Liu Wen Wu’s help, Ouyang Bi Sang would have definitely died.

Right now, all thanks to Liu Wen Wu’s immortal killer move, Ouyang Bi Sang managed to survive.

Liu Wen Wu was once Liu tribe’s Gu Immortal seed, he was the sworn brother of Ouyang Bi Sang and Mo Shi Kuang, they had participated in the Imperial Court contest.

Liu Wen Wu was already a Gu Immortal, with his help, Ouyang Bi Sang also succeeded.

Liu Wen Wu understood what Ouyang Bi Sang was thinking, he smiled gently: ”Second brother, go ahead and rest. With me here, you will be safe.”

Ouyang Bi Sang did not even have the strength to nod, he shut his eyes and fell asleep. This showed how much trust he had in Liu Wen Wu.

“Big brother! Second brother has already succeeded in the immortal ascension, I can do it too. When are you going to help me? I want to try it too.” Mo Shi Kuang showed a heated gaze and spoke in an anxious tone.

Liu Wen Wu smiled bitterly: ”Third brother, calm down. You’ve seen what happened to your second brother, the immortal ascension is very dangerous, he almost failed to balance the three qi and nearly failed completely.”

“With just my help, it is very unreliable to try and go through the unpredictable immortal ascension calamities and tribulations.”

“We were lucky this time because the calamities and tribulations were within my abilities. But you need to know that there are all kinds of tribulations, by the time you undergo immortal ascension, we may not be so lucky.”

“This...” Mo Shi Kuang scratched his head.

Liu Wen Wu added: ”Let’s wait a while for your second brother’s cultivation level to stabilize. Once he has some immortal methods, we can work together to help you, that will be safer.”

“Brother, you are right, I’ll wait.” Mo Shi Kuang agreed with the words and changed his decision.

But he did not know that Liu Wen Wu was sighing internally.

Long ago, Liu Wen Wu was just a Gu Master, he did not have such a wide vision, thus, he became sworn brothers with Mo Shi Kuang.

But after becoming a Gu Immortal, he realized that the world was ruled by humanity, all variant humans were marginalized.

Mo Shi Kuang’s inkman identity was increasingly sensitive.

After Liu Wen Wu helped Ouyang Bi Sang to become an immortal, the latter would become Liu tribe’s external supreme elder. He would be Liu Wen Wu’s supporter and stand on the same political side as him.

Even though Ouyang Bi Sang was a purebred human, Liu tribe’s other factions still attacked them —

Why was Liu Wen Wu helping an external member instead of nurturing Liu tribe’s own Gu Masters?

If Mo Shi Kuang became an immortal through Liu Wen Wu’s help, it would be an even worse situation when he becomes a member of his political faction.

This would be a weakness for the other factions to target!

Sometimes, Liu Wen Wu envied the ten great ancient sects of Central Continent.

The supreme elders of these ancient sects were able to create their own sects under their personal name to gather and distribute Central Continent’s resource points. If they were able to nurture Gu Immortals, then those would become their subordinates or companions.

This was a superb political method by the ten great ancient sects to control Central Continent.

But this could not work in the super clan dominated regions. Creating one’s own force was too much of a taboo.

Like in Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s lifetime, he wanted a hereditary monarchy, he wanted to unify and rule the entire world.

Eastern Sea’s Hua Ben Ku, Central Continent’s Mu Huai, and Northern Plains’ Ouyang Bi Sang...

With the deep foundation of the super forces, they knew the secrets behind immortal ascension, thus, many of their Gu Immortal seeds were quickly using the opportunity to ascend.

Southern Border.

“Oh no!” Yi Peng had a grim expression, he watched as the heaven, earth and human qi lost their balance.

Within the qi lump, Gu Master Yi Chong failed the immortal ascension, by the time the three qi lump dispersed, he was almost reduced to a stick, his arms and legs were gone, his entire body was a bloody mess.

Calamities and tribulations could be resisted by allies, but the balancing of three qi was something that only the Gu Master could handle, no one else could help.

“Sigh, you were too immersed in the natural inspiration. I already told you not to be greedy!” Yi Peng landed beside Yi Chong and sighed regrettably.

Yi Chong did not move, after a few breaths of time, he died.

Half a month later.

On an unknown mountain in Central Continent, Ben Duo Yi succeeded in the immortal ascension.

“I’ve finally become a rank six Gu Immortal.” He had a complex emotion, while he felt joy and excitement, there was also regret.

In order to resist the calamities and tribulations while balancing the three qi, he gave up on the chance of natural inspiration.

Ben Duo Yi’s master was Yu Mu Chun, a refinement path quasi-great grandmaster, and also a member of Shadow Sect. From this aspect, Ben Duo Yi was also a remnant of Shadow Sect.

He was chosen by Yu Mu Chun due to his exceptional talent. Ben Duo Yi was more witty than the average hairy man, he had clear thoughts and did not lose to humans in terms of spirituality.

This successful immortal ascension also proved that Yu Mu Chun had great foresight.

After cleaning up, Ben Duo Yi quickly left the mountain.

Not long after, a Gu Immortal arrived at this place.

“This is it.”

“The star array calculation formation showed that someone underwent tribulation here.”

“Oh? Seems like a lone cultivator.”

After inspecting, this Gu Immortal obtained some clearer clues.

His eyes started to shine.

The immortal ascension of lone cultivators was very difficult, since they succeeded, it meant that they were very valuable.

“If I can recruit this person successfully, I will earn a huge sum of contribution points. This person can also be in my faction in the future.”

Places with people would have competition for benefits, leading to conflict.

As long as the internal conflict of a sect was well managed, it would be a great system for eliminating the weak and nurturing the strong.

The sect higher-ups were willing to see this.

However, this Gu Immortal did not know that the person undergoing tribulation was not a purebred human but a hairy man.

Ben Duo Yi’s immortal ascension was just one of countless others.

First, the five regions’ super forces’ Gu Immortal seeds made their attempt, afterwards, lone immortals and demonic cultivators also gave it a shot.

Gradually, the trend of immortal ascension was formed.

The immortal ascension trend involved the righteous path, demonic cultivator, and even lone cultivators. Many lone cultivators like Ben Duo Yi emerged and showed themselves, surprising the world with their appearance.

The super forces of the five regions were also involved. Among super forces, there was even some hidden competition!

Tie clan’s Tie Ruo Nan became a rank six metal path Gu Immortal.

Shang clan’s Shang Xin Ci succeeded in her immortal ascension.

Two of Western Desert’s Lin clan’s Gu Masters became immortals at the same time.

Eastern Sea’s Nan Gong clan did not fall behind, in just seven days, two Gu Masters took a risk and succeeded, they both had considerable gains.

Next, Southern Border’s Tie clan spread joyous news again.

The revived Tie Mu Bai and Tie Bai Qi both succeeded in their immortal ascension.

The one that shocked the five regions’ Gu Immortal world the most was Southern Border’s Wu clan.

Wu clan’s Zhong Yi, Wu Shen Tong, Divine Doctor Sheng Shou, Wei Shen Jing, and others became rank six Gu Immortals, there were a total of nine people who succeeded, this was the number one record in the five regions!

Wu clan was lacking Gu Immortals previously, but under Wu Yong’s reform, they took in a large number of external elders.

With these Gu Immortals’ presence, Wu clan immediately became the Southern Border’s super force with the most number of Gu Immortals!

Immediately, all sorts of congratulatory letters from various forces were sent to Wu Yong via treasure yellow heaven or information path Gu worms.

Wu clan gained a huge amount of fame but Wu Yong only snickered coldly without feeling happy at all.

“Such celebrations are just a form of self-consolation for the chaotic future under the rule of the venerables. So what if we have more Gu Immortals, can we be safe? Against the venerables, we are all ants.”

“Moreover, in terms of numbers, Heavenly Court, Longevity Heaven, and the Heaven and Earth Great Love Alliance definitely have the most number of immortal ascensions. They are huge and possess too many super forces under them.”

Wu Yong was extremely clear of the situation.

He knew that the true trial was not the number of successful immortal ascensions, it was the huge impact that these new external supreme elders would cause after joining Wu clan, when they go against the traditional factions that had been long established through time.

As the first supreme elder of Wu clan, Wu Yong needed to maintain the stability of the clan, if there was too many internal conflicts, they would weaken themselves. In that case, he might as well not implement this change.

Central Continent.

Xiao Qi Xing descended from the sky. There was some dust on his white robe.

His eyebrows were sharp like swords, his body was straight like a spear, his expression was cold and he gave off an aura of pride.

“Good, good, good.” Gu Immortal Xiao Bai Hong laughed as he stroked his beard, looking at Xiao Qi Xing with a gaze of appreciation: ”As expected of my beloved great-grandson. You went through the immortal ascension without external help.”

Xiao Qi Xing replied: ”Great-grandfather, this is nothing to be proud of. Many lone cultivators could achieve it, so why can’t I? Rank six is merely the starting point.”

“Hahaha, well said!” Xiao Bai Hong’s laughter became even louder.

Next, Xiao Qi Xing asked the other nine children of human path.

“What? Sun Yuan Hua, Gu Ting, and the rest became rank six Gu Immortals but did not refine their vital Gu into an Immortal Gu?”

“Hehe, they are really trash!”

Different from the others, the immortal ascension of the ten children of human path were kept secret.

They were the key to developing human path in Central Continent, they were the future pillars of human path. Before they grew to a certain level, it was better to let them grow safely.

Some succeeded in their immortal ascension, some died while taking risks.

Some made their ancestors proud, their names were spread throughout the world, while some kept quiet and developed earnestly, keeping a low profile.

Some did not try to undergo immortal ascension, like Feng Jin Huang.

Some did not even have the qualification to try, for example, Southern Border’s Xia Cha and Ba Shi Ba.

There were also some who were preparing to undergo immortal ascension, like Western Desert’s Mo Li, and sovereign immortal aperture’s Gu Yue Fang Xiang.

Chapter 2289: Natural Inspiration

Southern Border.

Deep within a certain Earth Trench.

Kong Ri Tian made the final inspection of the Gu formation and confirmed that it was operational.

For the last ten or so days, he had purposely picked this location and set up several Gu formations in the vicinity of over ten li.

“Although I am not specialized in formation path, I can still create some simple mortal formations. With these formations, you will be able to quickly notice any peculiarities in the surroundings.”

“You have my guidance, your chance of success at immortal ascension is high.” Kong Sheng Tian’s will was inside Kong Ri Tian’s mind, he said with some confidence.

Kong Ri Tian nodded: ”Ancestor, is there anything else I need to know?”

Kong Sheng Tian thought about it and said: ”Don’t be greedy during the natural inspiration, but remember to make good use of it. Since you cultivate qi path, ask heaven’s will questions about qi path related matters, don’t go after the secrets of other paths, it will not be worth it.”

“Natural inspiration has its limits, you can’t receive an infinite amount of information.”

“Furthermore, when asking qi path related questions, don’t be too broad or demand too much. Don’t ask for rank eight or nine qi path Immortal Gu recipes, you won’t receive a complete one. Even if you obtain an incomplete recipe, it may not even have five percent of the content!”

Kong Ri Tian kept these words in his mind as he nodded: ”Then I’ll ask qi path related questions that are problems that I currently face.”

“That is the right thing to do.” Kong Sheng Tian laughed loudly.

Kong Ri Tian shattered his aperture and started the tribulation.

Heaven and earth qi surged in the surroundings, forming a three days flying ring tribulation.

The flying ring was powerful and soared in the sky, lasting for three days and night.

Kong Ri Tian resisted with difficulty, eventually becoming a rank six Gu Immortal with a high grade blessed land.

Kong Sheng Tian’s will sighed: ”Your luck is very poor to have encountered such a tribulation. This tribulation is very special, it will last for three days and nights, even if you destroy the ring, it will regenerate.”

“To protect you, I expended almost all my immortal essence.”

“I told you not to provoke that Xiao Yan.”

Kong Ri Tian was confused: ”What does this have to do with Xiao Yan?”

Kong Sheng Tian said: ”Xiao Yan’s innate luck is comparable to you before obtaining Sheng Tian true inheritance. Most importantly, he is Shang Xin Ci’s subordinate. This girl has incredible luck, going against Xiao Yan will cause your luck to be expended against Xiao Yan and Shang Xin Ci.”

“Now that your luck is low, when undergoing tribulation, the three days flying ring tribulation appeared to waste all of my remaining immortal essence.”

Kong Ri Tian had an unsightly expression.

Back then, he attacked Xiao Yan and wanted to frame it on the demonic path Gu Master Bao Tong. In the end, an accident occurred as he did not expect the tap fire to contain an immortal material flame.

Kong Ri Tian was not a Gu Master then, he did not want to waste the precious immortal essence for Kong Sheng Tian to use his immortal method, thus, an intense battle broke out and the tap fire was dispersed, causing the immortal essence flame inside to explode.

The immortal material flame burned the entire mountain and could not be stopped, Xiao Yan and Bao Tong were both trapped in the fire.

Kong Ri Tian managed to escape with the help of Kong Sheng Tian’s will.

To think that the backlash of that decision would influence Kong Ri Tian’s immortal ascension.

Kong Sheng Tian sighed: ”I underestimated that Shang Xin Ci. Unless your cultivation level and battle strength surpasses her completely, do not provoke her anymore. Do not even touch anyone who is close to her.”

Kong Ri Tian gritted his teeth: ”Ancestor, are you exaggerating this?”

“Hmph, foolish child. Innate luck[1. There are a lot of ways to write luck in Chinese, this one is written as ’qi variable’, which is why qi path is involved.] is profound and mystical, back in my days when qi path dominated the world, many geniuses were able to catch a glimpse of it profundity.”

“Do not underestimate the variance of luck.”

“Look at Giant Sun Immortal Venerable. I believe this person must have used innate luck as a reference when he created luck path.”

“You have already become a Gu Immortal, you should learn more. Gu cultivation paths are not independent of each other, they influence and affect each other in a connected way. The connection between qi path and luck path is this innate luck.”

Eventually, Kong Sheng Tian’s will convinced Kong Ri Tian after a lengthy talk.

“Gu Immortal cultivation is far more profound and deep than Gu Master cultivation. I am lucky to have your help, ancestor, otherwise, I would have to undergo immortal ascension without knowing anything!” Kong Ri Tian sighed.

Next, he consulted: ”What do I do now, what is the most important thing?”

Kong Sheng Tian’s will did not hesitate: ”Little fellow, although you become an immortal, there is not enough heaven and earth qi to help you refine your vital Gu into an Immortal Gu.”

“This qi path Gu worm is crucial to the entire Sheng Tian true inheritance.”

Kong Ri Tian understood at once: ”So now, I need to refine that Immortal Gu?”

Kong Sheng Tian’s will snorted coldly: ”Hehe, the ignorant have no fear. Do you think you can refine an Immortal Gu? Even if you go bankrupt, you will still have no chance of success.”

“Do you know that most rank six Gu Immortals do not even own one rank six Immortal Gu? Most rank seven Gu Immortals spend their lives trying to get a rank seven Immortal Gu. This is true even for venerables. Go and think about how hard it is for a Gu Immortal to refine an Immortal Gu that suits them!”

Kong Ri Tian was tongue-tied, he felt shocked: ”This is too hard, isn’t it?”

Kong Sheng Tian’s will sighed: ”Gu Immortal cultivation is tough, it is much risker than being a Gu Master. Kid, you need to learn to survive now. Each calamity and tribulation is a test. You have a higher starting point than many others, but you cannot act rashly. Especially in trying to refine an Immortal Gu, it can make you bankrupt without any gains in return.”

Kong Ri Tian was troubled: ”What do I do now? Ancestor, you told me that I should make my vital Gu an Immortal Gu, but you also told me that I cannot refine Immortal Gu. So what should I do? Stop beating around the bush.”

Kong Sheng Tian’s will snorted again: ”Kid, are you willing to listen to me now? earlier, I told you time and again not to provoke that Xiao Yan, but what did you do? You are just too young!”

“Yes, yes.” Kong Ri Tian quickly apologized: ”Ancestor, from now on, I will listen to you.”

Seeing that his descendant had given in, Kong Sheng Tian’s will stopped wasting time, he said: ”You are quite lucky to have a refinement path venerable like Fang Yuan in your era. Go make a transaction with him if you want to refine Immortal Gu.”

“Wait, you want me to transact with him in treasure yellow heaven? Aren’t you afraid...”

Before Kong Ri Tian could continue, Kong Sheng Tian rebuked him: ”Do you think a grand venerable will care about a rank six Immortal Gu? I know what you are afraid of, aren’t you afraid that Fang Yuan is still connected to Shang Xin Ci? But you did not do anything to her either.”

Kong Ri Tian heard this and thought about it, feeling a little hurt internally.

Kong Sheng Tian’s will was not wrong.

In Kong Ri Tian and Shang Xin Ci’s encounters, he had always suffered a loss. Last time, he was chased after by Shang Xin Ci and Wu Ji because of Sheng Tian true inheritance. Afterwards, he also suffered losses during his tribulation after provoking Xiao Yan.

Shang Xin Ci was having a great life now, while Kong Ri Tian was suffering more now.

“Let’s go to treasure yellow heaven, we will talk to Fang Yuan’s will.” Eventually, Kong Ri Tian said.

Back in Western Desert.

The sandstorm stopped.

Mo Li had rank six cultivation level, he bowed deeply at the featherman Gu Immortals in front of him.

“Friends from Yi clan, thank you for the help. Otherwise, I would not have been able to become a Gu Immortal on my own.” Mo Li thanked them sincerely.

Ever since the contest in Sand Heap blessed land, he was saved by the mysterious super force, Yi clan, in Western Desert.

Mo Li came to Yi clan’s headquarters and after interacting with them, he found that they were actually all feathermen.

This time, with the help of Yi clan’s Gu Immortals, Mo Li became an immortal.

Yi clan’s Gu Immortal Zhou Yi Kou said: ”Friend Mo Li, you are too polite. You are one who obtained Thieving Heaven true inheritance, that means you are his inheritor. Back then, our Yi clan’s ancestor was helped by Lord Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable and survived. With the help of his method, Yi clan was able to stay hidden for so many years.”

“Lord Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable is our benefactor, the entire Yi clan believes that Lord Demon Venerable has not died so easily without making a sound!”

“By helping you now, we also want to repay the debt we owe to Lord Thieving Heaven.”

“If one day in the future, Lord Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable revives, our entire Yi clan will follow him by his side.”

“Thus, we are comrades.”

Mo Li was deeply moved by the featherman Gu Immortal Zhou Yi Kou’s words, he had a warm feeling in his heart.

Central Continent.

Wei Wu Shang looked at the qi lump in his immortal aperture with a heated gaze.

Just earlier, he had succeeded in the tribulation, becoming a human path Gu Immortal.

He obtained a high grade blessed land, the remaining heaven and earth qi was enough for him to refine a vital Immortal Gu.

His vital Gu was thief Gu, it was already enveloped in heaven and earth qi now.

“I heard that Gu Ting, Sun Yuan Hua, and the rest became immortals but did not refine a human path Immortal Gu. I am different from them!”

“Recently, while deeply asleep at night, I had the urge to pee and woke up. At that moment, I gained a burst of inspiration and comprehended thief Gu’s Immortal Gu recipe.”

“With this Immortal Gu recipe and so much heaven and earth qi remaining, I can definitely refine thief Immortal Gu. Hahaha, this Immortal Gu recipe is worth waking up to pee at night.”

Although Wei Wu Shang entered the derivation formation, his memories were altered and caused him to think that it was inspiration that allowed him to create thief Immortal Gu’s recipe.

But...

After fifteen minutes.

Wei Wu Shang grunted as he fell to the ground. The heaven and earth qi were completely expended while his vital Gu was heavily damaged.

“I failed the Gu refinement?”

“Impossible!”

Wei Wu Shang could not believe what had happened.

“To refine the vital Gu, I used heaven and earth qi. This is borrowing the power of heaven and earth to refine Gu, it has nothing to do with my refinement path attainment. So how did I fail?”

Wei Wu Shang could only think of one explanation: ”I failed because Immortal Gu is unique?!”

Thinking of this, Wei Wu Shang shook his head.

In his view, this was even more impossible.

It meant that someone else had already refined thief Immortal Gu.

“I am the creator of thief Immortal Gu, how can anyone get the recipe before me? Unless... thief Immortal Gu already exists naturally in the world?”

“But that’s also strange... human path should not have developed this deeply yet.”

Wei Wu Shang fell into deep confusion as he contemplated.

Chapter 2290: Heaven’s Will, Please Scram

Heavenly Court.

Another Gu Immortal walked out of the derivation formation.

This female immortal wore golden armor, there was a golden cape flowing down her back, extending from her shoulder to the ground.

She was taller than normal people and her shoulders were broad, when she walked, her long legs were the most eye-catching as they made her look beautiful and elegant.

Her nose bridge was tall, her lips were thin and her eyes were also thin. She had outstanding presence, she was like born royalty that ruled above the common man. When she looked at people, because of her height, she often had to look down. She had an authoritative aura that was fermented naturally within her, people would lower their heads and not dare to look at her directly, it was as if they could only look at her feet in order to not offend her.

She was Qin Ding Ling.

After walking out of the derivation formation, Qin Ding Ling quickly recovered her senses.

She turned around and looked at the derivation formation behind her, her eyes shone with unprecedented brightness.

She was very excited!

Her entry to the formation gave her great gains.

The most exciting thing that she obtained from this derivation formation was the hope for Heavenly Court to defeat Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, Heaven Refining Demon Venerable, and Spectral Soul Demon Venerable!

Why was that?

Simply because the derivation formation’s ability to develop a Gu cultivator’s path was just too powerful.

Like how Qin Ding Ling obtained huge gains when she entered the formation this time.

This was not just her personal growth, it helped to push the entire luck path forward in development.

Thanks to her going into the formation, the luck path of the world took a huge stride forward, obtaining huge development.

What did this mean?

This meant that as long as more luck path Gu Immortals like Qin Ding Ling entered the derivation formation, luck path would develop further.

When the number of times accumulate, the quantitative growth would trigger a qualitative transformation.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable would be kicked out of his supreme grandmaster attainment level!

Supreme grandmaster attainment level meant that the Gu cultivator’s understanding of a certain path was equivalent to the world.

After Qin Ding Ling entered the formation, she became the core that used the vast number of inheritances in Heavenly Court to deduce many new research results of luck path.

These new results were just some accumulation that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable could decipher with just a glance.

Because these luck path research results were still under the scope of the current profundity of luck path, it had not exceeded the existing limits. It was a quantitative growth but not a qualitative change.

But once the quantity accumulated, there would be a qualitative transformation.

Once there was a qualitative change, the entire world’s luck path attainment level would rise by a level, while Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s attainment level would lag behind.

At that point, he would no longer be a luck path supreme grandmaster!

In that case, he would not be a Dao Lord anymore and would not be able to refine natural luck path dao marks.

That would be a disastrous blow to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable!

“It is a pity that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had been protecting luck path from getting spread widely in the world.”

“Otherwise, if there are more luck path Gu Immortals like me to enter the derivation formation, we will be able to kick Giant Sun Immortal Venerable out of supreme grandmaster attainment level.”

Qin Ding Ling expressed her pity towards this.

After leaving the derivation formation, she would not be able to enter for a long time. Going in forcefully would not have any gains but instead cause her irreparable harm.

It was too late to start nurturing luck path Gu Immortals.

Only a peak rank eight Gu cultivator like Qin Ding Ling could promote the advancement of the entire luck path.

Of course, it was not impossible for other luck path Gu Immortals or Gu Masters.

But they had not reached the apex of luck path, it was simply too hard to exceed the current accomplishments of heaven and earth.

For Heavenly Court, this was too costly to try and the gains they could derive from it were just too small.

“Next, it is my turn.” Fairy Maiden Soul smiled at Qin Ding Ling as she walked past the latter.

Fairy Maiden Soul went into the derivation formation and vanished.

She was Heavenly Court’s soul path great expert from Spectral Soul’s era, she was on par with Thunder Ghost True Monarch.

This entry into the formation would derive great gains, it would promote the development of the world’s soul path.

“It is a pity that Heavenly Court currently lacks refinement path great experts. There are many refinement path Gu Immortals in the ten great ancient sects but few are rank eight. Furthermore, none are great experts who have reached a certain height of refinement path.”

Qin Ding Ling pondered.

Heavenly Court’s derivation formation showed the terrifying power of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable!

But to kick a venerable out of supreme grandmaster attainment level, the difficulty was too high.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s luck path, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s soul path, and Heaven Refining Demon Venerable’s refinement path. There was a need to have many Gu cultivators in these three paths.

Heavenly Court had the derivation formation but rank nine derivation Gu was not refined by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, thus, it was still wild and took in natural essence on its own.

As a result, the derivation formation needed very little immortal essence to operate.

But Heavenly Court lacked crucial members.

Without enough great experts in these paths, the derivation formation could not kick the venerables out of their thrones.

“Maybe, this is the reason why Heavenly Court needs to focus on developing human path?” Qin Ding Ling had a flash of inspiration.

She could only see a small part of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s plan, she could not decipher the big picture.

Eastern Sea.

The sea was calm without any waves.

Gu Yue Fang Xiang was at the crucial moment of his immortal ascension.

Heaven, earth and human qi had already surrounded him completely.

Gu Yue Fang Xiang gritted his teeth as he did his best to balance the three qi, condensing them as much as he could.

“I must succeed!”

“I need to become a Gu Immortal to save my mother.”

“Also, I need to become a Gu Immortal and gain more strength to find my father!”

Gu Yue Fang Xiang cheered himself on, but soon, most of his attention was diverted to something else.

At this moment, he sensed heaven’s will.

This was the moment for natural inspiration!

“You must succeed.” The mermaid immortal Lian Ke Xin floated in the air openly as she appeared right beside Gu Yue Fang Xiang.

Her eyes did not move at all, she stared at him fixedly.

Unfortunately, the process of balancing the three qi could not be interrupted, otherwise, Lian Ke Xin would rather do it for him.

This time, she had taken the mission from the mission board to ’accidentally’ meet Gu Yue Fang Xiang and coax him to go to a place suitable for immortal ascension.

The truth was, Fang Yuan secretly opened sovereign immortal aperture’s door to bring Gu Yue Fang Xiang to the five regions.

While Gu Yue Fang Xiang was undergoing tribulation, Fang Yuan hid near him but was not idling.

He was secretly using a powerful rank nine heaven path killer move.

It was not obscured heavenly secret, this was — Stealing Heavenly Secret!

After activating this move, one could steal the knowledge of heaven’s will when a Gu Master undergoes ascension and experiences natural inspiration.

Stealing heavenly secret killer move’s first core was the rank nine heavenly secret Immortal Gu, the second core was rank eight great thief Immortal Gu.

Back then, when Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable first created rank eight heavenly secret Gu, the initial goal was to use it to sense heaven and earth, attempting to artificially enter natural inspiration.

Normally, a Gu cultivator would only have one opportunity at natural inspiration in their life.

When a Gu Master undergoes immortal ascension, they would use the opportunity when the aperture turns into an immortal aperture world to gain the recognition of heaven’s will and communicate with it.

At this time, the Gu Master would be able to ask heaven’s will questions, and their inquiries would be answered to a certain extent.

This was a once in a lifetime opportunity but the extent of answers was limited.

Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable succeeded.

There were no events in the world that heaven and earth did not know of.

Just using rank eight heavenly secret Gu would allow the Gu cultivator to ask heaven’s will and get an answer. It was able to expose the secrets of heaven and earth, even without any evidence, the Gu Immortal could reach the truth.

By using heavenly secret Gu with other Gu worms, before undergoing tribulation, they would be able to find out the content of the calamities and tribulations to make appropriate countermeasures.

And in terms of concealment, obscured heavenly secret was the best example.

If Fang Yuan used rank nine heavenly secret Gu alone, he would not be able to get any answers from heaven’s will.

Because heaven’s will did not like him.

Fang Yuan was one of the main culprits who destroyed fate Gu, heaven’s will had been trying to kill him the entire time.

With such a relationship, how could heaven’s will give him any answers?

Fang Yuan understood the advantages of natural inspiration. Earlier in the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, why did he produce so many powerful killer moves?

Other than self deduction, he had also secretly used the natural inspiration of many Gu Masters in his immortal aperture when they ascended, saving him precious time and energy.

Without these exceptional killer moves, Fang Yuan would have gotten killed by the two venerables.

Thus, natural inspiration was a huge reason why Fang Yuan emerged victorious in Crazed Demon Cave.

Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable wanted more natural inspiration opportunities, so did Fang Yuan!

Every Gu cultivator knew the precious value of natural inspiration.

To do this, Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable created rank eight heavenly secret Gu, what about Fang Yuan?

He made stealing heavenly secret killer move.

This killer move was created long ago, but it was only rank eight then and had limited strength.

Honestly speaking, it was worthless.

Too much immortal essence was expended for too little gains.

He might as well order Gu Masters to ask specific questions during their natural inspiration.

But this was in the past.

Right now, the situation had changed greatly.

The reason was rank nine heavenly secret Gu!

Where did rank nine heavenly secret Gu originate from?

Truthful floating ice.

This was Limitless Demon Venerable’s arrangement, he had used the chaos outside the world to fuel the Crazed Demon formation, it was a grand accomplishment from countless years of effort.

Starting from the eighth layer, Crazed Demon Cave was isolated from the five regions. Crazed Demon formation was no exception.

But Fang Yuan refined rank nine heavenly secret Gu in his own sovereign immortal aperture, it was also isolated from the five regions.

This meant that the current Gu cultivation world did not have the recipe of rank nine heavenly secret Gu.

By having rank nine heavenly secret Gu, on just this point, Fang Yuan was already above the entire world!

Rank eight stealing heavenly secret had limited power but rank nine stealing heavenly secret was above the world, it surpassed even heaven’s will!

Each time there was a Gu Master undergoing natural inspiration, Fang Yuan would activate rank nine stealing heavenly secret killer move.

The gains were simply unimaginably immense!

Fang Yuan had a chance to observe everything that happened in the world.

In normal situations, the natural inspiration of Gu Masters was limited, this was the restriction set by heaven’s will. But Fang Yuan’s stealing heavenly secret could directly steal the answer, it did not matter what heaven’s will intended to do!